<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">

<tv source-info-name="pluto_tv_us" source-info-url="pluto.tv">
  <channel id="DocuBox.hr">
    <display-name>DocuBox</display-name>
    <url>https://www.a1.hr/raspored</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/ad/96/zqmcf5r0_o.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008230000" stop="20231009000000">
    <title lang="hr">Lagerfield - The Kaiser Of Fashion</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(United States of America, 2019) A biography of the controversial fashion savant, creator of extraordinary fashion show sets, renowned photographer, and author of breathtaking books. Lagerfeld is the quintessential renaissance man.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/66f97ad561b130553c109e34b979f12b57e0b69d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009000000" stop="20231009010000">
    <title lang="hr">The Species Return</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France) With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. It is up to us to understand that energy. This series examine various species that have made a comeback among our European landscapes, providing "close to home" examples. We are now fully aware that every coming year brings about a reduction in our planet's biodiversity. One in eight species of bird, one in four mammals, and one in three amphibians are threatened with extinction by the end of the 21st century. But this is not necessarily a lost cause. With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. Even in our immediate surroundings, in a highly urbanised and industrialised Europe, some species of wildlife, which had been virtually wiped out, are reappearing. There are various reasons for this wildlife.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/215fcbf6379347c2cd660fdfc35458c949f49ee2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009010000" stop="20231009013000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Japan-tohoku: Japan Rising, United States of America) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009013000" stop="20231009020000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Japan-Tokyo - Electric City, United States of America) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009020000" stop="20231009023000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(San Diego, United States of America, 2012) Get your sun tan lotion on, because we're headed to the land of perfect weather and sunsets. We'll sample a fish taco, climb the 100's of steps of the California Tower, stand on the flight deck of the USS Midway, as well as, revisit San Diego's founding on the San Salvador at the San Diego Maritime museum.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009023000" stop="20231009030000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Montreal, United States of America, 2012) Bonjour! We're headed to Quebec Province on today's show. First, we get blown away by the thunderous pipes at Montreal's Notre Dame Basilica. After that, we go underneath the city at the Pointe a Calliere archaeology museum. Next, we'll learn about the native ecosystem at the gigantic, indoor, BioDome. Lastly, we'll learn about the 1967 Montreal Expo at the structures that are still visited today.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009030000" stop="20231009033000">
    <title lang="hr">Everyday Elements</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Carbon, Gold, Neon, Zirconium, Antimony, Italy) A series that puts chemistry in our everyday experience by showing the living connection we have with the chemicals and elements that make up our world. The matter that built skies and seas, the atoms that make up you and me, the chemistry around us that forms the things we touch, smell and see. This series shows us what the objects in our universe and in our homes are made from and why the particles around us behave as they do. Everything around us is built from Everyday Elements.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/00e11946a460c8e64f2ef2f35fd134c7f2175891.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009033000" stop="20231009040000">
    <title lang="hr">Everyday Elements</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Silver, Hydrogen, Phosphorus, Germanium, Sulphur, Italy) A series that puts chemistry in our everyday experience by showing the living connection we have with the chemicals and elements that make up our world. The matter that built skies and seas, the atoms that make up you and me, the chemistry around us that forms the things we touch, smell and see. This series shows us what the objects in our universe and in our homes are made from and why the particles around us behave as they do. Everything around us is built from Everyday Elements.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/00e11946a460c8e64f2ef2f35fd134c7f2175891.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009040000" stop="20231009050000">
    <title lang="hr">Depleted Uranium</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France, 2012) More than 50 countries now possess weapons based on depleted uranium (DU). Experimentation has been rife, and the consequences for civilians and the military alike have been dramatic. This investigation compares and contrasts the arguments of those who defend and attack a technology that is highly toxic. For 20 years, scientists, doctors, veterans and activists have denounced the use of DU. Against them are the arms industry lobbyists and nuclear authorities who continue to minimise the risks. Through archive documents, interviews and in situ investigations, accompanied by key witnesses (victims, experts...) we aim to present a clearer picture of the issues and stakes linked to the use of DU. Quick-paced, with a sense of urgency, the film underlines the essential background and conflicting viewpoints, enabling viewers to make up their own minds about a subject that concerns us all.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/37a92a4fdd8d0746a3a5ed29b497e07b1effd417.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009050000" stop="20231009053000">
    <title lang="hr">Close Quarter Battle</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Snipers &amp; Scout, Bohemia, United States of America, 2012) Joint Task Force Two (JTF 2) is the elite Canadian Forces Special Operations unit responsible for a broad range of missions, including counter-terrorism and armed assistance to other government departments. Highly secretive, JTF 2 and its predecessor, the Canadian Airborne Regiment, have been deployed in hotspots around the world from Haiti to Bosnia. This episode focuses on the legendary JTF sniper teams and their use in Afghanistan alongside the British SAS and the US Delta Force at "the sharp end of the spear." A book written by an ex-JTF member explains how, in 2006, both the Pentagon and the British Foreign Oﬃ ce noted the instrumental role that JTF 2 played in the rescue of the British and Canadian Christian Peacemaker Team held hostage in Iraq. Unique in look, the FN P90 personal defense weapon, used by JTF 2 soldiers and special police around the world, will be highlighted in this program.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7feffc49f5e30f537ccdb17974584cae10f136a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009053000" stop="20231009060000">
    <title lang="hr">Close Quarter Battle</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(S.W.A.T., Bohemia, United States of America, 2012) In 1968, a new form of military policing was being developed in a rural area north of Los Angeles. The Los Angeles Police Department sent an observer to this unit, and he, in turn, took this knowledge back to the LAPD. This contributed to the development of the department's first Special Weapons and Tactics (S.W.A.T.) team. This CQB episode takes an historical journey to examine how this incident affected and changed police tactics around the world. Using CQB's trademark "sub-second" analysis, the program also looks at how police S.W.A.T. teams train, plan and equip themselves for the challenges of urban combat. The dramatization of a 1980s S.W.A.T. siege of a gang safe-house demonstrates the complicated challenge of protecting innocent people who might be caught in the line of fire, as well as the specifics of the squad's training regimen, how they communicated, and the special equipment they used.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7feffc49f5e30f537ccdb17974584cae10f136a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009060000" stop="20231009070000">
    <title lang="hr">Rip Files</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Explore the Darkness, United States of America, 2016) Re-visit some of the team's most memorable cases.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b3169fe81752d7187aca9d116f43b30b3ec95cda.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009070000" stop="20231009080000">
    <title lang="hr">Herding Sheep In Iceland</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Germany, 2012) Starting at the beginning of September, the Northern Lights unveil their magical patterns on Iceland's starry skies. At the same time, Icelanders celebrate the "Retir": sheep and horses are herded to the lowlands. 4,500 sheep and 800 horses spend 3 to 4 months in the untamed highlands. Now, they are rounded up. No single farmer can herd so many animals to the lowlands. The entire community helps.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/ee023d015c4f1b53920e2ad8021f404adb159a73.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009080000" stop="20231009093000">
    <title lang="hr">Vacaciones Con Fidel</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Argentina, 2013) Tristan is a journalist with deep political convictions who worked for years doing journalistic research. Once married and with three children, he accepts a much more remunerative job on commercial television and gradually becomes involved in a life he did not expect.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5b850a6e285c7ee4419bc73153aa9064296e3747.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009093000" stop="20231009100000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys in Africa</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Ngorongoro: Battle For the Crater, Canada, 2017) Nicknamed the Garden of Eden, this volcanic caldera is home to over 25,000 big game animals. Here survival isn't just a game—it's a matter of life and death. You'll witness one of the great acts of nature—buffalo, lion and hyena in a face-to-face struggle for dominance. Life in the crater can take surprising twists.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/48b88f170ca85cf21edf213acebbf8658e33c18e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009100000" stop="20231009103000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys in Africa</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Nairobi: The Enchanted City, Canada, 2017) Nairobi is the capital of Kenya and one of the most fascinating cities in Africa. On our visit we'll see the colonial architecture of a bygone era and the ultra-modern side of town as well. We'll learn the truth behind the "Out of Africa" story and our host gets eye-to-eye with some endangered giraffes.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/48b88f170ca85cf21edf213acebbf8658e33c18e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009103000" stop="20231009113000">
    <title lang="hr">Past Hunters</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(The Haunted Parade, England, 2021) Derek Acorah's The Past Hunters travel to Hoylake and investigate a building known as The Parade. Dating back to 1909, this once former school, still seems to have ghostly pupils and teachers taking class.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/3bbfc89dfc434680cedf07251e71c27c71331722.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009113000" stop="20231009120000">
    <title lang="hr">Wow, I Never Knew That!</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Coca Cola, Slinky, Frisbee, United States of America) Wow, I Never Knew That! is a whimsical, half-hour television series that is jam-packed with exciting tidbits and fascinating facts that uncover the truths and origins behind the stuff you're already familiar with. From the items you use every day to the phrases you use in conversation to the habits you're so accustomed to, you'll be fascinated to learn how they've all really come about! Learn how a pharmacist and an accountant created the most famous drink in the world, COCA COLA! And, learn the "BEAR" truth behind how a U.S. president helped create everyone's favorite stuffed toy, THE TEDDY BEAR! Then, how did a piece of wire accidentally "SLINK" its way to become a fantastic fun toy for children? Plus, how a the WIFFLE BALL was invented.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/4b68bfb7c8a86555d661abb7e44615e226afd311.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009120000" stop="20231009123000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Vancouver, British Columbia, United States of America, 2012) This episode we visit the bright lights of Vancouver, Canada. We'll swing along the famous Capilano Suspension Bridge, get tranquil in Dr. Sun Yat Sen's Chinese garden, learn about Captain Vancouver at the Vancouver Maritime Museum, dig up Cesna Em "The City Before the City" at the Museum of Vancouver, and dive into the city's seedy underbelly at the Police Museum.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009123000" stop="20231009130000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys In India</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Mysore: The Rebel Kingdom, Canada, United States of America, 2017) Journeys explores the history and fables that surround the controversial rebel leader Tipu Sultan. Mysore was the center of an Empire strong enough to challenge the British. Tipu's over-the-top personality is reflected in the architecture, gardens and stories that still permeate this metropolis.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/1c9e8ee0ca875068a7ae4c86b19ea243172d376d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009130000" stop="20231009140000">
    <title lang="hr">Race to Mars</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Canada, France, 2007) Based on contemporary, international research being done at space agencies and in laboratories. Race To Mars imagines the first human voyage to Race to Mars capturing every exhilarating detail, from lift-off through touchdown on Mars to return to Earth, drawing viewers into the heart of an amazing journey. In the year 2030, the race to be the first to reach the Red Planet is on.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/aad71e1af50ec7e0f077b36f39ff5bbf8ddcfec8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009140000" stop="20231009150000">
    <title lang="hr">The Species Return</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France) With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. It is up to us to understand that energy. This series examine various species that have made a comeback among our European landscapes, providing "close to home" examples. We are now fully aware that every coming year brings about a reduction in our planet's biodiversity. One in eight species of bird, one in four mammals, and one in three amphibians are threatened with extinction by the end of the 21st century. But this is not necessarily a lost cause. With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. Even in our immediate surroundings, in a highly urbanised and industrialised Europe, some species of wildlife, which had been virtually wiped out, are reappearing. There are various reasons for this wildlife.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/215fcbf6379347c2cd660fdfc35458c949f49ee2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009150000" stop="20231009153000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(United States of America, 2010) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009153000" stop="20231009160000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(United States of America, 2010) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009160000" stop="20231009163000">
    <title lang="hr">Quirky Science</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Singapore) Who came up with the idea of canned food? It began with a battle between French and British armies, two centuries ago. Napoleon Bonaparte faced many problems with his goal to dominate Europe, one of which was feeding a large and sprawling army. In 1809 Napoleon held a contest, with a prize of 12,000 francs for the person who could come up with the most innovative method of preserving food. The winner was Nicolas François Appert who submitted a method of boiling and sealing food in glass bottles. Well if the French were going to travel farther and farther, the British needed to invent something as well: canning. However, opening the cans was quite a challenge – soldiers worked with stones and bayonets and it was only 30 years later that someone designed the first can opener! Although cans travel much easier across a battlefield, for decades they would not only mysteriously explode, but would also cause the harshest diseases. But how could the scientists of those days know? It wasn't until 50 years after Appert that Louis Pasteur discovered why canning (generally) worked so well. By testing the influence of air on broths, he did away with the idea that things spoiled "spontaneously" and launched his 'germ theory'. Even though canned foods became safer, they didn't taste any better. The ultra-lengthy boiling process was obviated with the help of pressure-cooking. And now, the future brings "zapped" canned food, something called 'raddaperization'. Does the name ring a bell?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8b3239061316f3441ba121811ae07d37f935ca50.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009163000" stop="20231009170000">
    <title lang="hr">Quirky Science</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Singapore) Throughout the history of mankind - the business of curing, of understanding and treating disease, has taken a rather peculiar path. Some procedures have proven to be very efficient while other methods could only have made things worse for the patient. Up to the 16th Century "treating" someone could mean diminishing one of four bodily fluids, paving the way for bloodletting. As it turns out, modern science proves that bloodletting does help in rare cases. In fact, bloodsucking leeches are excellent helpers to cure wounds. We now know that one little creature is the cause for many diseases: bacteria. But until the mid-19th century, many felt that such tiny organisms such as germs could not possibly kill larger ones such as humans. After all, we can't even see them with the naked eye! How then, did we discover them? Thanks to one doctor who decided to take a good look …between his teeth. Since then, we have found a cure for most bacterial infections in the form of Antibiotics. This was accidently discovered by Alexander Fleming - whilst leaving the office for a holiday, he left a culture plate smeared with his personal nasal mucus on his lab bench only to find that mould surrounding this mucus actually inhibited its growth. In the new millennium, this discovery of such a "Superdrug" is threatened by the advent of the 'Superbug'. Have these cures led to bacteria becoming more tolerant and harder to kill? What else will the future bring? A cure against the flu?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8b3239061316f3441ba121811ae07d37f935ca50.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009170000" stop="20231009180000">
    <title lang="hr">Salty Love</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Australia, 2005) Salty Love is an underwater story of love and how marine life has found ingenious ways to reproduce. From the magic of coral spawning, the dance of the manta ray, the bond of marine mammals, the dedication of the male sea horse, the labour of love by sea turtles there are so many amazing underwater relationships.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5381709d2c2bdbe7b485ff08d76e2732802a6b22.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009180000" stop="20231009183000">
    <title lang="hr">Wild Ones</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Biggest, United States of America, Bohemia, 2014) The colossal elephant. The lush tropical forests of Asia hold within them some of nature's mightiest creatures.Each of these silent footsteps carries with it the immense weight of the world's largest land mammal. The intimidating birds with soaring grace and aerial prowess, birds dominate our skies. To remain the undisputed pioneers of the air most bird species are feather light and relatively small. The barrel-like Hippo Lumbering across land, the enormity of the barrel like hippo is without question. Other grass eaters are frail by comparison. The towering giraffe standing taller than any other living animal in their towering majesty is the proud and elegant giraffe. The gigantic whale the Mighty whale graces our oceans with a size and strength unrivalled on land. Three times longer than the tallest giraffe and weighing more than a dozen hippos' the beautiful humpback whale is most famed for its mystical and haunting song. Which is the biggest of them all?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8c15ec21da13c41242b8229836d6429ec4f41779.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009183000" stop="20231009190000">
    <title lang="hr">Wild Ones</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Camouflage, United States of America, Bohemia, 2014) Camouflaged cats. Some animals will never be inconspicuous, others blend so perfectly with their surroundings that they can move through them without detection. For many of the cats of Africa, camouflage is key to survival. From the spots of the cheetah, the rosettes of the leopard and the stripes and dots of the serval, these cats have evolved to merge with their habitat. Hidden lizards. Feeding on these harvester ants, is a beautifully adapted predator, the regal horned lizard. Merging perfectly with their surroundings these small reptiles live in the rocky, gravelly, desert like habitats of Arizona where they make a living almost exclusively on ants. Cryptic snakes. In the leaf litter of Australia's woodlands and scrub hides one of its most cryptic and dangerous snakes – the death adder. The camouflaging patterns of snakes are mesmerizing – from the pearly multicolored sheen of the carpet python to the mottled bands of the death adder, snakes can be hidden right before our eyes. Shimmering cuttlefish . Many animals can hide and many can disguise themselves to some degree, but few can rival the camouflaging capabilities of the magnificent cuttlefish. Cuttlefish can not only change color, they can also change their shape as well as their texture as they morph through seamless variations of themselves.…. and concealed chameleons. Making camouflage an art form are the verdant sauntering highly distinctive chameleons that make their homes in rain forests, grasses, trees and bushes. There are well over 100 species of chameleon around today, ranging from the tiny pygmy chameleon to the prehistoric looking horned chameleon, most are found in Africa and Madagascar. Birds. In the frozen climbs of the northern hemisphere winter, ptarmigans blend against their snowy surroundings. Invisible spiders - Crab Spider. There is one tiny creature that has evolved a camouflage that is so perfect in its simplicity it is often overlooked by the casual human observer. Adapted to their hunting terrain the crab spiders that are found on bark and leaves are darker in coloration than those found on flowers which is the master of disguise?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/a28d962f612173fff3d2e7b72b0237fbaac570c9.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009190000" stop="20231009200000">
    <title lang="hr">Berber, A Quest For Water</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France, 2014) In the remote valleys of the Atlas range in Morocco, lies a village Tizi Anoucheg, where water is a rare resource. Berbers are the only people to be found in this harsh environment. They convert the red and dried valleys into a lush green using ancestral irrigation methods. With climate change threatening their very existence one man rises to the occasion &amp; tries to solve the severe water problem.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/28e1d76616885d24d86e0d956a14e09fc554f6da.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009200000" stop="20231009203000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys In India</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Nagarhole And Bandipur: The Southern Paradise Of India, Canada, United States of America, 2017) These two national parks have some of the most diverse wildlife found on the Indian subcontinent. From the ancestors of our domesticated livestock to leopards, bear and elephants—this is a photographer's paradise. Join Bill as he attempts to track down two of the hardest predators to photograph—the leopard and the sloth bear.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/1c9e8ee0ca875068a7ae4c86b19ea243172d376d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009203000" stop="20231009220000">
    <title lang="hr">WWII Documentary Films</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Remember Pearl Harbor Narrated By Tom Selleck, United States of America, 2016) Award-winning documentary films produced to enlighten future generations about the personal stories of the WWII generations.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5fd5c62bb216bf178deb7f9826706bf611219a43.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009220000" stop="20231009230000">
    <title lang="hr">The Islanders</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Jeju, South Korea, France, 2009) Discovering some the world's hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud of their insularity and their distinct sense of identity. A rich cocktail of history, customs, cuisine and economic resources distinguishes the island people and the nature and beaches that surround them. Our documentaries explore the varied and often little known lifestyles and peculiarities on the twenty featured islands. The approach so effectively used during our series on beaches and coastal areas, is here recreated, each program a mix of stunning visuals and interviews, which together highlight the exotic and uncommon events of daily life with a backdrop of spectacular island scenery. The aim of this unique series is as always to surprise, amuse and inform the viewer.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/951514df86583e7be3589e652aad5e4929943427.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009230000" stop="20231009233000">
    <title lang="hr">The Aviators</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Canada, 2020) The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world re-nowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents as they cover a bread range of topics designed to keep both pilots and aviation enthusiasts informed and entertained. The series covers everything from new aicraft designs to the latest GPS technologies, accident and safety awareness, airline profiles and remote fly-in getaways all over the world - The Aviators has it all!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/67f3db272722a7b3886b75ef12f5ad07dfa25d95.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009233000" stop="20231010000000">
    <title lang="hr">The Aviators</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Canada, 2020) The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world re-nowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents as they cover a bread range of topics designed to keep both pilots and aviation enthusiasts informed and entertained. The series covers everything from new aicraft designs to the latest GPS technologies, accident and safety awareness, airline profiles and remote fly-in getaways all over the world - The Aviators has it all!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/67f3db272722a7b3886b75ef12f5ad07dfa25d95.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010000000" stop="20231010003000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Hoover Dam, United States of America) Marvel at the site of America's most famous water dam. We'll learn about how the Hoover Dam was built, why it's necessary, and take a behind the scenes look at its inner workings.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010003000" stop="20231010010000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Boise, Idaho, United States of America, 2012) We've got our own private Idaho in Boise. We'll tour one of the most stunning buildings in the frontier west at the Idaho State Capitol, dance all night with the Basques at the Basque museum and cultural center, soar to new heights at the Warhawk Air Museum in Nampa, and get a shiver down our spines at the Idaho state penitentiary.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010010000" stop="20231010020000">
    <title lang="hr">St. Helena, Forgotten Island Of the Atlantic</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France, Germany, 2009) 360°GEO - Report sets foot on the isolated island of St Helena and documents what life is like in the midst of the South Atlantic.Standing solitarily far out in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean is the British Overseas Territory of St. Helena. Island do not get much more remote than this. It is situated 2,000 kilometers from the African coast and 3,000 kilometers from the South American Coast. You can see why it was chosen as a place of exile for the French emperor Napoleon.It is all but impossible to escape from St. Helena. Even today, the only connection to the outside world is by ship, given that the island has no airport. About 4,000 people or "Saints" as they refer to themselves, brave the solitude and live on the island.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/247701e0f615bca6dba56eefcd1f0f5ff2e6f321.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010020000" stop="20231010030000">
    <title lang="hr">Nomads</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Mountain Biking Nevada) Pro mountain bikers test out their tricks in the dusty terrain of the Las Vegas dessert.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/cff3b8ff9df0069c0257e0afa823a9c0c74d3703.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010030000" stop="20231010033000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Quest</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Papua New Guinea, Canada, 2020) Bill Ball breaks the rules and stereo types of travel shows as he ventures beyond the highlights. What do you do after you've lead groups to over 140 countries and all 7 continents? Welcome to Bill's bucket list on steroids... Travel Quest. This new, fast-paced series chases Bill around the globe as he seeks out anything but the mundane and ordinary—coming face-to-face with the largest crocodiles in the world, snorkeling with thousands of jellyfish, walking on the rim of an exploding volcano, feeding a group of sharks without a cage, bicycling across the Serengeti... this is not your typical travel show!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/998ffe5c40c0e9a766a6c15398e2f272aad98935.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010033000" stop="20231010040000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Quest</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(South Korea, Canada, 2020) Bill Ball breaks the rules and stereo types of travel shows as he ventures beyond the highlights. What do you do after you've lead groups to over 140 countries and all 7 continents? Welcome to Bill's bucket list on steroids... Travel Quest. This new, fast-paced series chases Bill around the globe as he seeks out anything but the mundane and ordinary—coming face-to-face with the largest crocodiles in the world, snorkeling with thousands of jellyfish, walking on the rim of an exploding volcano, feeding a group of sharks without a cage, bicycling across the Serengeti... this is not your typical travel show!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/998ffe5c40c0e9a766a6c15398e2f272aad98935.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010040000" stop="20231010050000">
    <title lang="hr">The Islanders</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Sumba, Indonesia, France, 2009) Discovering some the world's hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud of their insularity and their distinct sense of identity. A rich cocktail of history, customs, cuisine and economic resources distinguishes the island people and the nature and beaches that surround them. Our documentaries explore the varied and often little known lifestyles and peculiarities on the twenty featured islands. The approach so effectively used during our series on beaches and coastal areas, is here recreated, each program a mix of stunning visuals and interviews, which together highlight the exotic and uncommon events of daily life with a backdrop of spectacular island scenery. The aim of this unique series is as always to surprise, amuse and inform the viewer.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/951514df86583e7be3589e652aad5e4929943427.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231010050000" stop="20231010060000">
    <title lang="hr">Africa's Creative Killers</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Open Ground, South Africa, 2015) Peppered across Africa are a few iconic locations that are renowned for killing action. Arenas bathed in a history of blood, places where Africa's icons have hunted successfully for generations. Predators here develop unique and clever ways to hunt. But the circumstances aren't the driving factor in this story. Sometimes these predators look for the perfect patch of ground to kill, a small area of long grass, or a single path that leads to the perfect ambush. How do they amplify their age-old skills by using the lie of the land? The fastest mammal on the planet, Cheetah's don't only use speed to kill. They use look out points to scan for weak prey and a baby fawn as lure to get its mother to come closer. Africa's heavy weight the Lion is twice the weight and half the speed of the Cheetah. They need cover to hunt down their prey, so they stake out ambush points in Gullies, Marshland and Forest, lying in wait for their prey the wildebeest. We follow three characters through the Ndutu rainy season, starting with the arrival of the annual wildebeest migration, through to the wildebeest calves growing up and continuing their journey to the north-west. The film looks at how our characters use the environment and features of the landscape to their advantage. Reflecting on how they have learnt this from previous generations and will pass onto the next.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/52b994c635c4ee5ac0cef18fd3beb30a98920017.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <channel id="DokuTV.hr">
    <display-name>Doku TV</display-name>
    <url>https://www.a1.hr/raspored</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/62/bb/s1Xsn7k4_o.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008231400" stop="20231009000500">
    <title lang="hr">Tajne Pariza</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Do sada su stotine stručnjaka cijeli život pokušavale dešifrirati povijest Pariza. Mnoge priče i glasine ostale su nedokazane. Pariz stoljećima čuva svoje tajne. Neke pobuđuju fascinaciju, a druge pobuđuju maštu. Činjenice, sličnosti i pouzdani svjedoci, dokazuju pojavu ovih događaja. U ovom serijalu znanstvena i povijesna istraživanja otkrit će najmračnije tajne Grada svjetla. Ovdje je grad Pariz kakav još niste vidjeli.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/200fb769b066b8735dbbecde5a4e79c06895e394.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009000500" stop="20231009010000">
    <title lang="hr">Divlja godina</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska) Ovaj dokumentarni serijal od tri nastavka donosi nam jedinstveni pogled na najznačajnije predjele britanskih sela: obalu Pembrokeshire, The North York Moors i The Fenlands, svaki obilježen vlastitim karakterom i prepun tajni koje su poznate samo onima koji tamo žive. Serijal "Divlja godina" zaranja duboko ispod površine ovih triju senzacionalnih lokacija smještenih u Britaniji te istražuje povezanost okoliša, divljeg raslinja i njihovih stanovnika. Doznat ćemo kako je tijekom tisuća godina krajolik evoluirao. Koristeći spektakularnu tehniku prolaska vremena, serijal "Divlja godina" donosi nam potpuno svjež uvid u nemirni ritam britanskog seoskog života i njegovog okoliša, nudeći nam pogled kako i zašto su se ova nevjerojatna i povijesna mjesta razvila upravo na ovakav način.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7796b8f6e73c253c6992ff863cdb69d295e8420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009010000" stop="20231009015900">
    <title lang="hr">Posljednji divovi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2021) "Posljednji divovi" dokumentarni je serijal koji nas vodi u adrenalinske misije pune akcije u potrazi za hladnim planinskim titanima "Velikog sjevera" i golijatima iz džungle Amazone. Svrha je spasiti vrste kojima prijeti izumiranje, ali Cyril Chauquet i njegov tim također moraju preživjeti ekstremne opasnosti dok traže legendarne divove koji postoje desecima milijuna godina, ali koje su lov i okolišni čimbenici doveli u opasnost. Traže ogromnu, oklopljenu bijelu jesetru, prapovijesnog Pirarucua i jednog od najugroženijih slatkovodnih golijata na planetu: ogromnu Piraibu. To je ekstremna avantura ali očuvanje i ekstremni ribolov njihova su strast što je od vitalnog značaja ako žele spasiti neke ugrožene vrste.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/7ae4cb0d7445e0929775847e84e1ca75f44b9dc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009015900" stop="20231009025900">
    <title lang="hr">Prokletstvo Von Dutcha</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2021) Kako je buntovna, kultna modna marka koju su osnovali anti-junaci kasnih 90-ih, katapultirana do globalne slave i prigrljena od strane zvijezda kao što su Pamela Anderson i Tommy Lee, Jay Z, Justin Timberlake i Britney Spears, Paris Hilton i mnogi drugi? U rasponu od gotovo tri desetljeća, ovo je priča o ljudima koji stoje iza zloglasne modne marke Von Dutch, zabadanju nožea u leđa, pohlepi i krvoproliću koji su doveli do njegovog pada. Priča počinje u osamdesetima s kulturom surfanja na Venice Beachu, preko centra Los Angelesa 90-ih pa do eksplozije moderne kulture slavnih osoba ranih 2000-ih. Uz ekskluzivni pristup hrabrim i često bizarnim likovima uključenim u sagu, "Prokletstvo Von Dutcha" upoznaje nas s surferom i narko gangsterom koji je osnovao etiketu, te otkriva kako su je prihvatili hollywoodski igrači.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/0d9b88081bb7c9cfba8eb94de4eb0fad34598071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009025900" stop="20231009042900">
    <title lang="hr">Na putu do škole</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska) U mnogim dijelovima svijeta doći do škole je izazov sam po sebi, a ovaj dokumentarni film pokazuje nam s čime se mladi ljudi moraju suočiti samo do bi došli do učionice. U Keniji, putevi Jacksona i njegove sestre križat će se s opasnim slonovima. U Patagoniji, Carlito i njegova mlađa sestra jašu na konju po opasnim predjelima jer im treba 18 kilometara do škole. U Maroku, Zahria i njezini prijatelji trče preko planina kako bi došli na vrijeme na predavanje. U Indiji, Samuel je u invalidskim kolicima, a njegov mlađi brat gura kolica kroz močvarna područja. Dirljiv i inspirirajući, film "Na putu do škole" slavi snagu, posvećenost i hrabrost ovih mladih učenika u želji da se obrazuju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/425bdb3fb5206ab47e95f9b382fce42b38ddfb26.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009042900" stop="20231009060000">
    <title lang="hr">Pljačka Banksyja</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2016) Ožujak 2004. godine. Umjetnik poznat kao Banksy ilegalno je podigao sklupturu visoku 3 metra na malom trgu kraj avenije Shaftsbury u Londonu. Nazvana "Pijanac", ona je Banksyjev odgovor na Rodinovog "Mislioca", čuvenu skulpturu čovjeka zadubljenog u misli, brade oslonjene na ruku. Banksyjeva skulptura ima slično držanje, ali njegov čovjek izgleda kao netko tko se poslije veće količine alkohola srušio na stolicu, a na glavi mu stoji prometni čunj. Ubrzo, skulpturu je s postolja "oteo" AK47, umjetnik koji predvodi "podzemnu globalnu mrežu aktivista" pod nazivom "Art Kaida" čiji je cilj "uzdrmati suvremenu umjetnost"... Nakon nekoliko godina i medijskog rata između Banksyja i "Art Kaide", navodi se da je Banksy "sredio" da se skulptura uništi na bilo koji način. Međutim, nakon dosta vremena čini se da će AK47 udahnuti novi život u ovu sagu.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/da7f6b5b245c7347d3415b87c1acf0549d2d2ff3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009060000" stop="20231009070000">
    <title lang="hr">Divlja godina</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska) Ovaj dokumentarni serijal od tri nastavka donosi nam jedinstveni pogled na najznačajnije predjele britanskih sela: obalu Pembrokeshire, The North York Moors i The Fenlands, svaki obilježen vlastitim karakterom i prepun tajni koje su poznate samo onima koji tamo žive. Serijal "Divlja godina" zaranja duboko ispod površine ovih triju senzacionalnih lokacija smještenih u Britaniji te istražuje povezanost okoliša, divljeg raslinja i njihovih stanovnika. Doznat ćemo kako je tijekom tisuća godina krajolik evoluirao. Koristeći spektakularnu tehniku prolaska vremena, serijal "Divlja godina" donosi nam potpuno svjež uvid u nemirni ritam britanskog seoskog života i njegovog okoliša, nudeći nam pogled kako i zašto su se ova nevjerojatna i povijesna mjesta razvila upravo na ovakav način.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7796b8f6e73c253c6992ff863cdb69d295e8420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009070000" stop="20231009080000">
    <title lang="hr">Posljednji divovi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2021) "Posljednji divovi" dokumentarni je serijal koji nas vodi u adrenalinske misije pune akcije u potrazi za hladnim planinskim titanima "Velikog sjevera" i golijatima iz džungle Amazone. Svrha je spasiti vrste kojima prijeti izumiranje, ali Cyril Chauquet i njegov tim također moraju preživjeti ekstremne opasnosti dok traže legendarne divove koji postoje desecima milijuna godina, ali koje su lov i okolišni čimbenici doveli u opasnost. Traže ogromnu, oklopljenu bijelu jesetru, prapovijesnog Pirarucua i jednog od najugroženijih slatkovodnih golijata na planetu: ogromnu Piraibu. To je ekstremna avantura ali očuvanje i ekstremni ribolov njihova su strast što je od vitalnog značaja ako žele spasiti neke ugrožene vrste.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/7ae4cb0d7445e0929775847e84e1ca75f44b9dc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009080000" stop="20231009090000">
    <title lang="hr">Veleno: Grad nestale djece</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Italija, 2021) Krajem 1990-ih u ruralnoj Italiji otkrivena je sotonistička mreža pedofila.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/ed012f31e35ad7953567e7d306e9fb29e6d4d8dd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009090000" stop="20231009102000">
    <title lang="hr">Proročanstvo o papama</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Irski nadbiskup iz 12. stoljeća Sveti Malahija napisao je tekst pod nazivom "Proročanstvo o papama" u kojem je predvidio kraj papinstva, uništenje Rima i sudnji dan. Je li to samo još jedna apokaliptična vizija? Još jedna priča o "kraju svijeta"? Vjerojatno nije. Tijekom gotovo 900 godina "Proročanstvo o papama" pokazalo se točnim. Čini se da je tim tekstom predviđena budućnost. U ovom dokumentarnom filmu provedena je istraga u Rimu, razgovarano je s brojnim stručnjacima, dok se u Vatikanu provjeravala točnost "Proročanstva o papama" nasuprot činjenica i događaja. Čini se da puno toga potvrđuje predviđanja Svetog Malahija.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/93c24a02b6d3cf51972884532ad878a05ca453d8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009102000" stop="20231009111500">
    <title lang="hr">Najpoznatije europske željezničke stanice</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Ponovno posjetite pet najznačajnijih željezničkih postaja izgrađenih u 19. stoljeću u Europi koje su i danas značajne. Sve su to katedrale industrijskog doba s licem okrenute budućnosti. Pričaju nevjerojatne priče o arhitektonskim i mehaničkim podvizima, kada je tadašnji jet set putovao Europom uz pomoć parnih mašina. Zahvaljujući spektakularnim 4k snimkama, ova serija otkriva veličanstvenost ovih javnih zgrada i brojne tajne koje one kriju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/2dbdfa1fd06d1f6354919a0cfb27954644a5ac1e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009111500" stop="20231009121000">
    <title lang="hr">2, 3 dana u gradu</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2017) Koliko možete saznati o europskom gradu i uživati u njemu za samo dva ili tri dana? Vjerojatno puno ako želite brzinski prolaziti jedan spomenik za drugim i odlučiti jako malo spavati ili nikako.Ali što je s istraživanjem grada više od samo površnog, kada odlučite odšetati od jednog spomenika i zaviriti u neku sporednu ulicu te dobiti savjete o manje poznatim, ali vrlo tipičnim mjestima u gradu? Ovaj dokumentarni serijal odvest će vas na putovanje u kojem ćete istražiti tajne i naoko obične ulice, barove i javna mjesta koja stvaraju specifičnu atmosferu svakoga grada. Vidjet ćete, upoznati i doživjeti nova iskustva.Od bolnice za lutke u Lisabonu, kroz budimpeštanski dan i noć pa sve do međunarodnog diplomatskog središta u Bruxelles, ovaj serijal će vas odvesti na putovanje na kojem ćete se upoznati s time kako su se europski gradovi s godinama promijenili i razvili. Ako ništa drugo, ulice ovih europskih gradova će vam otkriti svoj šarm.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/589ca571bfa1a9364d16f2b2e23dd970e16409bb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009121000" stop="20231009130500">
    <title lang="hr">Sanjaj budućnost</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Medicina budućnosti, Francuska, 2016) Kako će budućnost izgledati? Kako će sadašnja otkrića i istraživanja utjecati na naše svakodnevne živote 2050. godine? Slavni znanstvenici, svjetski poznate osobe i ljudi puni strasti iz cijelog svijeta podijeliti će svoja istraživanja i svoje poglede na budući život u 20 nevjerojatnih epizoda od koji je svaka fokusirana na jednu temu: Medicina, Kuće, Hrana, Moda, Prijevoz,</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/d9bd692471de51c37907e2f8be0a15e09f45f68f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009130500" stop="20231009140000">
    <title lang="hr">Iznimni inženjerski pothvati</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Njemačka, 2017) Ova serija ukazuje na primamljivo zavodljiv proces gradnje i montaže globalnih superlativa, gdje se inovacije stapaju s nevjerojatnim mašinama. Od najvećih svjetskih brodova do hiper modernih zrakoplova. Od jedne od najvećih tvornica kamiona do oklopnih čeličnih vozila. Testosteronski dokumentarni serijal u najboljem izdanju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/32b10ab36380881648046000ea830fc8edcef9b2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009140000" stop="20231009160000">
    <title lang="hr">Pod suncem</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Letonija, Sjeverna Koreja, Češka, Rusija, Njemačka, 2015) Film razotkriva propagandne modele stvaranja sjevernokorejskog nacionalnog filmskog narativa. Poznatog ruskog redatelja, Vitalija Manskog, vlasti Demokratske Narodne Republike Koreje pozvale su da snimi film o djevojčici Zinmi i njenoj obitelji kako bi svijetu prikazao idealan život u toj zemlji. Na vlastitom setu redatelj je uključio svoju kameru i tajno snimao 'ono što nije trebao', od namještanja filmskog seta, do neprestanih promjena dijaloga, svaki put kada se partijskim komesarima neka replika učinila nedovoljno komunističkom. Na satu povijesti, na filmskom setu, u svakodnevnom životu, sve je zadano, kao i scenarij još jednog propagandnog filma, čiji se nastanak po prvi put vidi iznutra. Prvorazredni kreativni dokumentarac jednog od trenutno najboljih europskih redatelja.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/f0bcd16db6f3941e2ac658a272b1b5d84de8fd26.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009160000" stop="20231009170000">
    <title lang="hr">Brodovi i ljudi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada) Za ljude koji žive u blizini plovnih putova ili na priobalnim područjima širom svijeta, brodovi su bitan element njihova svakodnevnog života. Ova serija vodi nas na putovanje u otkrivanju brodova svih oblika i veličina, koji služe u različite svrhe. Od improviziranog čamca do većih brodova za kolektivni prijevoz, od plutajućih restorana ili škola do tradicionalnih ribarskih čamaca, svaka epizoda isprepliće dva odredišta i kombinira različite vrste brodova.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/bec2fa3e4e1f5a6602ca50eea377f7fcd06b0eef.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009170000" stop="20231009180000">
    <title lang="hr">Najčudnija mjesta istočne Europe</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada) Želite li svom sljedećem putovanju dodati neke uzbudljive atrakcije? Formula serije je jednostavna; za svaki istočnoeuropski grad koji posjeti, šarmantna i dinamična voditeljica sastavlja popis 10 najčudnijih mjesta za vidjeti i stvari koje treba učiniti. Gradovi se istražuju jedan po jedan. Intrigantna mjesta, bizarne turističke atrakcije, ostaci prošlosti i živopisni ljudi s neobičnim talentima su u trgovini, spremni vas šokirati!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/95b7c0a7628592ae421e350a0af38310d6d2e8e0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009180000" stop="20231009190000">
    <title lang="hr">Najpoznatije europske željezničke stanice</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Ponovno posjetite pet najznačajnijih željezničkih postaja izgrađenih u 19. stoljeću u Europi koje su i danas značajne. Sve su to katedrale industrijskog doba s licem okrenute budućnosti. Pričaju nevjerojatne priče o arhitektonskim i mehaničkim podvizima, kada je tadašnji jet set putovao Europom uz pomoć parnih mašina. Zahvaljujući spektakularnim 4k snimkama, ova serija otkriva veličanstvenost ovih javnih zgrada i brojne tajne koje one kriju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/2dbdfa1fd06d1f6354919a0cfb27954644a5ac1e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009190000" stop="20231009200000">
    <title lang="hr">2, 3 dana u gradu</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2017) Koliko možete saznati o europskom gradu i uživati u njemu za samo dva ili tri dana? Vjerojatno puno ako želite brzinski prolaziti jedan spomenik za drugim i odlučiti jako malo spavati ili nikako.Ali što je s istraživanjem grada više od samo površnog, kada odlučite odšetati od jednog spomenika i zaviriti u neku sporednu ulicu te dobiti savjete o manje poznatim, ali vrlo tipičnim mjestima u gradu? Ovaj dokumentarni serijal odvest će vas na putovanje u kojem ćete istražiti tajne i naoko obične ulice, barove i javna mjesta koja stvaraju specifičnu atmosferu svakoga grada. Vidjet ćete, upoznati i doživjeti nova iskustva.Od bolnice za lutke u Lisabonu, kroz budimpeštanski dan i noć pa sve do međunarodnog diplomatskog središta u Bruxelles, ovaj serijal će vas odvesti na putovanje na kojem ćete se upoznati s time kako su se europski gradovi s godinama promijenili i razvili. Ako ništa drugo, ulice ovih europskih gradova će vam otkriti svoj šarm.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/589ca571bfa1a9364d16f2b2e23dd970e16409bb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009200000" stop="20231009210000">
    <title lang="hr">Ukradena remek djela</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2017) Ovo je najveći muzej na svijetu… muzej umjetnina ukradenih tijekom stoljeća i nikad ponovno otkrivenih. Ova djela progone noćne more svojih vlasnika i okupiraju dane stotinama policajaca diljem svijeta, kao i nekolicini privatnih agencija; nijedna zemlja ili muzej od značaja ne može tvrditi da je pošteđen. Prema Interpolu, krađa umjetnina je četvrta najveća kriminalna trgovina, nakon trgovine drogom, trgovine oružjem i pranja novca. Kako bi moglo biti drugačije, kada skokovita cijena umjetnina tjera vrijednost nekih slika u desetke milijuna eura? Čini se da je ovaj svijet pun misterija. Sindikati kriminala surađuju sa sitnim kriminalcima, a policiji je više stalo do povrata predmeta nego do uhićenja počinitelja.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/7446c325cf3e9e35f9f604d81c4ed7c91dd8e87f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009210000" stop="20231009220000">
    <title lang="hr">Prve dame Amerike</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Nancy Reagan, SAD, 2020) Kažu da iza svakog velikog muškarca stoji velika žena. "Prve dame Amerike", koje donose nagrađivani redatelji Kim Duke, Liz Mermin i Kat English, fascinantna je dokumentarna serija u šest dijelova a svaka epizoda istražuje život jedne od šest kultnih žena čija imena pričaju priču o novijoj povijesti SAD-a: Eleanor Roosevelt, Lady Bird Johnson, Jackie Kennedy, Nancy Reagan, Hillary Rodham Clinton i Michelle Obama. Serija istražuje kako se svaka od tih žena našla u samom srcu američke moći i kako je svaka od njih ostavila svoj trag u američkom političkom životu i društvu. Spajajući dubinske intervjue, rijetke arhivske snimke i uvjerljive rekreacije, prve dame otkrivaju ključne, često skrivene trenutke, koji su oblikovali putovanje tih žena. Svaka od tih žena pomogla je stvoriti naslijeđe svog supruga, dok su također slijedili vlastite ciljeve i oblikovale svoje jedinstvene uloge. "Prve dame Amerike" konačno stavljaju ove moćne dame na prvo mjesto.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/adab8eab458809db5cc469d32fa2ad134a870b1f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009220000" stop="20231009230000">
    <title lang="hr">Sanjaj budućnost</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Medicina budućnosti, Francuska, 2016) Kako će budućnost izgledati? Kako će sadašnja otkrića i istraživanja utjecati na naše svakodnevne živote 2050. godine? Slavni znanstvenici, svjetski poznate osobe i ljudi puni strasti iz cijelog svijeta podijeliti će svoja istraživanja i svoje poglede na budući život u 20 nevjerojatnih epizoda od koji je svaka fokusirana na jednu temu: Medicina, Kuće, Hrana, Moda, Prijevoz,</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/d9bd692471de51c37907e2f8be0a15e09f45f68f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009230000" stop="20231010000000">
    <title lang="hr">Iznimni inženjerski pothvati</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Njemačka, 2017) Ova serija ukazuje na primamljivo zavodljiv proces gradnje i montaže globalnih superlativa, gdje se inovacije stapaju s nevjerojatnim mašinama. Od najvećih svjetskih brodova do hiper modernih zrakoplova. Od jedne od najvećih tvornica kamiona do oklopnih čeličnih vozila. Testosteronski dokumentarni serijal u najboljem izdanju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/32b10ab36380881648046000ea830fc8edcef9b2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231010000000" stop="20231010010000">
    <title lang="hr">Najpoznatije europske željezničke stanice</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Ponovno posjetite pet najznačajnijih željezničkih postaja izgrađenih u 19. stoljeću u Europi koje su i danas značajne. Sve su to katedrale industrijskog doba s licem okrenute budućnosti. Pričaju nevjerojatne priče o arhitektonskim i mehaničkim podvizima, kada je tadašnji jet set putovao Europom uz pomoć parnih mašina. Zahvaljujući spektakularnim 4k snimkama, ova serija otkriva veličanstvenost ovih javnih zgrada i brojne tajne koje one kriju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/2dbdfa1fd06d1f6354919a0cfb27954644a5ac1e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231010010000" stop="20231010020000">
    <title lang="hr">2, 3 dana u gradu</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2017) Koliko možete saznati o europskom gradu i uživati u njemu za samo dva ili tri dana? Vjerojatno puno ako želite brzinski prolaziti jedan spomenik za drugim i odlučiti jako malo spavati ili nikako.Ali što je s istraživanjem grada više od samo površnog, kada odlučite odšetati od jednog spomenika i zaviriti u neku sporednu ulicu te dobiti savjete o manje poznatim, ali vrlo tipičnim mjestima u gradu? Ovaj dokumentarni serijal odvest će vas na putovanje u kojem ćete istražiti tajne i naoko obične ulice, barove i javna mjesta koja stvaraju specifičnu atmosferu svakoga grada. Vidjet ćete, upoznati i doživjeti nova iskustva.Od bolnice za lutke u Lisabonu, kroz budimpeštanski dan i noć pa sve do međunarodnog diplomatskog središta u Bruxelles, ovaj serijal će vas odvesti na putovanje na kojem ćete se upoznati s time kako su se europski gradovi s godinama promijenili i razvili. Ako ništa drugo, ulice ovih europskih gradova će vam otkriti svoj šarm.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/589ca571bfa1a9364d16f2b2e23dd970e16409bb.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231010020000" stop="20231010040000">
    <title lang="hr">Pod suncem</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Letonija, Sjeverna Koreja, Češka, Rusija, Njemačka, 2015) Film razotkriva propagandne modele stvaranja sjevernokorejskog nacionalnog filmskog narativa. Poznatog ruskog redatelja, Vitalija Manskog, vlasti Demokratske Narodne Republike Koreje pozvale su da snimi film o djevojčici Zinmi i njenoj obitelji kako bi svijetu prikazao idealan život u toj zemlji. Na vlastitom setu redatelj je uključio svoju kameru i tajno snimao 'ono što nije trebao', od namještanja filmskog seta, do neprestanih promjena dijaloga, svaki put kada se partijskim komesarima neka replika učinila nedovoljno komunističkom. Na satu povijesti, na filmskom setu, u svakodnevnom životu, sve je zadano, kao i scenarij još jednog propagandnog filma, čiji se nastanak po prvi put vidi iznutra. Prvorazredni kreativni dokumentarac jednog od trenutno najboljih europskih redatelja.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/f0bcd16db6f3941e2ac658a272b1b5d84de8fd26.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231010040000" stop="20231010050000">
    <title lang="hr">Brodovi i ljudi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada) Za ljude koji žive u blizini plovnih putova ili na priobalnim područjima širom svijeta, brodovi su bitan element njihova svakodnevnog života. Ova serija vodi nas na putovanje u otkrivanju brodova svih oblika i veličina, koji služe u različite svrhe. Od improviziranog čamca do većih brodova za kolektivni prijevoz, od plutajućih restorana ili škola do tradicionalnih ribarskih čamaca, svaka epizoda isprepliće dva odredišta i kombinira različite vrste brodova.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/bec2fa3e4e1f5a6602ca50eea377f7fcd06b0eef.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231010050000" stop="20231010060000">
    <title lang="hr">Najčudnija mjesta istočne Europe</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada) Želite li svom sljedećem putovanju dodati neke uzbudljive atrakcije? Formula serije je jednostavna; za svaki istočnoeuropski grad koji posjeti, šarmantna i dinamična voditeljica sastavlja popis 10 najčudnijih mjesta za vidjeti i stvari koje treba učiniti. Gradovi se istražuju jedan po jedan. Intrigantna mjesta, bizarne turističke atrakcije, ostaci prošlosti i živopisni ljudi s neobičnim talentima su u trgovini, spremni vas šokirati!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/95b7c0a7628592ae421e350a0af38310d6d2e8e0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <channel id="StarMovies.hr">
    <display-name>Star Movies</display-name>
    <url>https://www.a1.hr/raspored</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/35/1b/Y6eSWKO0_o.png" />
  </channel>
</tv>

