<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">

<tv source-info-name="pluto_tv_us" source-info-url="pluto.tv">
  <channel id="DocuBox.hr">
    <display-name>DocuBox</display-name>
    <url>https://www.a1.hr/raspored</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/ad/96/zqmcf5r0_o.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231007230000" stop="20231008000000">
    <title lang="hr">Past Hunters</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(The Chocolate Factory, England, 2021) Derek Acorah's The Past Hunters travel to Hull to investigate ghostly goings on inside of a former chocolate factory. The investigation turns out to be no picnic, as the ghosts haunting make direct contact with the team.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/3bbfc89dfc434680cedf07251e71c27c71331722.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008000000" stop="20231008010000">
    <title lang="hr">The Islanders</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Sainte Marie Island, Madagascar, France, 2009) Discovering some the world's hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud of their insularity and their distinct sense of identity. A rich cocktail of history, customs, cuisine and economic resources distinguishes the island people and the nature and beaches that surround them. Our documentaries explore the varied and often little known lifestyles and peculiarities on the twenty featured islands. The approach so effectively used during our series on beaches and coastal areas, is here recreated, each program a mix of stunning visuals and interviews, which together highlight the exotic and uncommon events of daily life with a backdrop of spectacular island scenery. The aim of this unique series is as always to surprise, amuse and inform the viewer.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/951514df86583e7be3589e652aad5e4929943427.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008010000" stop="20231008020000">
    <title lang="hr">Sokotra, Endangered Treasure Island</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Germany, France, 2009) Sokotra, an island</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/74ceb89c353d40b6fdfda27aae3e3d9c51dd5557.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008020000" stop="20231008030000">
    <title lang="hr">Spitsbergen Icy Island</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Germany, 2010) 360° GEO - Report attended German supplier Rupert Krapp, on his tours through the rough landscape and picturesque fjords of Spitsbergen.The Arctic autumn is short. As early as the end of September the inhabitants of Spitsbergen prepare themselves for the long dark winter. Those who can leave the island. But a small group of people stays, mostly comprised of students, scientists and logisticians: among them is Rupert Krapp.Since late 1999, he has been living in Longyearbyen, the largest settlement on the main island. From here, he delivers goods to all those requiring supplies at their solitary stations and on their scientific research vessels.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/1e146e706bd73b9ca11c187ab2297b2acad732b8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008030000" stop="20231008040000">
    <title lang="hr">French Foreign Legion Hell In the Rain</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Germany, 2010) 360° Geo - Report accompanies 2 young legionnaires during their training as jungle fighters. It is humid in the rainforest around Regina, the outpost of the French military in the South American jungle. It's not for nothing that the country is called "Guayana", "Land of water". The foreign legionnaires, who have gathered here for training to become jungle combatants, experience the meaning of this name daily. The squad is international, the training hard: transport of the wounded through the rain forest, guerilla attacks, river crossings, survival training, the self-supply of food, and time and time again, drill! The men of the 3rd infantry regiment quite often operate for days in the jungle, tracking down illegal immigrants or gold seekers.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/3f31d2194bfe94031c061befdc8cf010d315ba0e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008040000" stop="20231008043000">
    <title lang="hr">The Aviators</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Canada, 2020) The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world re-nowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents as they cover a bread range of topics designed to keep both pilots and aviation enthusiasts informed and entertained. The series covers everything from new aicraft designs to the latest GPS technologies, accident and safety awareness, airline profiles and remote fly-in getaways all over the world - The Aviators has it all!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/67f3db272722a7b3886b75ef12f5ad07dfa25d95.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008043000" stop="20231008050000">
    <title lang="hr">Show Me Where You Live</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Iran - Masuleh Life on the Rooftops, France, 2015) Show me where you live is a documentary series that aims to answer the following question: How can human beings claim ownership to a space so that they can live safely within it, function as a society, and above all be in harmony with the environment around them?

As we discover cultures and emblematic populations, we follow Philippe Simay who is at the heart of Inhabiting the World and represents its identity and originality. Philippe takes us on an epic adventure around the Human Habitat and sets the tone for the journey. As a humanist and philosopher, Philippe is a tireless surveyor of the city, and an explorer of living spaces. Determined to travel around the world, Philippe unveils how the populations that he encounters claim the space they occupy, shapes it and adjust to it.

In this series of 20 films, of 26 minutes each, the habitat will be a major showcase revealing our capacity to adapt ourselves at a time where we need to find solutions in order to address immense changes.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/2daaac87647cf66c02dbcee6c4031ade7eb1311f.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008050000" stop="20231008053000">
    <title lang="hr">Show Me Where You Live</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Louisiana - Bayous A Lost Paradise, France, 2016) Show me where you live is a documentary series that aims to answer the following question: How can human beings claim ownership to a space so that they can live safely within it, function as a society, and above all be in harmony with the environment around them?

As we discover cultures and emblematic populations, we follow Philippe Simay who is at the heart of Inhabiting the World and represents its identity and originality. Philippe takes us on an epic adventure around the Human Habitat and sets the tone for the journey. As a humanist and philosopher, Philippe is a tireless surveyor of the city, and an explorer of living spaces. Determined to travel around the world, Philippe unveils how the populations that he encounters claim the space they occupy, shapes it and adjust to it.

In this series of 20 films, of 26 minutes each, the habitat will be a major showcase revealing our capacity to adapt ourselves at a time where we need to find solutions in order to address immense changes.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/6cc230d478fe57503459f85587938051e8ded4d5.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008053000" stop="20231008060000">
    <title lang="hr">The Karen Twins: Child Soldiers of Myanmar</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(2015) When they were kids, Johnny and Luther Htoo were invincible. This is at least what believed "God's Army" soldiers, a Karen guerilla group led by the 12 years old twin brothers. Today, Johnny and Luther are 27 years old. Their past glory is long gone, and their respective lives illustrate the fate of Burmese ethnic minorities who dare confronting the central government.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/e439b9668fa2b4811d077dd8329616711119d630.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008060000" stop="20231008063000">
    <title lang="hr">Close Quarter Battle</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Bohemia, United States of America, 2012) The history of the British Empire colonial legacy in Northern Ireland is well known the world over but a there is a largely untold story of the the firefights between and close quarter battles exchanged between the provisional IRA, the British army and the elite SAS. Although the IRA often employed "terrorist" techniques within the city of london and on England's mainland not much is said of the often guerilla warfare techniques of the British Special Air Service in Northern Ireland since the beginning of this conflict. In this episode we will examine how the history of the Special Air Service affected the training of every elite force after it and how the close quarter battles in Northern Ireland in the late 1970s through to the millennium shaped both special forces and resistance methods.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7feffc49f5e30f537ccdb17974584cae10f136a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008063000" stop="20231008070000">
    <title lang="hr">Close Quarter Battle</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Bohemia, United States of America, 2012) In 1989, CIA operative Kurt Muse was imprisoned at the notorious Carcel Modelo in Panama for his role in organizing radio transmissions against dictator Manuel Noriega. That December, an elite group of the US Delta Force breached the roof of the prison, and one of the most daring close quarter battle operations in history began. From the dramatic helicopter crash and wounding of several Delta operators to the extraction of the entire team by the 5th Infantry Division, this is prime material for CQB analysis. In this episode, CQB recreates the raid, focusing on the "sub-second" reflexes of the Delta Force team from the moment they entered the prison to their extraction from the roof of the prison by an MH-6 "Little Bird" helicopter.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7feffc49f5e30f537ccdb17974584cae10f136a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008070000" stop="20231008073000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys in Africa</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Tarangire: Land Of the Elephant, Canada, 2017) This is definitely the land of the elephant. Large herds of pachyderms roam this marshy park putting on a show for whoever wants to watch. But that's not the only big boys of this park—buffalo, lion and a host of hoofed game make this a wonder to behold.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/48b88f170ca85cf21edf213acebbf8658e33c18e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008073000" stop="20231008080000">
    <title lang="hr">Wild Capture School</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(England, United States of America) A boma is created with a funnel system and students are placed in strategic areas to man the curtain rails..</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5daa8313df068323c047d0677ec9465d05453b6d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008080000" stop="20231008090000">
    <title lang="hr">Mind In Motion</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France, Canada, 2008) Our exploration will lead us into the depths of the brain and to the very sources of consciousness, for a fascinating glimpse into the process of thought. How can we decide whether a person in a coma is likely to return to consciousness? How can a person see with the tongue? Why do amputees experience phantom sensations in missing limbs? What do we have in common with the fruit fly? What are the effects of meditation on the brain? Scientific answers to these questions and others are now within our reach, thanks to stunning new research in the neurosciences. It focuses on the brain, our mental mechanisms, the connection between body and mind. Why we need to represent ourselves and others consciously in order to survive? In our quest for answers, we have met some remarkable scientists - high-ranking pioneers who are innovative yet modest. They share their discoveries and questions with us while stressing that it is vitally importance for our society to try and understand why we have conscious brains. The story of their search, across North America and Europe, will be vividly told through evocative visuals and original imagery from new brain exploration technology.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/514f58e00d148f9fe8858587c8edc790bf1900b2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008090000" stop="20231008100000">
    <title lang="hr">Fine Cocoa From Esmeralda</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Germany, France, 2012) Cacao Nacional from Ecuador is also known as "Theobroma Cacao" or "food of the gods". The pods grow in the remotest regions of the country, including in small villages along the Rio Santiago and the Rio Napo. Theobroma's distinctive flavor is valued by chocolatiers around the world. The high demand helps cocoa farmers like Lilian and Cleofe develop a new, long-term and more reliable means of subsistence. Cocoa plantations also immensely benefit the environment: cocoa trees grow in mixed species plantations and thereby protect the rainforest. They represent an alternative to palm tree plantations that are highly destructive to the local environment.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/959c0d42dcf8adec29ede104543ccaad922cdaf4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008100000" stop="20231008103000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Louisiana New Orleans - The Perfect Musical Storm, United States of America) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008103000" stop="20231008110000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Colombia - Colombia Rocks, United States of America) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008110000" stop="20231008120000">
    <title lang="hr">Coral Sea Dreaming</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(United States of America, 1999) Coral Sea Dreaming enters into the very heart of life – and death – on a coral reef. It is a story that spans 500 million years and stars some of the most exotic and wonderous marine creatures on earth. Coral is the planet's greatest natu- ral architect, and coral reefs boast the highest biodiversity of any ecosystem.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/9d5bdf558c45914687989cd04c1cb952bcb7b9e6.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008120000" stop="20231008123000">
    <title lang="hr">The Aviators</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Canada, 2020) The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world re-nowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents as they cover a bread range of topics designed to keep both pilots and aviation enthusiasts informed and entertained. The series covers everything from new aicraft designs to the latest GPS technologies, accident and safety awareness, airline profiles and remote fly-in getaways all over the world - The Aviators has it all!</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/67f3db272722a7b3886b75ef12f5ad07dfa25d95.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008123000" stop="20231008133000">
    <title lang="hr">The Cheery Cemetery Of Romania</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Germany, France, 2013) The "Cimitirul Vesel" in Sâpânta, in the North of Romania is an unusual cemetery. As unusual as its name, which translates as: "the cheerful cemetery". Around the Orthodox Church, dark blue crosses, decorated with a blaze of multi-colored pictures portray happiness. The crosses depict scenes characterizing the deceased - and and not positively in every case. Extramarital relationships, mischief, brawls, accidents, professions and preferences, strokes of fake - the carver, painter and poet of the crosses, Dumitru Pop, decides on the epitaph. Over the decades, the cemetery of Sâpânta has become the memory of the village.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/4a81b2becb67db9ffe131678fc9a7b4901398a28.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008133000" stop="20231008143000">
    <title lang="hr">WWII Documentary Films</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Above And Beyond: The Incredible Escape Of Jewish-american B-17 Pilots From Nazi-occupied Europe In WWII, United States of America, 2014) Award-winning documentary films produced to enlighten future generations about the personal stories of the WWII generations.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5fd5c62bb216bf178deb7f9826706bf611219a43.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008143000" stop="20231008150000">
    <title lang="hr">Mindworks</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Illusions of Touch, Australia) Understanding how we think and see by playing games with our brains. This factual entertainment series explores the way we see and interpret the world around us with engaging tests, activities, demonstrations and explanations. In each episode we experience visual and audio illusions, sensory puzzles and brain tricks from the worlds of art, science, nature and psychology and learn why they baffle our senses.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c39aca411ae55261e2544f1aecbfbc59650a80c0.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008150000" stop="20231008153000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys in Africa</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Safari 101: Tips For A Successful Adventure, Canada, 2017) All the essentials for going on, and having a successful safari are covered before our host gets a very special challenge—to find at least half of the "Big Twelve" on one safari drive. Four hours and six (6) very special animals—can he do it using his own rules for a successful safari?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/48b88f170ca85cf21edf213acebbf8658e33c18e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008153000" stop="20231008163000">
    <title lang="hr">Of Boats And Men</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Canada, 2018) Travelling by boat bears a priceless sense of Freedom and offers endless new vistas to all passengers. Across waterways around the world Boats are an essential tool of daily life whether they carry goods, serve as utilities or services in remote areas.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/16e86f24aca391bfafadef18c5f714bd5189e967.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008163000" stop="20231008170000">
    <title lang="hr">Show Me Where You Live</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Spain - Granada's Hidden Gardens, France, 2016) Show me where you live is a documentary series that aims to answer the following question: How can human beings claim ownership to a space so that they can live safely within it, function as a society, and above all be in harmony with the environment around them?

As we discover cultures and emblematic populations, we follow Philippe Simay who is at the heart of Inhabiting the World and represents its identity and originality. Philippe takes us on an epic adventure around the Human Habitat and sets the tone for the journey. As a humanist and philosopher, Philippe is a tireless surveyor of the city, and an explorer of living spaces. Determined to travel around the world, Philippe unveils how the populations that he encounters claim the space they occupy, shapes it and adjust to it.

In this series of 20 films, of 26 minutes each, the habitat will be a major showcase revealing our capacity to adapt ourselves at a time where we need to find solutions in order to address immense changes.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/3991c1aff6e8caeb02b30ca594725b1ad2f0e662.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008170000" stop="20231008173000">
    <title lang="hr">Show Me Where You Live</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Cuba, Havana, Vetetable Garden City, France, 2017) Show me where you live is a documentary series that aims to answer the following question: How can human beings claim ownership to a space so that they can live safely within it, function as a society, and above all be in harmony with the environment around them?

As we discover cultures and emblematic populations, we follow Philippe Simay who is at the heart of Inhabiting the World and represents its identity and originality. Philippe takes us on an epic adventure around the Human Habitat and sets the tone for the journey. As a humanist and philosopher, Philippe is a tireless surveyor of the city, and an explorer of living spaces. Determined to travel around the world, Philippe unveils how the populations that he encounters claim the space they occupy, shapes it and adjust to it.

In this series of 20 films, of 26 minutes each, the habitat will be a major showcase revealing our capacity to adapt ourselves at a time where we need to find solutions in order to address immense changes.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/28dc30516e01bd757326ae8e44263c636663cf5b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008173000" stop="20231008180000">
    <title lang="hr">Wild Capture School</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(England, United States of America) A student is prepared to carry out the darting of a massive problematic buffalo that has been terrorizing staff members close to a camp. This task must be done on foot and the student needs to practice darting from many different distances before he can proceed.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5daa8313df068323c047d0677ec9465d05453b6d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008180000" stop="20231008190000">
    <title lang="hr">Animal Doctors</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France, 2014) Explore how animals developed over time and generations their own medicine and health care strategies. How have these been passed onto early humans ? Questioning traditional boundaries between human and animal, we will travel from Central African Republic, to Tanzania, from the US to France with the leading experts in animal behaviour. Today\'s science revisits the birth of animal intelligence and culture.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c1be6916876e002b39a0a260b9920c45804dae89.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008190000" stop="20231008193000">
    <title lang="hr">Wild Ones</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Wild Australia, United States of America, Bohemia, 2014) The legendary wild dingo, the iconic kangaroos, vicious feral cats, the delightfully bizarre platypus and the unmistakably cuddly koala - all call Australia home. KOALA One of Australia's most recognizable creatures spends most of its life hidden from view in the comfort of the gum trees it calls home. DINGO Dingoes have been in Australia for thousands of years. Descended from wolves these agile canines are sleek and efficient hunters. Lithe, elegant, ferocious and highly alert these magnificent pack hunting animals are Australia's largest land carnivores. KANGAROOS Of all Australia's one hundred and forty marsupials, the kangaroos are the most iconic, their bounding strides summing up the very essence of the land. WILD CATS Australia is home to over 12 million wild house cats. These lithe, nimble felines are the only cats in Australia and have made homes for themselves in every part of the country – from rainforests to desert, to woodlands and grasslands. PLATYPUS Of all the animals that have evolved in Australia, there is one that is more intriguing, more enchanting and more unique than any other.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8c15ec21da13c41242b8229836d6429ec4f41779.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008193000" stop="20231008200000">
    <title lang="hr">Wild Ones</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(United States of America, Bohemia, 2013) Radar accurate eyes survey the land, slotted feathers adjust flight paths as falcons attack, pelicans soar, kestrels hover, owls silently fly, parrots flock, vultures swarm and eagles swoop. Which is the true Master of the Sky? PEREGRINE FALCON Master of all they survey, the dynamic raptors are magnificent birds of prey. Revered for over 2000 years as a symbol of speed and power the peregrine falcon was a favorite with Egyptian and Chinese falconers. BUDGIE When these petite brightly colored budgies take to the air above the arid lands of Australia they color the skies green and yellow. WEDGE TAILED EAGLE Some animals inspire awe and respect by their presence alone. The wedge tailed eagle, the largest bird of prey in Australia, is one such animal. PELICAN These graceful formation flying birds that soar on thermals high above ground are some of the largest and most engaging of all the water birds. SEABIRDS Of the eight and a half thousand species of birds in the world, just under 300 of them are seabirds. Ranging from those that are migratory and dispersive to those that are rarely seen away from their breeding colonies the long-winged birds that live a life of sea and air are truly free. BARN OWL Guardian of the forest, keeper of wisdom and soul behind all seeing eyes, Barn Owls evoke an eerie respect from all who encounter them. VULTURE Constantly scanning the open plains of Africa are the highly tuned eyes of the famous birds that clean up these savannas. NANKEEN KESTREL Over the open landscapes of Australia flies its smallest falcon – the long tailed, long winged, inquisitive Nankeen Kestrel.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/876365fffaa94d9736339190fe8070abee305d90.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008200000" stop="20231008210000">
    <title lang="hr">Trouble in Lemur Land</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(England, 2011) High up in the mountains of north-eastern Madagascar lives one of the world's most critically endangered primates. There are less than a thousand Silky Sifakas alive today and this area of remote rainforest, known as Marojejy–Anjanaharibe-Sud, is their only home.In the past, the rugged terrain here kept the Silkies relatively safe but things are now changing at an alarming pace. This magical place is under serious threat from illegal logging operations as international demand for highly sought-after rosewood and ebony increases. Unscrupulous logging gangs are encroaching on the Silkies' last remaining habitat."Trouble in Lemur Land" follows two men, an American primatologist and a Malagasy conservationist, on their quest to protect this rare species, at the same time providing a rare glimpse into the life of this extraordinarily beautiful and graceful animal.The film centres around the arrival of two babies in the group – a glimmer of hope in an otherwise desperate situation. Lemur reproduction rates are slow and Silkies only mate one day in the year, so it is a very special moment when primatologist Erik Patel sees the newborns for the first time. He has a permanent camp on the outskirts of their last remaining territory and we are given a rare glimpse into this intimate, close-knit group as the babies develop in the sanctuary of the forest canopy.Meanwhile, taking advantage of long-term political instability, the loggers are steadily extracting Madagascar's rosewood for export to China. Although they are well armed and highly motivated, conservationist Desire Rabary is not afraid to confront them, regardless of the risks. He heads up a network of local people who play a vital role in the survival of the forest and its lemurs. Over the past five years, he has worked hard to actively expose the loggers' illegal trail of destruction but, as this film reveals, the heart of the problem starts on his own doorstep.This 50-minute HD film brings the forest to life, with stunning images of many of its other species, including the striking helmet vanga bird, white-fronted brown lemur, red-bellied lemur, green tree frogs, panther chameleons and the elusive fossa. This treasure trove of endemic Madagascan wildlife is a timely reminder of what we stand to lose if the environmental issues so critical to their survival are not urgently addressed.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/fea74a23ceb409015e333a91d470d02b90331a0b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008210000" stop="20231008213000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys In India</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Central India: Land Of Pilgrimages, Canada, United States of America, 2017) Two of the most sacred places in India are featured in this fascinating episode. Bill first burst the myths surrounding the legendary Khajuraho and its intricately carved temples before heading to the Holy City of Varanasi. Varanasi, the Jerusalem or Mecca for Hindus with its deep connection to the Ganges River, is explored with an insider's perspective.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/1c9e8ee0ca875068a7ae4c86b19ea243172d376d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008213000" stop="20231008220000">
    <title lang="hr">Journeys in Africa</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Masai Mara: Land Of the Leopard, Canada, 2017) We elect to stay on a few extra days to try and obtain some good leopard footage. These are the most elusive of the "Big Twelve" and filming them is a major challenge. In the process of tracking leopards, we run across a newborn gazelle trying to walk for the first time. Will it succeed before the predators find it? Can we find and film a leopard up close?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/48b88f170ca85cf21edf213acebbf8658e33c18e.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008220000" stop="20231008230000">
    <title lang="hr">The Islanders</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Jeju, South Korea, France, 2009) Discovering some the world's hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud of their insularity and their distinct sense of identity. A rich cocktail of history, customs, cuisine and economic resources distinguishes the island people and the nature and beaches that surround them. Our documentaries explore the varied and often little known lifestyles and peculiarities on the twenty featured islands. The approach so effectively used during our series on beaches and coastal areas, is here recreated, each program a mix of stunning visuals and interviews, which together highlight the exotic and uncommon events of daily life with a backdrop of spectacular island scenery. The aim of this unique series is as always to surprise, amuse and inform the viewer.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/951514df86583e7be3589e652aad5e4929943427.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231008230000" stop="20231009000000">
    <title lang="hr">Lagerfield - The Kaiser Of Fashion</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(United States of America, 2019) A biography of the controversial fashion savant, creator of extraordinary fashion show sets, renowned photographer, and author of breathtaking books. Lagerfeld is the quintessential renaissance man.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/66f97ad561b130553c109e34b979f12b57e0b69d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009000000" stop="20231009010000">
    <title lang="hr">The Species Return</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France) With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. It is up to us to understand that energy. This series examine various species that have made a comeback among our European landscapes, providing "close to home" examples. We are now fully aware that every coming year brings about a reduction in our planet's biodiversity. One in eight species of bird, one in four mammals, and one in three amphibians are threatened with extinction by the end of the 21st century. But this is not necessarily a lost cause. With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. Even in our immediate surroundings, in a highly urbanised and industrialised Europe, some species of wildlife, which had been virtually wiped out, are reappearing. There are various reasons for this wildlife.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/215fcbf6379347c2cd660fdfc35458c949f49ee2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009010000" stop="20231009013000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Japan-tohoku: Japan Rising, United States of America) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009013000" stop="20231009020000">
    <title lang="hr">Music Voyager</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Japan-Tokyo - Electric City, United States of America) Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting sounds of the planet. The host is Jacob Edgar, an explorer who does not search for lost cities or ancient ruins. He's on the quest for a different kind of treasure…music. As an ethnomusicologist and world music record producer, Edgar travels the globe hunting for the best songs the world has to offer, and he suffers through some of the worst…so you don't have to. Along the way, he's rewarded with a backstage pass to concert halls, street festivals, recording studios and rehearsal rooms. With local musicians as his guide, Edgar tastes exotic and occasionally ghastly food, visits off-the-beaten path attractions and parties the night away to amazing concerts at hidden venues that only the locals know. Join music voyager for unexpected adventures and surprising discoveries that unveil the magic, mystery and music of far off lands.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c204bb39360dac0c28e0d62b48c61f4cdcb6ee1b.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009020000" stop="20231009023000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(San Diego, United States of America, 2012) Get your sun tan lotion on, because we're headed to the land of perfect weather and sunsets. We'll sample a fish taco, climb the 100's of steps of the California Tower, stand on the flight deck of the USS Midway, as well as, revisit San Diego's founding on the San Salvador at the San Diego Maritime museum.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009023000" stop="20231009030000">
    <title lang="hr">Travel Thru History</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Montreal, United States of America, 2012) Bonjour! We're headed to Quebec Province on today's show. First, we get blown away by the thunderous pipes at Montreal's Notre Dame Basilica. After that, we go underneath the city at the Pointe a Calliere archaeology museum. Next, we'll learn about the native ecosystem at the gigantic, indoor, BioDome. Lastly, we'll learn about the 1967 Montreal Expo at the structures that are still visited today.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/8f1927627793211ed201b174dacb22f82f6ebbb2.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009030000" stop="20231009033000">
    <title lang="hr">Everyday Elements</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Carbon, Gold, Neon, Zirconium, Antimony, Italy) A series that puts chemistry in our everyday experience by showing the living connection we have with the chemicals and elements that make up our world. The matter that built skies and seas, the atoms that make up you and me, the chemistry around us that forms the things we touch, smell and see. This series shows us what the objects in our universe and in our homes are made from and why the particles around us behave as they do. Everything around us is built from Everyday Elements.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/00e11946a460c8e64f2ef2f35fd134c7f2175891.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009033000" stop="20231009040000">
    <title lang="hr">Everyday Elements</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Silver, Hydrogen, Phosphorus, Germanium, Sulphur, Italy) A series that puts chemistry in our everyday experience by showing the living connection we have with the chemicals and elements that make up our world. The matter that built skies and seas, the atoms that make up you and me, the chemistry around us that forms the things we touch, smell and see. This series shows us what the objects in our universe and in our homes are made from and why the particles around us behave as they do. Everything around us is built from Everyday Elements.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/00e11946a460c8e64f2ef2f35fd134c7f2175891.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009040000" stop="20231009050000">
    <title lang="hr">Depleted Uranium</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(France, 2012) More than 50 countries now possess weapons based on depleted uranium (DU). Experimentation has been rife, and the consequences for civilians and the military alike have been dramatic. This investigation compares and contrasts the arguments of those who defend and attack a technology that is highly toxic. For 20 years, scientists, doctors, veterans and activists have denounced the use of DU. Against them are the arms industry lobbyists and nuclear authorities who continue to minimise the risks. Through archive documents, interviews and in situ investigations, accompanied by key witnesses (victims, experts...) we aim to present a clearer picture of the issues and stakes linked to the use of DU. Quick-paced, with a sense of urgency, the film underlines the essential background and conflicting viewpoints, enabling viewers to make up their own minds about a subject that concerns us all.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/37a92a4fdd8d0746a3a5ed29b497e07b1effd417.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009050000" stop="20231009053000">
    <title lang="hr">Close Quarter Battle</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Snipers &amp; Scout, Bohemia, United States of America, 2012) Joint Task Force Two (JTF 2) is the elite Canadian Forces Special Operations unit responsible for a broad range of missions, including counter-terrorism and armed assistance to other government departments. Highly secretive, JTF 2 and its predecessor, the Canadian Airborne Regiment, have been deployed in hotspots around the world from Haiti to Bosnia. This episode focuses on the legendary JTF sniper teams and their use in Afghanistan alongside the British SAS and the US Delta Force at "the sharp end of the spear." A book written by an ex-JTF member explains how, in 2006, both the Pentagon and the British Foreign Oﬃ ce noted the instrumental role that JTF 2 played in the rescue of the British and Canadian Christian Peacemaker Team held hostage in Iraq. Unique in look, the FN P90 personal defense weapon, used by JTF 2 soldiers and special police around the world, will be highlighted in this program.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7feffc49f5e30f537ccdb17974584cae10f136a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DocuBox.hr" start="20231009053000" stop="20231009060000">
    <title lang="hr">Close Quarter Battle</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(S.W.A.T., Bohemia, United States of America, 2012) In 1968, a new form of military policing was being developed in a rural area north of Los Angeles. The Los Angeles Police Department sent an observer to this unit, and he, in turn, took this knowledge back to the LAPD. This contributed to the development of the department's first Special Weapons and Tactics (S.W.A.T.) team. This CQB episode takes an historical journey to examine how this incident affected and changed police tactics around the world. Using CQB's trademark "sub-second" analysis, the program also looks at how police S.W.A.T. teams train, plan and equip themselves for the challenges of urban combat. The dramatization of a 1980s S.W.A.T. siege of a gang safe-house demonstrates the complicated challenge of protecting innocent people who might be caught in the line of fire, as well as the specifics of the squad's training regimen, how they communicated, and the special equipment they used.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7feffc49f5e30f537ccdb17974584cae10f136a.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <channel id="DokuTV.hr">
    <display-name>Doku TV</display-name>
    <url>https://www.a1.hr/raspored</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/62/bb/s1Xsn7k4_o.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231007230000" stop="20231008000000">
    <title lang="hr">Stonehenge: Skrivena istina</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska) Misterije Stonehengea, jedne od najpoznatijih drevnih znamenitosti na Zemlji, već stoljećima fasciniraju svijet. U ovom posve novom dokumentarcu povijest se ispisuje iznova dok pratimo tim stručnjaka koji koriste vrhunsku tehnologiju kako bi istražili golemi, novootkriveni prsten u samom srcu ovog svetog mjesta. U zadivljujućem novom otkriću vidimo kako arheolozi prvi put koriste optički stimuliranu luminiscenciju za utvrđivanje datuma izgradnje velikog prstena, dugo skrivenog u tamnoj zemlji. Saznajemo da, izgrađena prije otprilike 4340 godina, ova divovska građevina predstavlja posljednji, krunski dodatak krajoliku Stonehengea; posljednji mega-spomenik neolitika i simbol kraja jedne ere. Uz današnju najnapredniju tehnologiju laserskog mapiranja, istraživanja dronovima, inovativnu laboratorijsku analizu i CGI mapiranje, ova izvanredna nova otkrića konačno nam pomažu da se približimo otkrivanju tajni Stonehengea.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/9808187f6e7c00ee3cb75afc1bd837106dfbfece.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008000000" stop="20231008010000">
    <title lang="hr">Znanost protiv terorizma</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2019) Tijekom posljednje dvije godine istraživači u matematici, virtualnoj stvarnosti, kemiji, fizici, informatici ili inženjerstvu pomicali su granice svojih područja. Njihov je cilj razviti točniju analizu podataka i pokrenuti učinkovitije odgovore na međunarodni terorizam. Blisko surađujući s donositeljima javnih odluka i sigurnosnim akterima, razvijali su i dizajnirali niz najsuvremenijih tehnologija kako bi spasili živote. Postoje sofisticirani algoritmi za praćenje sumnjivih pojedinaca, olfaktorni DNK, špijuniranje mini-dronova, novih tkanina ili materijala... Ovo nije znanstvena fantastika. Serija ulazi u tajne laboratorije onih koji svoje vještine stavljaju u službu zaštite svijeta.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b32533c18f65ec3155e2092c86ebb85c55c5b96d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008010000" stop="20231008020000">
    <title lang="hr">Medvjeđe supermoći</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) U predjelu švedskih tajgi (zimzelenih šuma četinjača), u blizini grada Tackåsena, grupa doktora i znanstvenika prati tragove smeđih medvjeda, slijedeći ih do njihovog brloga. Oni se, naime, nalaze na nevjerojatnoj misiji: uzeti uzorke krvi i tkiva te obaviti cijeli niz medicinskih testova nad medvjedima koji spavaju zimski san. Njihov cilj? Razumjeti nevjerojatnu otpornost koju ove životinje posjeduju, a sve kako bi pronašli lijek za učestale zdravstvene probleme kod ljudi.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/c5ae4034f8b2651e842ea4069e7b40cf97fdb9c7.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008020000" stop="20231008030000">
    <title lang="hr">Belsen: Neispričana priča</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska, 2020) Ovaj uvjerljiv, duboko važan film, dokumentira priče preživjelih u jednom od najozloglašenijih koncentracijskih logora Drugog svjetskog rata. Sedamdeset i pet godina nakon oslobođenja, posljednji preživjeli - djeca tijekom interniranja - vraćaju se na mjesto logora i dijele svoja ključna sjećanja. Više od pedeset i dvije tisuće ljudi stradalo je kod Bergena Belsona, uključujući Anne Frank i njezinu sestru Margot. Poznat po svojim užasnim uvjetima, malo se ljudi uspjelo izvući živo, a oni koji su uspjeli uvijek su nosili svoja sjećanja sa sobom. Ovaj snažan film dokumentira njihova razmišljanja, zajedno s onima koji su ih oslobodili, potresnom osjetljivošću, čineći ga uvjerljivim i neophodnim za gledanje.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/f3d72bcf2393847d7cb807f187757a8bfb0ce5ec.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008030000" stop="20231008040000">
    <title lang="hr">Spremni za Mars</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Utrka za putovanje Crvenim planetom je započela! Ipak, dostizanje Marsa predstavlja izazov koji nadilazi bilo što prije. Dok je povratno putovanje na Mjesec misije Apollo XI trajalo osam dana, trebat će 3 godine da se stigne do Marsa i vrati se. Nacionalne svemirske agencije, znanstvenici i privatna poduzeća natječu se u pronalaženju pionirskih načina da budu dio ove avanture i ulažu ogromne svote novca kako bi postigli svoj cilj. Ovog će se puta susresti s vodećim svjetskim znanstvenicima, inženjerima i inovatorima koji rade diljem svijeta kako bi omogućili putovanje. Razmatra se svaki pojedinačni aspekt ljudskog opstanka i traže se rješenja. Dođite i saznajte više o tome što će se spakirati za Mars! Koja je raketa sposobna prijeći tako veliku udaljenost? Kako se ljudsko tijelo može osposobiti za prilagođavanje životu u okruženju bez gravitacije? Kako će se proizvoditi hrana i voda? U kojim će se naseljima prvi ljudi naseliti na Marsu? I, što je još važnije, kako će se netko moći mentalno i fizički nositi s iskušenjem i ograničenim prostorom?</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/cedd9d7588915064d68e7c10c2098f1b9b5b80ca.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008040000" stop="20231008050000">
    <title lang="hr">Izgradnja Pariza 1900. godine</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2021) U Parizu, 15. travnja 1900. godine, počinje najveća proslava ikada održana na svijetu. Svjetski sajam potpuno transformira grad: egzotični luksuzni hoteli koji krase obale Seine, kolosalni spomenici koji se pojavljuju na svakom uglu ulice i šetnice samo su neke od značajki koje očaravaju publiku. Više od 50 milijuna posjetitelja otkriva ovaj novi Pariz, uzvišen dolaskom struje. Kako su inženjeri uspjeli postaviti električni, podzemni sustav podzemne željeznice u manje od dvije godine? Zašto su sagradili Grand Palais na stubovima? Koje su tehnološke izazove svladali kako bi osmislili Gare d'Orsay u srcu Pariza? Gigantske zgrade podignute su u rekordnom roku. Stotinu i dvadeset godina kasnije neki su i danas među najljepšim spomenicima glavnog grada.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/5290bc0dadc6819efd89928c58d81080cc74bb2d.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008050000" stop="20231008060000">
    <title lang="hr">Svjetski chefovi u Francuskoj</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska) Upoznajte se s novom generacijom talentiranih kuhara koji utjelovljuju nova lica Francuske i internacionalne kuhinje. Porijeklom iz Brazila, Argentine, Japana, Južne Afrike, Libanona,</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/21f7e00240b441998c2a50e23b0c5f3d07900176.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008060000" stop="20231008070000">
    <title lang="hr">Posljednji divovi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2021) "Posljednji divovi" dokumentarni je serijal koji nas vodi u adrenalinske misije pune akcije u potrazi za hladnim planinskim titanima "Velikog sjevera" i golijatima iz džungle Amazone. Svrha je spasiti vrste kojima prijeti izumiranje, ali Cyril Chauquet i njegov tim također moraju preživjeti ekstremne opasnosti dok traže legendarne divove koji postoje desecima milijuna godina, ali koje su lov i okolišni čimbenici doveli u opasnost. Traže ogromnu, oklopljenu bijelu jesetru, prapovijesnog Pirarucua i jednog od najugroženijih slatkovodnih golijata na planetu: ogromnu Piraibu. To je ekstremna avantura ali očuvanje i ekstremni ribolov njihova su strast što je od vitalnog značaja ako žele spasiti neke ugrožene vrste.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/047b3fe9a92d3afe3079d83530762f993044aa98.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008070000" stop="20231008082500">
    <title lang="hr">Oscar Peterson: Crno i bijelo</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2020) "Oscar Peterson: Crno i bijelo" dugometražni je doku-koncert koji priča priču o jazz legendi Oscaru Petersonu. Predstavljajući Petersonovu glazbu u sadašnjem i povijesnom kontekstu, ovaj stilski film ispituje auru njegove osobnosti i njegova iskustva s turneja i rada s najsjajnijim zvijezdama ere, od Elle Fitzgerald preko Counta Basieja i Louisa Armstronga do Nat King Colea. Kroz arhivske snimke, intervjue i nastupe, film također istražuje rasizam koji je mučio Oscarov život unatoč njegovoj slavi i uspjehu, te rasne implikacije njegovog javnog imidža i uspona do zvijezde. Ovo je priča o istinskoj glazbenoj legendi; beskompromisni glazbenik s osjećajem rasnog ponosa koji je tijekom cijele svoje karijere pokazivao predanost mentorstvu nove generacije umjetnika, a predstavit će ekskluzivne doprinose ljudi čije je živote dotaknuo i koje nastavlja inspirirati, uključujući Herbieja Hancocka, Quincyja Jonesa, Billyja Joela, Ramseya Lewisa, Kelly Peterson i druge.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/86a38f52d2bc6a0627b33dad785a6597bc87b6cd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008082500" stop="20231008100000">
    <title lang="hr">Tražeći Gillesa Carona</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2019) Gilles Caron bio je na vrhuncu svoje karijere kao briljantni fotoreporter kada je nestao u Kambodži 1970. Imao je samo 30 godina. Kroz njegove kultne fotografije ovaj film, konstruiran kao istraga, ima za cilj vratiti fotografovu prisutnost, ispričati priču o njegovom pogledu i tome kako je u tako kratkom vremenu uspio pokriti svaki visoki sukob svog vremena.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/2e81a145b088b4151ee4d70ff51a05c4c6f8086c.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008100000" stop="20231008110000">
    <title lang="hr">Divlja godina</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska) Ovaj dokumentarni serijal od tri nastavka donosi nam jedinstveni pogled na najznačajnije predjele britanskih sela: obalu Pembrokeshire, The North York Moors i The Fenlands, svaki obilježen vlastitim karakterom i prepun tajni koje su poznate samo onima koji tamo žive. Serijal "Divlja godina" zaranja duboko ispod površine ovih triju senzacionalnih lokacija smještenih u Britaniji te istražuje povezanost okoliša, divljeg raslinja i njihovih stanovnika. Doznat ćemo kako je tijekom tisuća godina krajolik evoluirao. Koristeći spektakularnu tehniku prolaska vremena, serijal "Divlja godina" donosi nam potpuno svjež uvid u nemirni ritam britanskog seoskog života i njegovog okoliša, nudeći nam pogled kako i zašto su se ova nevjerojatna i povijesna mjesta razvila upravo na ovakav način.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7796b8f6e73c253c6992ff863cdb69d295e8420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008110000" stop="20231008120000">
    <title lang="hr">Posljednji divovi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2021) "Posljednji divovi" dokumentarni je serijal koji nas vodi u adrenalinske misije pune akcije u potrazi za hladnim planinskim titanima "Velikog sjevera" i golijatima iz džungle Amazone. Svrha je spasiti vrste kojima prijeti izumiranje, ali Cyril Chauquet i njegov tim također moraju preživjeti ekstremne opasnosti dok traže legendarne divove koji postoje desecima milijuna godina, ali koje su lov i okolišni čimbenici doveli u opasnost. Traže ogromnu, oklopljenu bijelu jesetru, prapovijesnog Pirarucua i jednog od najugroženijih slatkovodnih golijata na planetu: ogromnu Piraibu. To je ekstremna avantura ali očuvanje i ekstremni ribolov njihova su strast što je od vitalnog značaja ako žele spasiti neke ugrožene vrste.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/7ae4cb0d7445e0929775847e84e1ca75f44b9dc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008120000" stop="20231008130000">
    <title lang="hr">Alhambra: Utvrda Andaluzije</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/044cea9726d5fbc6b751dc303981d761be620877.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008130000" stop="20231008140000">
    <title lang="hr">Tajne Pariza</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Do sada su stotine stručnjaka cijeli život pokušavale dešifrirati povijest Pariza. Mnoge priče i glasine ostale su nedokazane. Pariz stoljećima čuva svoje tajne. Neke pobuđuju fascinaciju, a druge pobuđuju maštu. Činjenice, sličnosti i pouzdani svjedoci, dokazuju pojavu ovih događaja. U ovom serijalu znanstvena i povijesna istraživanja otkrit će najmračnije tajne Grada svjetla. Ovdje je grad Pariz kakav još niste vidjeli.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/200fb769b066b8735dbbecde5a4e79c06895e394.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008140000" stop="20231008150000">
    <title lang="hr">Prokletstvo Von Dutcha</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2021) Kako je buntovna, kultna modna marka koju su osnovali anti-junaci kasnih 90-ih, katapultirana do globalne slave i prigrljena od strane zvijezda kao što su Pamela Anderson i Tommy Lee, Jay Z, Justin Timberlake i Britney Spears, Paris Hilton i mnogi drugi? U rasponu od gotovo tri desetljeća, ovo je priča o ljudima koji stoje iza zloglasne modne marke Von Dutch, zabadanju nožea u leđa, pohlepi i krvoproliću koji su doveli do njegovog pada. Priča počinje u osamdesetima s kulturom surfanja na Venice Beachu, preko centra Los Angelesa 90-ih pa do eksplozije moderne kulture slavnih osoba ranih 2000-ih. Uz ekskluzivni pristup hrabrim i često bizarnim likovima uključenim u sagu, "Prokletstvo Von Dutcha" upoznaje nas s surferom i narko gangsterom koji je osnovao etiketu, te otkriva kako su je prihvatili hollywoodski igrači.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/0d9b88081bb7c9cfba8eb94de4eb0fad34598071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008150000" stop="20231008163000">
    <title lang="hr">Na putu do škole</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska) U mnogim dijelovima svijeta doći do škole je izazov sam po sebi, a ovaj dokumentarni film pokazuje nam s čime se mladi ljudi moraju suočiti samo do bi došli do učionice. U Keniji, putevi Jacksona i njegove sestre križat će se s opasnim slonovima. U Patagoniji, Carlito i njegova mlađa sestra jašu na konju po opasnim predjelima jer im treba 18 kilometara do škole. U Maroku, Zahria i njezini prijatelji trče preko planina kako bi došli na vrijeme na predavanje. U Indiji, Samuel je u invalidskim kolicima, a njegov mlađi brat gura kolica kroz močvarna područja. Dirljiv i inspirirajući, film "Na putu do škole" slavi snagu, posvećenost i hrabrost ovih mladih učenika u želji da se obrazuju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/425bdb3fb5206ab47e95f9b382fce42b38ddfb26.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008163000" stop="20231008175900">
    <title lang="hr">Pljačka Banksyja</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2016) Ožujak 2004. godine. Umjetnik poznat kao Banksy ilegalno je podigao sklupturu visoku 3 metra na malom trgu kraj avenije Shaftsbury u Londonu. Nazvana "Pijanac", ona je Banksyjev odgovor na Rodinovog "Mislioca", čuvenu skulpturu čovjeka zadubljenog u misli, brade oslonjene na ruku. Banksyjeva skulptura ima slično držanje, ali njegov čovjek izgleda kao netko tko se poslije veće količine alkohola srušio na stolicu, a na glavi mu stoji prometni čunj. Ubrzo, skulpturu je s postolja "oteo" AK47, umjetnik koji predvodi "podzemnu globalnu mrežu aktivista" pod nazivom "Art Kaida" čiji je cilj "uzdrmati suvremenu umjetnost"... Nakon nekoliko godina i medijskog rata između Banksyja i "Art Kaide", navodi se da je Banksy "sredio" da se skulptura uništi na bilo koji način. Međutim, nakon dosta vremena čini se da će AK47 udahnuti novi život u ovu sagu.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/da7f6b5b245c7347d3415b87c1acf0549d2d2ff3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008175900" stop="20231008190000">
    <title lang="hr">Divlja godina</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska) Ovaj dokumentarni serijal od tri nastavka donosi nam jedinstveni pogled na najznačajnije predjele britanskih sela: obalu Pembrokeshire, The North York Moors i The Fenlands, svaki obilježen vlastitim karakterom i prepun tajni koje su poznate samo onima koji tamo žive. Serijal "Divlja godina" zaranja duboko ispod površine ovih triju senzacionalnih lokacija smještenih u Britaniji te istražuje povezanost okoliša, divljeg raslinja i njihovih stanovnika. Doznat ćemo kako je tijekom tisuća godina krajolik evoluirao. Koristeći spektakularnu tehniku prolaska vremena, serijal "Divlja godina" donosi nam potpuno svjež uvid u nemirni ritam britanskog seoskog života i njegovog okoliša, nudeći nam pogled kako i zašto su se ova nevjerojatna i povijesna mjesta razvila upravo na ovakav način.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7796b8f6e73c253c6992ff863cdb69d295e8420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008190000" stop="20231008195900">
    <title lang="hr">Posljednji divovi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2021) "Posljednji divovi" dokumentarni je serijal koji nas vodi u adrenalinske misije pune akcije u potrazi za hladnim planinskim titanima "Velikog sjevera" i golijatima iz džungle Amazone. Svrha je spasiti vrste kojima prijeti izumiranje, ali Cyril Chauquet i njegov tim također moraju preživjeti ekstremne opasnosti dok traže legendarne divove koji postoje desecima milijuna godina, ali koje su lov i okolišni čimbenici doveli u opasnost. Traže ogromnu, oklopljenu bijelu jesetru, prapovijesnog Pirarucua i jednog od najugroženijih slatkovodnih golijata na planetu: ogromnu Piraibu. To je ekstremna avantura ali očuvanje i ekstremni ribolov njihova su strast što je od vitalnog značaja ako žele spasiti neke ugrožene vrste.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/7ae4cb0d7445e0929775847e84e1ca75f44b9dc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008195900" stop="20231008205900">
    <title lang="hr">Veleno: Grad nestale djece</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Italija, 2021) Krajem 1990-ih u ruralnoj Italiji otkrivena je sotonistička mreža pedofila.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/ed012f31e35ad7953567e7d306e9fb29e6d4d8dd.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008205900" stop="20231008222000">
    <title lang="hr">Proročanstvo o papama</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Irski nadbiskup iz 12. stoljeća Sveti Malahija napisao je tekst pod nazivom "Proročanstvo o papama" u kojem je predvidio kraj papinstva, uništenje Rima i sudnji dan. Je li to samo još jedna apokaliptična vizija? Još jedna priča o "kraju svijeta"? Vjerojatno nije. Tijekom gotovo 900 godina "Proročanstvo o papama" pokazalo se točnim. Čini se da je tim tekstom predviđena budućnost. U ovom dokumentarnom filmu provedena je istraga u Rimu, razgovarano je s brojnim stručnjacima, dok se u Vatikanu provjeravala točnost "Proročanstva o papama" nasuprot činjenica i događaja. Čini se da puno toga potvrđuje predviđanja Svetog Malahija.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/93c24a02b6d3cf51972884532ad878a05ca453d8.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008222000" stop="20231008231400">
    <title lang="hr">Alhambra: Utvrda Andaluzije</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/044cea9726d5fbc6b751dc303981d761be620877.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231008231400" stop="20231009000500">
    <title lang="hr">Tajne Pariza</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska, 2018) Do sada su stotine stručnjaka cijeli život pokušavale dešifrirati povijest Pariza. Mnoge priče i glasine ostale su nedokazane. Pariz stoljećima čuva svoje tajne. Neke pobuđuju fascinaciju, a druge pobuđuju maštu. Činjenice, sličnosti i pouzdani svjedoci, dokazuju pojavu ovih događaja. U ovom serijalu znanstvena i povijesna istraživanja otkrit će najmračnije tajne Grada svjetla. Ovdje je grad Pariz kakav još niste vidjeli.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/200fb769b066b8735dbbecde5a4e79c06895e394.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009000500" stop="20231009010000">
    <title lang="hr">Divlja godina</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Engleska) Ovaj dokumentarni serijal od tri nastavka donosi nam jedinstveni pogled na najznačajnije predjele britanskih sela: obalu Pembrokeshire, The North York Moors i The Fenlands, svaki obilježen vlastitim karakterom i prepun tajni koje su poznate samo onima koji tamo žive. Serijal "Divlja godina" zaranja duboko ispod površine ovih triju senzacionalnih lokacija smještenih u Britaniji te istražuje povezanost okoliša, divljeg raslinja i njihovih stanovnika. Doznat ćemo kako je tijekom tisuća godina krajolik evoluirao. Koristeći spektakularnu tehniku prolaska vremena, serijal "Divlja godina" donosi nam potpuno svjež uvid u nemirni ritam britanskog seoskog života i njegovog okoliša, nudeći nam pogled kako i zašto su se ova nevjerojatna i povijesna mjesta razvila upravo na ovakav način.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/b7796b8f6e73c253c6992ff863cdb69d295e8420.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009010000" stop="20231009015900">
    <title lang="hr">Posljednji divovi</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Kanada, 2021) "Posljednji divovi" dokumentarni je serijal koji nas vodi u adrenalinske misije pune akcije u potrazi za hladnim planinskim titanima "Velikog sjevera" i golijatima iz džungle Amazone. Svrha je spasiti vrste kojima prijeti izumiranje, ali Cyril Chauquet i njegov tim također moraju preživjeti ekstremne opasnosti dok traže legendarne divove koji postoje desecima milijuna godina, ali koje su lov i okolišni čimbenici doveli u opasnost. Traže ogromnu, oklopljenu bijelu jesetru, prapovijesnog Pirarucua i jednog od najugroženijih slatkovodnih golijata na planetu: ogromnu Piraibu. To je ekstremna avantura ali očuvanje i ekstremni ribolov njihova su strast što je od vitalnog značaja ako žele spasiti neke ugrožene vrste.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/7ae4cb0d7445e0929775847e84e1ca75f44b9dc4.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009015900" stop="20231009025900">
    <title lang="hr">Prokletstvo Von Dutcha</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2021) Kako je buntovna, kultna modna marka koju su osnovali anti-junaci kasnih 90-ih, katapultirana do globalne slave i prigrljena od strane zvijezda kao što su Pamela Anderson i Tommy Lee, Jay Z, Justin Timberlake i Britney Spears, Paris Hilton i mnogi drugi? U rasponu od gotovo tri desetljeća, ovo je priča o ljudima koji stoje iza zloglasne modne marke Von Dutch, zabadanju nožea u leđa, pohlepi i krvoproliću koji su doveli do njegovog pada. Priča počinje u osamdesetima s kulturom surfanja na Venice Beachu, preko centra Los Angelesa 90-ih pa do eksplozije moderne kulture slavnih osoba ranih 2000-ih. Uz ekskluzivni pristup hrabrim i često bizarnim likovima uključenim u sagu, "Prokletstvo Von Dutcha" upoznaje nas s surferom i narko gangsterom koji je osnovao etiketu, te otkriva kako su je prihvatili hollywoodski igrači.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/0d9b88081bb7c9cfba8eb94de4eb0fad34598071.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009025900" stop="20231009042900">
    <title lang="hr">Na putu do škole</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(Francuska) U mnogim dijelovima svijeta doći do škole je izazov sam po sebi, a ovaj dokumentarni film pokazuje nam s čime se mladi ljudi moraju suočiti samo do bi došli do učionice. U Keniji, putevi Jacksona i njegove sestre križat će se s opasnim slonovima. U Patagoniji, Carlito i njegova mlađa sestra jašu na konju po opasnim predjelima jer im treba 18 kilometara do škole. U Maroku, Zahria i njezini prijatelji trče preko planina kako bi došli na vrijeme na predavanje. U Indiji, Samuel je u invalidskim kolicima, a njegov mlađi brat gura kolica kroz močvarna područja. Dirljiv i inspirirajući, film "Na putu do škole" slavi snagu, posvećenost i hrabrost ovih mladih učenika u želji da se obrazuju.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/425bdb3fb5206ab47e95f9b382fce42b38ddfb26.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="DokuTV.hr" start="20231009042900" stop="20231009060000">
    <title lang="hr">Pljačka Banksyja</title>
    <desc lang="hr">(SAD, 2016) Ožujak 2004. godine. Umjetnik poznat kao Banksy ilegalno je podigao sklupturu visoku 3 metra na malom trgu kraj avenije Shaftsbury u Londonu. Nazvana "Pijanac", ona je Banksyjev odgovor na Rodinovog "Mislioca", čuvenu skulpturu čovjeka zadubljenog u misli, brade oslonjene na ruku. Banksyjeva skulptura ima slično držanje, ali njegov čovjek izgleda kao netko tko se poslije veće količine alkohola srušio na stolicu, a na glavi mu stoji prometni čunj. Ubrzo, skulpturu je s postolja "oteo" AK47, umjetnik koji predvodi "podzemnu globalnu mrežu aktivista" pod nazivom "Art Kaida" čiji je cilj "uzdrmati suvremenu umjetnost"... Nakon nekoliko godina i medijskog rata između Banksyja i "Art Kaide", navodi se da je Banksy "sredio" da se skulptura uništi na bilo koji način. Međutim, nakon dosta vremena čini se da će AK47 udahnuti novi život u ovu sagu.</desc>
    <category lang="hr">Documentary</category>
    <icon src="https://ssc.a1.hr/ITV/pictures/da7f6b5b245c7347d3415b87c1acf0549d2d2ff3.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <channel id="StarMovies.hr">
    <display-name>Star Movies</display-name>
    <url>https://www.a1.hr/raspored</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/35/1b/Y6eSWKO0_o.png" />
  </channel>
</tv>

