<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">

<tv source-info-name="ESA Web TV One guide by TV" source-info-url="https://www.esa.int/ESA_Multimedia/ESA_Web_TV">
  <channel id="ESAWebTVOne.int">
    <display-name>ESA Web TV One</display-name>
    <url>https://www.esa.int/ESA_Multimedia/ESA_Web_TV</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410010000 +0200" stop="20240410080000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Wake up in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Start your day with spectacular imagery from space. (Duration 07:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410080000 +0200" stop="20240410083000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space health</title>
    <desc lang="en">Living in space does impact the health of astronauts and they undergo rigorous training exercises to keep fit in zero gravity. But how does space research help improve the health of populations on Earth? In this programme, find out how research carried out on the ISS advances our medical knowledge on ageing, hibernation, muscles or even blood vessels. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410083000 +0200" stop="20240410084500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: ESA Astronaut class of 2022 – various basic trainings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Are you wondering what the ESA astronauts training is like? Join the five astronauts of the ESA Astronaut Class of 2022: Sophie Adenot, Pablo Álvarez Fernández, Rosemary Coogan, Raphaël Liégeois, Marco Sieber and the Australian Space Agency astronaut candidate Katherine Bennell-Pegg.  You’ll discover a few of their many trainings: the dive into the Neutral Buoyancy Lab, centrifuge training, microbiology courses and a sea survival training.  Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410084500 +0200" stop="20240410091500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The white continent</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cold, dark and remote: Antarctica is as close to space as you can get on Earth. No wonder both scientists and astronauts like to venture on the white continent. In this programme, we take you to the Concordia research station in Antarctica to meet the people spending their winter months in total isolation. We follow ESA astronaut Alexander Gerst on an expedition to retrieve meteorites from the ice. And a leading climate scientist delves into how and why the ice is melting fast not just in Antarctica, but all around the world. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410091500 +0200" stop="20240410094500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Euclid's first images: the dazzling edge of darkness</title>
    <desc lang="en">One space telescope launched in July 2023. Five stunning images released a couple of months later. In this programme, relive the moment ESA revealed to the world the first images of the Euclid spacecraft. Never before has a telescope been able to create such  full-colour images of the cosmos across such a large patch of the sky. Five images that show that the telescope is ready for its mission to create the most extensive 3D map of the Universe yet and uncover some of its hidden secrets – especially regarding the nature of dark energy and dark matter. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410094500 +0200" stop="20240410101500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Celebrating the International Space Station</title>
    <desc lang="en">For more than 20 years, ESA astronauts have joined other crew members on board the International Space Station. More than 240 people have lived and worked on the orbital outpost, carrying our essential research to advance our scientific knowledge in space, but also on Earth. In this special programme recorded for the 20th anniversary of the station, join the very first European astronaut on board Umberto Guidoni, together with Tim Peake, Thomas Pesquet and many others, as they reflect on the station’s remarkable achievements. Watch them recall the best moments of their time on board, including filming strikes from thunderstorms on Earth from the ISS cupola or even dressing up for Halloween. Finally, they share their thoughts on what space exploration might look like in the next 20 years. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410101500 +0200" stop="20240410104500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Stories from the lab</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Materials and Electrical Components Laboratory at ESA’s ESTEC establishment in the Netherlands supports ESA projects at all stages of development. In this 30-minute programme, discover how experts found solution for a variety of issues from a stuck mobile gantry to Gaia’s failed memory modules. See how ‘beta cloth’ fibre was tested for resilience for the Aeolus mission, and how engineers research how spacecraft material respond to the extreme environment of space over time. The lab is an impartial authority – decades of accumulated experience to back up project teams, equipped to carry out a wide variety of tests in-house, or turn to a network of external facilities when required. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410104500 +0200" stop="20240410111500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Return to the Moon: the Artemis journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">More than 50 years after Neil Armstrong set foot on the surface of the Moon, our natural satellite is once again a prime goal of space exploration. Europe has joined USA and other nations to prepare the way for new lunar landings. The Artemis programme aims to establish permanent stations on and around our Moon. Humans will very likely walk again on the Moon in the coming decade – including European astronauts. ESA’s contribution to the Artemis programme is the European Service Module – the module that will provide electricity, water, air for the Orion spacecraft – as well as keeping it at the right temperature and on course. Want to know more about Artemis I, II, III and more? Watch this programme. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410111500 +0200" stop="20240410121500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Das Weltall in Ihrer Sprache – Space in German</title>
    <desc lang="en">Entdecken Sie die europäischen Weltraumaktivitäten in deutscher Sprache. Lernen Sie die Mission Cosmic Kiss des deutschen ESA-Astronauten Matthias Maurer kennen. Seine Mission soll im Herbst 2021 mit dem Start zur ISS beginnen. In Zusammenarbeit mit dem Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt und der Deutschen Raumfahrtagentur im DLR  können sie mit Alexander Gerst die Geheimnisse der Schwerelosigkeit erkunden. Entdecken Sie außerdem unser Sonnensystem und den Mond mit unserem außerirdischen Freund Paxi, oder finden Sie es heraus wie Europa das Problem des Weltraummülls angeht. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410121500 +0200" stop="20240410124500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space Round Up #3</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens next for the new 2022 class of ESA astronauts? Which recent launch to a faraway planet – and its moons – got everyone excited? And which anniversary did we celebrate on 12 March? Get all the answers and more in our third edition of Space Round Up – your news gateway to space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410124500 +0200" stop="20240410131500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Connecting and navigating</title>
    <desc lang="en">From satcoms to GPS, learn how satellites help you find where you are, get you where you want to go, and help you stay connected. This programme introduces space’s part in the 5G revolution and the benefits of satellite communication technology from crisis management to aviation. Take a look back on the development of Europe’s own global satellite navigation system, Galileo. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410131500 +0200" stop="20240410134500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Advancing Earth observation</title>
    <desc lang="en">Getting a bird's-eye view of the Earth is key to understanding it. For decades, satellites have observed our planet from above and their data is now being used by everyone, from relief agencies to local authorities. Learn how Earth Observation helps protecting our environment and how it has become a crucial tool in the fight against climate change. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410134500 +0200" stop="20240410144500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Espace en français – Space in French</title>
    <desc lang="en">En novembre dernier, la toute nouvelle classe d’astronautes 2022 a été présentée au grand public. Pour la première fois depuis 2009, l’ESA a en effet recruté 17 nouveaux astronautes, dont cinq seront astronautes ‘de carrière’. Parmi eux, une française, Sophie Adenot et un belge, Raphael Liégeois. Dans ce programme tout en français, découvrez ces nouveaux astronautes et suivez-les lors de leurs premiers entrainements au Centre Européen des Astronautes à Cologne en Allemagne. Développé en partenariat avec le Centre National d’Études Spatiales, ce programme fait également le point sur la formation des astronautes, sur le retour tant attendu de l’Homme sur la lune – et sur les préparatifs pour une future mission sur Mars. Au menu enfin : Thomas Pesquet nous parle d’eau et d’assainissement ; nous évoquerons aussi la gastronomie dans l’espace et la mesure des étoiles à travers la mission Gaia. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410144500 +0200" stop="20240410151500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Dealing with space debris</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the space highways set to become busier, keeping space clean is a top priority. Discover the ESA initiatives to detect and manage debris, including how spacecraft operators steer satellites back into Earth’s atmosphere. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410151500 +0200" stop="20240410154500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">FIRE - An ESA documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this enthralling new ESA documentary, explore how people on the frontline are using space to better monitor and fight the flames. Follow the incredible stories of the firefighters who dealt with unprecedented fires in Gironde, France, and the forest officers using satellite data to plan for the forests’ recovery. Journey into the heart of Earth's elemental might and discover how space is changing the game for monitoring volcanic eruptions too – including one of the world’s most studied volcano, Mount Etna. FIRE is the first episode of ESA’s new series centred around the elements and showcases how Earth observation has become crucial to those fighting the effects of climate change on the ground. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410154500 +0200" stop="20240410160000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The incredible Adventures of the Hera Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suitable for kids and adults alike, the five episodes of this cartoon series tell the story of the Hera mission, due to launch in October 2024. Following the DART mission’s impact with the Dimorphos asteroid last year – modifying its orbit and sending a plume of debris thousands of kilometres out into space – Hera will return to Dimorphos to perform a close-up survey of the crater left by DART. Hera will be Europe and humankind's first investigation of a planetary defence technique aimed at deflecting asteroids and avoid a collision with Earth. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410160000 +0200" stop="20240410163000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Discover space with Paxi</title>
    <desc lang="en">For kids of all ages: join Paxi, a friendly alien, as he explores Earth, the Moon and beyond. The adventure starts with an introduction to our green friend, and then we follow him through the Solar System. Understanding how our home planet works is important too – and Paxi is ready to teach us! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410163000 +0200" stop="20240410170000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Detecting marine plastic pollution from space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Plastic pollution has become a major challenge not only on Earth but also in our seas -with terrible impacts on marine life and ecosystems. Every 60 seconds the equivalent of a lorry-load of plastic enters the global ocean. Tackling marine litter is a complex challenge involving changes to our economic models, product conception, consumer behaviour and waste disposal systems around the globe. So how can space help out?  Could satellites track plastic litter drifting in the sea? Several ESA-led projects are starting to investigate. In this programme, follow ESA and Deltares researchers as they evaluate whether satellite instruments can detect and monitor marine plastic. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410170000 +0200" stop="20240410171500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ISS Lifestyle</title>
    <desc lang="en">What’s it like to live in space? Join astronauts at 400 km high on the International Space Station. From meals to sleeping to cutting hair, ESA astronauts give us an insider’s view of life in space. It’s not all fun and games –conducting experiments on themselves is part of the job! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410171500 +0200" stop="20240410181500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Leadership at Mission Control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Head of Mission Operations Paolo Ferri as he takes us through major events in his career at ESA, solving the unexpected problems that are part of any space endeavour.  Paolo describes three missions that suffered unexpected and potentially fatal flaws: Smart-1, Cluster and Exosat, and how on-the-ground knowledge, innovation and ingenuity prevented their untimely demise, allowing the science to go on. Recounting his personal experiences, he illustrates the importance of effective communication, as well as leadership, coaching and learning – and lesson learned while working under pressure. For the full set of Paolo’s master class, see our Videos on Demand. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410181500 +0200" stop="20240410184500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The worst that can happen</title>
    <desc lang="en">A team of university students from University College Dublin has taken Ireland to space, for the very first time. The story begins in 2017, when the team was accepted to ESA's educational CubeSat programme, Fly Your Satellite! Over the course of six years, they have designed, built, and tested the satellite with the help of ESA experts and with access to ESA's state-of-the-art spacecraft testing facilities. Finally, on 2 December 2023 EIRSAT-1 launched to space and the rest is Irish history. Níl aon satailít mar do shatailít féin! [There’s no satellite like your own satellite!] (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410184500 +0200" stop="20240410191500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">On the hunt for the riskiest asteroid</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a 50-metre asteroid threatens to strike Earth? In the movies, a superhero would probably save humanity at the last minute – but in reality? Enter Rosa Jesse, our Space Safety Editor and the detective in charge of finding out how risky this new asteroid really is. Initial observations showed 2021 QM1 – the asteroid’s official name – had a chance of striking Earth in 2052, but it soon became invisible as the Sun’s glare got in the way of observations and the asteroid moved away from Earth. Rosa investigates and meets the real people in charge of scrutinising our skies: the asteroid hunters from ESA’s Near-Earth Object Coordination Centre. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410191500 +0200" stop="20240410194500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">MELT</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rising temperatures, melting ice…How will glaciers look over the coming decades? “It all depends on what humans are doing now in terms of greenhouse gas emissions”: this is the message one scientist delivered during an ESA-led expedition to the Gorner Glacier in Switzerland filmed during summer 2021. Put your boots on and join ESA astronaut Luca Parmitano, glaciologists and climate experts on the ice! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410194500 +0200" stop="20240410200000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Andreas Mogensen – Huginn Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Want to visit the ISS? Follow Andreas Mogensen for a short fly within the ISS and watch him conducting science experiments, such as the immunity assay, and robotics demonstrations for the Huggin mission. You will also get to see a spectacular space flyover of the Iberian Peninsula and the Alps that Andreas shared with us during his mission. Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240410200000 +0200" stop="20240411010000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relax with a selection of dazzling imagery from space. (Duration 04:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411010000 +0200" stop="20240411080000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Wake up in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Start your day with spectacular imagery from space. (Duration 07:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411080000 +0200" stop="20240411083000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Dealing with space debris</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the space highways set to become busier, keeping space clean is a top priority. Discover the ESA initiatives to detect and manage debris, including how spacecraft operators steer satellites back into Earth’s atmosphere. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411083000 +0200" stop="20240411090000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space Round Up #3</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens next for the new 2022 class of ESA astronauts? Which recent launch to a faraway planet – and its moons – got everyone excited? And which anniversary did we celebrate on 12 March? Get all the answers and more in our third edition of Space Round Up – your news gateway to space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411090000 +0200" stop="20240411091500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: ESA Astronaut class of 2022 - Guest dive in the Neutral Buoyancy Lab</title>
    <desc lang="en">Immerse yourself in a 10m deep swimming pool with the ESA Astronaut Class of 2022 for one of their most emblematic trainings: the dive in the Neutral Buoyancy Lab (NBL) at the NASA Johnson Space Centre in Texas!  The principle used to simulate weightlessness in a huge tank of water is called 'neutral buoyancy'. The NBL brings astronauts in close conditions to weightlessness and offer a great simulation of life in low-Earth orbit, and beyond. Be ready to dive with Sophie Adenot, Pablo Álvarez Fernández, Rosemary Coogan, Raphaël Liégeois, Marco Sieber and the Australian Space Agency astronaut candidate Katherine Bennell-Peg. Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411091500 +0200" stop="20240411094500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Celebrating the International Space Station</title>
    <desc lang="en">For more than 20 years, ESA astronauts have joined other crew members on board the International Space Station. More than 240 people have lived and worked on the orbital outpost, carrying our essential research to advance our scientific knowledge in space, but also on Earth. In this special programme recorded for the 20th anniversary of the station, join the very first European astronaut on board Umberto Guidoni, together with Tim Peake, Thomas Pesquet and many others, as they reflect on the station’s remarkable achievements. Watch them recall the best moments of their time on board, including filming strikes from thunderstorms on Earth from the ISS cupola or even dressing up for Halloween. Finally, they share their thoughts on what space exploration might look like in the next 20 years. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411094500 +0200" stop="20240411101500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">MELT</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rising temperatures, melting ice…How will glaciers look over the coming decades? “It all depends on what humans are doing now in terms of greenhouse gas emissions”: this is the message one scientist delivered during an ESA-led expedition to the Gorner Glacier in Switzerland filmed during summer 2021. Put your boots on and join ESA astronaut Luca Parmitano, glaciologists and climate experts on the ice! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411101500 +0200" stop="20240411104500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The white continent</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cold, dark and remote: Antarctica is as close to space as you can get on Earth. No wonder both scientists and astronauts like to venture on the white continent. In this programme, we take you to the Concordia research station in Antarctica to meet the people spending their winter months in total isolation. We follow ESA astronaut Alexander Gerst on an expedition to retrieve meteorites from the ice. And a leading climate scientist delves into how and why the ice is melting fast not just in Antarctica, but all around the world. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411104500 +0200" stop="20240411111500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Advancing Earth observation</title>
    <desc lang="en">Getting a bird's-eye view of the Earth is key to understanding it. For decades, satellites have observed our planet from above and their data is now being used by everyone, from relief agencies to local authorities. Learn how Earth Observation helps protecting our environment and how it has become a crucial tool in the fight against climate change. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411111500 +0200" stop="20240411121500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Planet Aqua</title>
    <desc lang="en">About 70% of our planet is made of water. While fresh water sustains life on Earth, it is also essential for living in space. In this new documentary, ESA astronaut Andre Kuipers recounts his experience living in orbit and looking at the blue face of ‘Planet Aqua’. What observations can astronauts and divers share when it comes to water? How do satellites track marine litter? And how are spacecraft-grade recycling systems being used back down on Earth? Watch to get all the answers. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411121500 +0200" stop="20240411123000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">An astronaut at mission control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Before ESA astronaut Andreas Mogensen launched to the International Space Station for his second mission in space called Huginn, he agreed to come and meet the experts who are flying our satellites and spacecrafts at the European Space Operations Centre (ESOC) in Darmstadt, Germany. Why does an astronaut need to know about the handrails of the International Space Station before every spacewalk? What happens if a spacecraft is on a collision course with a faraway planet? How can sun radiation impact astronauts and…our electricity grids? Andreas’ encounters at ESOC will give you all the answers. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411123000 +0200" stop="20240411130000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The worst that can happen</title>
    <desc lang="en">A team of university students from University College Dublin has taken Ireland to space, for the very first time. The story begins in 2017, when the team was accepted to ESA's educational CubeSat programme, Fly Your Satellite! Over the course of six years, they have designed, built, and tested the satellite with the help of ESA experts and with access to ESA's state-of-the-art spacecraft testing facilities. Finally, on 2 December 2023 EIRSAT-1 launched to space and the rest is Irish history. Níl aon satailít mar do shatailít féin! [There’s no satellite like your own satellite!] (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411130000 +0200" stop="20240411133000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The making of JUICE - Episode 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the second episode of this ‘behind the scenes’ documentary, we look back on the excitement building up before the launch of Juice. Watch and follow the Juice team and the spacecraft itself as it is tested in the Netherlands and assembled before being shipped to Europe’s spaceport in French Guiana for launch. The JUICE mission aims at exploring Jupiter and its icy moons – in the hope of learning more about the origins and possibility of life in our Universe. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411133000 +0200" stop="20240411134500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The incredible Adventures of the Hera Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suitable for kids and adults alike, the five episodes of this cartoon series tell the story of the Hera mission, due to launch in October 2024. Following the DART mission’s impact with the Dimorphos asteroid last year – modifying its orbit and sending a plume of debris thousands of kilometres out into space – Hera will return to Dimorphos to perform a close-up survey of the crater left by DART. Hera will be Europe and humankind's first investigation of a planetary defence technique aimed at deflecting asteroids and avoid a collision with Earth. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411134500 +0200" stop="20240411143000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The making of JUICE - The Instruments</title>
    <desc lang="en">Juice, the Jupiter Icy Moons Explorer, launched on board an Ariane 5 rocket on 14th April 2023. The spacecraft has a state-of-the-art science payload comprising remote sensing, geophysical and in-situ instruments. Using these instruments scientists will study the atmosphere of Jupiter and the surfaces and exospheres of the icy moons, Europa, Ganymede and Callisto. In this episode of The Making of JUICE, scientists of each of the instrument teams tell about what they plan to do once Juice arrives in the jovian system in 2031. (Duration 00:45:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411143000 +0200" stop="20240411150000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Hubble highlights</title>
    <desc lang="en">Revisit some of the NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope’s biggest science discoveries from its three decades in operation. This programme kicks off with an introduction to the ‘Mother of Hubble’ Nancy Roman, then takes us on a tour of some of the telescope’s big finds. Explore how Hubble’s observations will be complemented by those of the upcoming NASA/ESA/CSA James Webb Space Telescope. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411150000 +0200" stop="20240411160000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Das Weltall in Ihrer Sprache – Space in German</title>
    <desc lang="en">Entdecken Sie die europäischen Weltraumaktivitäten in deutscher Sprache. Lernen Sie die Mission Cosmic Kiss des deutschen ESA-Astronauten Matthias Maurer kennen. Seine Mission soll im Herbst 2021 mit dem Start zur ISS beginnen. In Zusammenarbeit mit dem Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt und der Deutschen Raumfahrtagentur im DLR  können sie mit Alexander Gerst die Geheimnisse der Schwerelosigkeit erkunden. Entdecken Sie außerdem unser Sonnensystem und den Mond mit unserem außerirdischen Freund Paxi, oder finden Sie es heraus wie Europa das Problem des Weltraummülls angeht. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411160000 +0200" stop="20240411170000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Espace en français – Space in French</title>
    <desc lang="en">En novembre dernier, la toute nouvelle classe d’astronautes 2022 a été présentée au grand public. Pour la première fois depuis 2009, l’ESA a en effet recruté 17 nouveaux astronautes, dont cinq seront astronautes ‘de carrière’. Parmi eux, une française, Sophie Adenot et un belge, Raphael Liégeois. Dans ce programme tout en français, découvrez ces nouveaux astronautes et suivez-les lors de leurs premiers entrainements au Centre Européen des Astronautes à Cologne en Allemagne. Développé en partenariat avec le Centre National d’Études Spatiales, ce programme fait également le point sur la formation des astronautes, sur le retour tant attendu de l’Homme sur la lune – et sur les préparatifs pour une future mission sur Mars. Au menu enfin : Thomas Pesquet nous parle d’eau et d’assainissement ; nous évoquerons aussi la gastronomie dans l’espace et la mesure des étoiles à travers la mission Gaia. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411170000 +0200" stop="20240411171500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">A colourful journey through our Universe with James Webb</title>
    <desc lang="en">It is the largest, most powerful telescope ever launched into space: the James Webb Space Telescope! Following Hubble Space Telescope’s footsteps, James Webb is unveiling the secrets of the creation of the Universe and making breakthrough discoveries in multiple fields of astronomy. Have you ever wondered what the early Universe looked like? Would you like to discover new galaxies?  Let’s travel back in time, dive into our origins and look at the striking infrared images of the most distant universe we have ever seen …so far. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411171500 +0200" stop="20240411174500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Training for unknown terrain</title>
    <desc lang="en">Astronauts undergo rigorous training that prepares them to adapt to and survive in harsh conditions. Follow the simulation of an Earth-landing gone wrong and how astronauts – or any explorers – stay alive until help arrives. With preparations underway to send humans back to the Moon and onto Mars, astronauts need to learn how to cope with long-duration spaceflight, orient themselves in unknown territory and conduct useful research about their surroundings whilst enduring it. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411174500 +0200" stop="20240411181500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">FIRE - An ESA documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this enthralling new ESA documentary, explore how people on the frontline are using space to better monitor and fight the flames. Follow the incredible stories of the firefighters who dealt with unprecedented fires in Gironde, France, and the forest officers using satellite data to plan for the forests’ recovery. Journey into the heart of Earth's elemental might and discover how space is changing the game for monitoring volcanic eruptions too – including one of the world’s most studied volcano, Mount Etna. FIRE is the first episode of ESA’s new series centred around the elements and showcases how Earth observation has become crucial to those fighting the effects of climate change on the ground. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411181500 +0200" stop="20240411183000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: ESA Astronaut class of 2022 – Sea Survival</title>
    <desc lang="en">Put on your life jacket and join the ESA Astronaut Class of 2022 for their sea survival training! ESA prepares the astronauts for almost everything in space, but also anything on the ground. Extreme Earth landing conditions - such as on the sea - can take place during emergency landings. Before they can be rescued, astronauts may have to rely only on very basic items and the emergency pack available in their capsule. Follow Sophie Adenot, Pablo Álvarez Fernández, Rosemary Coogan, Raphaël Liégeois, Marco Sieber and the Australian Space Agency astronaut candidate Katherine Bennell-Pegg during one of the most physical demanding courses of their basic training. Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411183000 +0200" stop="20240411190000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Working at ESA</title>
    <desc lang="en">What is it like to work at a space agency? With its 22 Member States and more than 2600 staff members working across Europe in nine different locations, ESA is a unique place to work. Between 2020 and 2030, 44% of the ESA workforce will retire and ESA has been riding a recruitment wave. In this programme, the Human Resources department answers all your questions on working at ESA. Meet also some of ESA’s workforce including Young Graduate Trainees who explain some of the projects they’re involved in and what it’s like to work in space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411190000 +0200" stop="20240411193000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space health</title>
    <desc lang="en">Living in space does impact the health of astronauts and they undergo rigorous training exercises to keep fit in zero gravity. But how does space research help improve the health of populations on Earth? In this programme, find out how research carried out on the ISS advances our medical knowledge on ageing, hibernation, muscles or even blood vessels. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411193000 +0200" stop="20240411200000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The making of JUICE - Episode 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do you develop a spacecraft in the midst of a global pandemic? In this film, director Maarten Roos takes you behind the scenes of a very special mission called Juice. This new spacecraft developed by ESA took to the skies on 14th April 2023. After an eight-year journey, the Jupiter Icy Moons Explorer (JUICE) will study the gas giant Jupiter and three of its largest moons: Ganymede, Callisto and Europa. In the first episode of this atmospheric documentary, follow the JUICE team as they are confronted with unexpected challenges, such as the Covid pandemic. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240411200000 +0200" stop="20240412010000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relax with a selection of dazzling imagery from space. (Duration 04:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412010000 +0200" stop="20240412080000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Wake up in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Start your day with spectacular imagery from space. (Duration 07:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412080000 +0200" stop="20240412081500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Samantha’s launch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Immerse yourself in an astronaut’s journey from Earth to the International Space Station. Rough Cut brings you up close to the key moments of a launch – without the loud music and usual commentaries. Follow ESA astronaut Samantha Cristoforetti as she waves goodbye to her loved ones, steps into the Crew Dragon capsule with three fellow NASA astronauts and feels the first effects of the launch and weightlessness. Stay with her when she finally enters the hatch of the International Space Station after a transit of just under 24 hours, and greets another ESA astronaut, Matthias Maurer – all in zero gravity. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412081500 +0200" stop="20240412083000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">An astronaut at mission control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Before ESA astronaut Andreas Mogensen launched to the International Space Station for his second mission in space called Huginn, he agreed to come and meet the experts who are flying our satellites and spacecrafts at the European Space Operations Centre (ESOC) in Darmstadt, Germany. Why does an astronaut need to know about the handrails of the International Space Station before every spacewalk? What happens if a spacecraft is on a collision course with a faraway planet? How can sun radiation impact astronauts and…our electricity grids? Andreas’ encounters at ESOC will give you all the answers. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412083000 +0200" stop="20240412090000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Hubble highlights</title>
    <desc lang="en">Revisit some of the NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope’s biggest science discoveries from its three decades in operation. This programme kicks off with an introduction to the ‘Mother of Hubble’ Nancy Roman, then takes us on a tour of some of the telescope’s big finds. Explore how Hubble’s observations will be complemented by those of the upcoming NASA/ESA/CSA James Webb Space Telescope. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412090000 +0200" stop="20240412091500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The incredible Adventures of the Hera Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suitable for kids and adults alike, the five episodes of this cartoon series tell the story of the Hera mission, due to launch in October 2024. Following the DART mission’s impact with the Dimorphos asteroid last year – modifying its orbit and sending a plume of debris thousands of kilometres out into space – Hera will return to Dimorphos to perform a close-up survey of the crater left by DART. Hera will be Europe and humankind's first investigation of a planetary defence technique aimed at deflecting asteroids and avoid a collision with Earth. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412091500 +0200" stop="20240412093000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">A colourful journey through our Universe with James Webb</title>
    <desc lang="en">It is the largest, most powerful telescope ever launched into space: the James Webb Space Telescope! Following Hubble Space Telescope’s footsteps, James Webb is unveiling the secrets of the creation of the Universe and making breakthrough discoveries in multiple fields of astronomy. Have you ever wondered what the early Universe looked like? Would you like to discover new galaxies?  Let’s travel back in time, dive into our origins and look at the striking infrared images of the most distant universe we have ever seen …so far. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412093000 +0200" stop="20240412100000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">FIRE - An ESA documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this enthralling new ESA documentary, explore how people on the frontline are using space to better monitor and fight the flames. Follow the incredible stories of the firefighters who dealt with unprecedented fires in Gironde, France, and the forest officers using satellite data to plan for the forests’ recovery. Journey into the heart of Earth's elemental might and discover how space is changing the game for monitoring volcanic eruptions too – including one of the world’s most studied volcano, Mount Etna. FIRE is the first episode of ESA’s new series centred around the elements and showcases how Earth observation has become crucial to those fighting the effects of climate change on the ground. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412100000 +0200" stop="20240412103000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space for our climate</title>
    <desc lang="en">The world is heating up, and it appears to be due to our actions. According to scientists, we are living through the largest climate change since the end of the last ice age, 10 000 years ago. Its consequences are already being felt across the globe: shrinking glaciers, rising sea levels, changes in atmospheric composition. So how can space support the efforts to curb global warming? In this programme, learn how data from ESA satellites orbiting the Earth can provide precious information for decision-makers on key components of the climate system – from mapping the world’s forest to measuring the melting of ice sheets. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412103000 +0200" stop="20240412104500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Samantha in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spend some time with Samantha Cristoforetti as she carries out the daily activities of an astronaut on the International Space Station (ISS): floating in space and conducting experiments in zero gravity, even doing some gardening and performing a spacewalk! This summer, Samantha became the first European woman to put a spacesuit on and exit the airlock of the ISS. In this programme, relive the slow and meticulous tasks a spacewalker must carry out including, on this occasion, some works on the European Robotic Arm. Rough Cut is the programme that lets you immerse yourself into key moments, without any commentary nor music. Only natural sounds and often, just the silence of our Universe. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412104500 +0200" stop="20240412114500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Das Weltall in Ihrer Sprache – Space in German</title>
    <desc lang="en">Entdecken Sie die europäischen Weltraumaktivitäten in deutscher Sprache. Lernen Sie die Mission Cosmic Kiss des deutschen ESA-Astronauten Matthias Maurer kennen. Seine Mission soll im Herbst 2021 mit dem Start zur ISS beginnen. In Zusammenarbeit mit dem Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt und der Deutschen Raumfahrtagentur im DLR  können sie mit Alexander Gerst die Geheimnisse der Schwerelosigkeit erkunden. Entdecken Sie außerdem unser Sonnensystem und den Mond mit unserem außerirdischen Freund Paxi, oder finden Sie es heraus wie Europa das Problem des Weltraummülls angeht. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412114500 +0200" stop="20240412121500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space health</title>
    <desc lang="en">Living in space does impact the health of astronauts and they undergo rigorous training exercises to keep fit in zero gravity. But how does space research help improve the health of populations on Earth? In this programme, find out how research carried out on the ISS advances our medical knowledge on ageing, hibernation, muscles or even blood vessels. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412121500 +0200" stop="20240412124500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">MELT</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rising temperatures, melting ice…How will glaciers look over the coming decades? “It all depends on what humans are doing now in terms of greenhouse gas emissions”: this is the message one scientist delivered during an ESA-led expedition to the Gorner Glacier in Switzerland filmed during summer 2021. Put your boots on and join ESA astronaut Luca Parmitano, glaciologists and climate experts on the ice! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412124500 +0200" stop="20240412134500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Leadership at Mission Control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Head of Mission Operations Paolo Ferri as he takes us through major events in his career at ESA, solving the unexpected problems that are part of any space endeavour.  Paolo describes three missions that suffered unexpected and potentially fatal flaws: Smart-1, Cluster and Exosat, and how on-the-ground knowledge, innovation and ingenuity prevented their untimely demise, allowing the science to go on. Recounting his personal experiences, he illustrates the importance of effective communication, as well as leadership, coaching and learning – and lesson learned while working under pressure. For the full set of Paolo’s master class, see our Videos on Demand. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412134500 +0200" stop="20240412141500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The white continent</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cold, dark and remote: Antarctica is as close to space as you can get on Earth. No wonder both scientists and astronauts like to venture on the white continent. In this programme, we take you to the Concordia research station in Antarctica to meet the people spending their winter months in total isolation. We follow ESA astronaut Alexander Gerst on an expedition to retrieve meteorites from the ice. And a leading climate scientist delves into how and why the ice is melting fast not just in Antarctica, but all around the world. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412141500 +0200" stop="20240412144500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Euclid's first images: the dazzling edge of darkness</title>
    <desc lang="en">One space telescope launched in July 2023. Five stunning images released a couple of months later. In this programme, relive the moment ESA revealed to the world the first images of the Euclid spacecraft. Never before has a telescope been able to create such  full-colour images of the cosmos across such a large patch of the sky. Five images that show that the telescope is ready for its mission to create the most extensive 3D map of the Universe yet and uncover some of its hidden secrets – especially regarding the nature of dark energy and dark matter. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412144500 +0200" stop="20240412151500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Discover space with Paxi</title>
    <desc lang="en">For kids of all ages: join Paxi, a friendly alien, as he explores Earth, the Moon and beyond. The adventure starts with an introduction to our green friend, and then we follow him through the Solar System. Understanding how our home planet works is important too – and Paxi is ready to teach us! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412151500 +0200" stop="20240412154500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Celebrating the International Space Station</title>
    <desc lang="en">For more than 20 years, ESA astronauts have joined other crew members on board the International Space Station. More than 240 people have lived and worked on the orbital outpost, carrying our essential research to advance our scientific knowledge in space, but also on Earth. In this special programme recorded for the 20th anniversary of the station, join the very first European astronaut on board Umberto Guidoni, together with Tim Peake, Thomas Pesquet and many others, as they reflect on the station’s remarkable achievements. Watch them recall the best moments of their time on board, including filming strikes from thunderstorms on Earth from the ISS cupola or even dressing up for Halloween. Finally, they share their thoughts on what space exploration might look like in the next 20 years. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412154500 +0200" stop="20240412161500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Return to the Moon: the Artemis journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">More than 50 years after Neil Armstrong set foot on the surface of the Moon, our natural satellite is once again a prime goal of space exploration. Europe has joined USA and other nations to prepare the way for new lunar landings. The Artemis programme aims to establish permanent stations on and around our Moon. Humans will very likely walk again on the Moon in the coming decade – including European astronauts. ESA’s contribution to the Artemis programme is the European Service Module – the module that will provide electricity, water, air for the Orion spacecraft – as well as keeping it at the right temperature and on course. Want to know more about Artemis I, II, III and more? Watch this programme. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412161500 +0200" stop="20240412163000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: ESA Astronaut class of 2022 – various basic trainings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Are you wondering what the ESA astronauts training is like? Join the five astronauts of the ESA Astronaut Class of 2022: Sophie Adenot, Pablo Álvarez Fernández, Rosemary Coogan, Raphaël Liégeois, Marco Sieber and the Australian Space Agency astronaut candidate Katherine Bennell-Pegg.  You’ll discover a few of their many trainings: the dive into the Neutral Buoyancy Lab, centrifuge training, microbiology courses and a sea survival training.  Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412163000 +0200" stop="20240412170000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space Round Up #3</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens next for the new 2022 class of ESA astronauts? Which recent launch to a faraway planet – and its moons – got everyone excited? And which anniversary did we celebrate on 12 March? Get all the answers and more in our third edition of Space Round Up – your news gateway to space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412170000 +0200" stop="20240412180000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Espace en français – Space in French</title>
    <desc lang="en">En novembre dernier, la toute nouvelle classe d’astronautes 2022 a été présentée au grand public. Pour la première fois depuis 2009, l’ESA a en effet recruté 17 nouveaux astronautes, dont cinq seront astronautes ‘de carrière’. Parmi eux, une française, Sophie Adenot et un belge, Raphael Liégeois. Dans ce programme tout en français, découvrez ces nouveaux astronautes et suivez-les lors de leurs premiers entrainements au Centre Européen des Astronautes à Cologne en Allemagne. Développé en partenariat avec le Centre National d’Études Spatiales, ce programme fait également le point sur la formation des astronautes, sur le retour tant attendu de l’Homme sur la lune – et sur les préparatifs pour une future mission sur Mars. Au menu enfin : Thomas Pesquet nous parle d’eau et d’assainissement ; nous évoquerons aussi la gastronomie dans l’espace et la mesure des étoiles à travers la mission Gaia. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412180000 +0200" stop="20240412181500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ISS Lifestyle</title>
    <desc lang="en">What’s it like to live in space? Join astronauts at 400 km high on the International Space Station. From meals to sleeping to cutting hair, ESA astronauts give us an insider’s view of life in space. It’s not all fun and games –conducting experiments on themselves is part of the job! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412181500 +0200" stop="20240412184500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The worst that can happen</title>
    <desc lang="en">A team of university students from University College Dublin has taken Ireland to space, for the very first time. The story begins in 2017, when the team was accepted to ESA's educational CubeSat programme, Fly Your Satellite! Over the course of six years, they have designed, built, and tested the satellite with the help of ESA experts and with access to ESA's state-of-the-art spacecraft testing facilities. Finally, on 2 December 2023 EIRSAT-1 launched to space and the rest is Irish history. Níl aon satailít mar do shatailít féin! [There’s no satellite like your own satellite!] (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412184500 +0200" stop="20240412191500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Stories from the lab</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Materials and Electrical Components Laboratory at ESA’s ESTEC establishment in the Netherlands supports ESA projects at all stages of development. In this 30-minute programme, discover how experts found solution for a variety of issues from a stuck mobile gantry to Gaia’s failed memory modules. See how ‘beta cloth’ fibre was tested for resilience for the Aeolus mission, and how engineers research how spacecraft material respond to the extreme environment of space over time. The lab is an impartial authority – decades of accumulated experience to back up project teams, equipped to carry out a wide variety of tests in-house, or turn to a network of external facilities when required. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412191500 +0200" stop="20240412193000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Samantha returns to Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do astronauts come back to Earth? What happens during the long hours of descent? Our latest episode of Rough Cut condensates about 6 hours of footage into a 15min immersive watch. From entering the SpaceX spacecraft and closing the hatch of the International Space Station, to deploying parachutes and splashing-off the coast of Florida, follow ESA astronaut Samantha Cristoforetti as she returns to Earth. Rough Cut compiles raw images with natural sound only and no comments. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412193000 +0200" stop="20240412200000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Watching for asteroids</title>
    <desc lang="en">Next October 2024, ESA will launch the HERA spacecraft into space as part of the world’s first test of asteroid deflection. But where do asteroids come from, why they are a threat and what is being done to monitor their movement? Get all the answers from ESA’s planetary defence experts and learn about the possibilities of asteroid deflection in this special programme on all-things asteroids. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240412200000 +0200" stop="20240413010000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relax with a selection of dazzling imagery from space. (Duration 04:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413010000 +0200" stop="20240413080000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Wake up in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Start your day with spectacular imagery from space. (Duration 07:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413080000 +0200" stop="20240413083000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Detecting marine plastic pollution from space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Plastic pollution has become a major challenge not only on Earth but also in our seas -with terrible impacts on marine life and ecosystems. Every 60 seconds the equivalent of a lorry-load of plastic enters the global ocean. Tackling marine litter is a complex challenge involving changes to our economic models, product conception, consumer behaviour and waste disposal systems around the globe. So how can space help out?  Could satellites track plastic litter drifting in the sea? Several ESA-led projects are starting to investigate. In this programme, follow ESA and Deltares researchers as they evaluate whether satellite instruments can detect and monitor marine plastic. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413083000 +0200" stop="20240413090000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space for our climate</title>
    <desc lang="en">The world is heating up, and it appears to be due to our actions. According to scientists, we are living through the largest climate change since the end of the last ice age, 10 000 years ago. Its consequences are already being felt across the globe: shrinking glaciers, rising sea levels, changes in atmospheric composition. So how can space support the efforts to curb global warming? In this programme, learn how data from ESA satellites orbiting the Earth can provide precious information for decision-makers on key components of the climate system – from mapping the world’s forest to measuring the melting of ice sheets. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413090000 +0200" stop="20240413093000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The making of JUICE - Episode 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do you develop a spacecraft in the midst of a global pandemic? In this film, director Maarten Roos takes you behind the scenes of a very special mission called Juice. This new spacecraft developed by ESA took to the skies on 14th April 2023. After an eight-year journey, the Jupiter Icy Moons Explorer (JUICE) will study the gas giant Jupiter and three of its largest moons: Ganymede, Callisto and Europa. In the first episode of this atmospheric documentary, follow the JUICE team as they are confronted with unexpected challenges, such as the Covid pandemic. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413093000 +0200" stop="20240413103000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Das Weltall in Ihrer Sprache – Space in German</title>
    <desc lang="en">Entdecken Sie die europäischen Weltraumaktivitäten in deutscher Sprache. Lernen Sie die Mission Cosmic Kiss des deutschen ESA-Astronauten Matthias Maurer kennen. Seine Mission soll im Herbst 2021 mit dem Start zur ISS beginnen. In Zusammenarbeit mit dem Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt und der Deutschen Raumfahrtagentur im DLR  können sie mit Alexander Gerst die Geheimnisse der Schwerelosigkeit erkunden. Entdecken Sie außerdem unser Sonnensystem und den Mond mit unserem außerirdischen Freund Paxi, oder finden Sie es heraus wie Europa das Problem des Weltraummülls angeht. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413103000 +0200" stop="20240413110000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The making of JUICE - Episode 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the second episode of this ‘behind the scenes’ documentary, we look back on the excitement building up before the launch of Juice. Watch and follow the Juice team and the spacecraft itself as it is tested in the Netherlands and assembled before being shipped to Europe’s spaceport in French Guiana for launch. The JUICE mission aims at exploring Jupiter and its icy moons – in the hope of learning more about the origins and possibility of life in our Universe. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413110000 +0200" stop="20240413111500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The incredible Adventures of the Hera Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suitable for kids and adults alike, the five episodes of this cartoon series tell the story of the Hera mission, due to launch in October 2024. Following the DART mission’s impact with the Dimorphos asteroid last year – modifying its orbit and sending a plume of debris thousands of kilometres out into space – Hera will return to Dimorphos to perform a close-up survey of the crater left by DART. Hera will be Europe and humankind's first investigation of a planetary defence technique aimed at deflecting asteroids and avoid a collision with Earth. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413111500 +0200" stop="20240413114500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Hubble highlights</title>
    <desc lang="en">Revisit some of the NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope’s biggest science discoveries from its three decades in operation. This programme kicks off with an introduction to the ‘Mother of Hubble’ Nancy Roman, then takes us on a tour of some of the telescope’s big finds. Explore how Hubble’s observations will be complemented by those of the upcoming NASA/ESA/CSA James Webb Space Telescope. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413114500 +0200" stop="20240413123000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The making of JUICE - The Instruments</title>
    <desc lang="en">Juice, the Jupiter Icy Moons Explorer, launched on board an Ariane 5 rocket on 14th April 2023. The spacecraft has a state-of-the-art science payload comprising remote sensing, geophysical and in-situ instruments. Using these instruments scientists will study the atmosphere of Jupiter and the surfaces and exospheres of the icy moons, Europa, Ganymede and Callisto. In this episode of The Making of JUICE, scientists of each of the instrument teams tell about what they plan to do once Juice arrives in the jovian system in 2031. (Duration 00:45:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413123000 +0200" stop="20240413124500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: ESA Astronaut class of 2022 – various basic trainings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Are you wondering what the ESA astronauts training is like? Join the five astronauts of the ESA Astronaut Class of 2022: Sophie Adenot, Pablo Álvarez Fernández, Rosemary Coogan, Raphaël Liégeois, Marco Sieber and the Australian Space Agency astronaut candidate Katherine Bennell-Pegg.  You’ll discover a few of their many trainings: the dive into the Neutral Buoyancy Lab, centrifuge training, microbiology courses and a sea survival training.  Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413124500 +0200" stop="20240413131500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Celebrating the International Space Station</title>
    <desc lang="en">For more than 20 years, ESA astronauts have joined other crew members on board the International Space Station. More than 240 people have lived and worked on the orbital outpost, carrying our essential research to advance our scientific knowledge in space, but also on Earth. In this special programme recorded for the 20th anniversary of the station, join the very first European astronaut on board Umberto Guidoni, together with Tim Peake, Thomas Pesquet and many others, as they reflect on the station’s remarkable achievements. Watch them recall the best moments of their time on board, including filming strikes from thunderstorms on Earth from the ISS cupola or even dressing up for Halloween. Finally, they share their thoughts on what space exploration might look like in the next 20 years. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413131500 +0200" stop="20240413134500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">MELT</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rising temperatures, melting ice…How will glaciers look over the coming decades? “It all depends on what humans are doing now in terms of greenhouse gas emissions”: this is the message one scientist delivered during an ESA-led expedition to the Gorner Glacier in Switzerland filmed during summer 2021. Put your boots on and join ESA astronaut Luca Parmitano, glaciologists and climate experts on the ice! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413134500 +0200" stop="20240413141500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The white continent</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cold, dark and remote: Antarctica is as close to space as you can get on Earth. No wonder both scientists and astronauts like to venture on the white continent. In this programme, we take you to the Concordia research station in Antarctica to meet the people spending their winter months in total isolation. We follow ESA astronaut Alexander Gerst on an expedition to retrieve meteorites from the ice. And a leading climate scientist delves into how and why the ice is melting fast not just in Antarctica, but all around the world. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413141500 +0200" stop="20240413144500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Euclid's first images: the dazzling edge of darkness</title>
    <desc lang="en">One space telescope launched in July 2023. Five stunning images released a couple of months later. In this programme, relive the moment ESA revealed to the world the first images of the Euclid spacecraft. Never before has a telescope been able to create such  full-colour images of the cosmos across such a large patch of the sky. Five images that show that the telescope is ready for its mission to create the most extensive 3D map of the Universe yet and uncover some of its hidden secrets – especially regarding the nature of dark energy and dark matter. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413144500 +0200" stop="20240413151500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Advancing Earth observation</title>
    <desc lang="en">Getting a bird's-eye view of the Earth is key to understanding it. For decades, satellites have observed our planet from above and their data is now being used by everyone, from relief agencies to local authorities. Learn how Earth Observation helps protecting our environment and how it has become a crucial tool in the fight against climate change. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413151500 +0200" stop="20240413154500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Return to the Moon: the Artemis journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">More than 50 years after Neil Armstrong set foot on the surface of the Moon, our natural satellite is once again a prime goal of space exploration. Europe has joined USA and other nations to prepare the way for new lunar landings. The Artemis programme aims to establish permanent stations on and around our Moon. Humans will very likely walk again on the Moon in the coming decade – including European astronauts. ESA’s contribution to the Artemis programme is the European Service Module – the module that will provide electricity, water, air for the Orion spacecraft – as well as keeping it at the right temperature and on course. Want to know more about Artemis I, II, III and more? Watch this programme. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413154500 +0200" stop="20240413161500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The worst that can happen</title>
    <desc lang="en">A team of university students from University College Dublin has taken Ireland to space, for the very first time. The story begins in 2017, when the team was accepted to ESA's educational CubeSat programme, Fly Your Satellite! Over the course of six years, they have designed, built, and tested the satellite with the help of ESA experts and with access to ESA's state-of-the-art spacecraft testing facilities. Finally, on 2 December 2023 EIRSAT-1 launched to space and the rest is Irish history. Níl aon satailít mar do shatailít féin! [There’s no satellite like your own satellite!] (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413161500 +0200" stop="20240413171500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Espace en français – Space in French</title>
    <desc lang="en">En novembre dernier, la toute nouvelle classe d’astronautes 2022 a été présentée au grand public. Pour la première fois depuis 2009, l’ESA a en effet recruté 17 nouveaux astronautes, dont cinq seront astronautes ‘de carrière’. Parmi eux, une française, Sophie Adenot et un belge, Raphael Liégeois. Dans ce programme tout en français, découvrez ces nouveaux astronautes et suivez-les lors de leurs premiers entrainements au Centre Européen des Astronautes à Cologne en Allemagne. Développé en partenariat avec le Centre National d’Études Spatiales, ce programme fait également le point sur la formation des astronautes, sur le retour tant attendu de l’Homme sur la lune – et sur les préparatifs pour une future mission sur Mars. Au menu enfin : Thomas Pesquet nous parle d’eau et d’assainissement ; nous évoquerons aussi la gastronomie dans l’espace et la mesure des étoiles à travers la mission Gaia. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413171500 +0200" stop="20240413173000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ISS Lifestyle</title>
    <desc lang="en">What’s it like to live in space? Join astronauts at 400 km high on the International Space Station. From meals to sleeping to cutting hair, ESA astronauts give us an insider’s view of life in space. It’s not all fun and games –conducting experiments on themselves is part of the job! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413173000 +0200" stop="20240413174500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Andreas Mogensen – Huginn Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Want to visit the ISS? Follow Andreas Mogensen for a short fly within the ISS and watch him conducting science experiments, such as the immunity assay, and robotics demonstrations for the Huggin mission. You will also get to see a spectacular space flyover of the Iberian Peninsula and the Alps that Andreas shared with us during his mission. Simply raw images, natural sound and minimal editing… This is Rough Cut! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413174500 +0200" stop="20240413180000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">An astronaut at mission control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Before ESA astronaut Andreas Mogensen launched to the International Space Station for his second mission in space called Huginn, he agreed to come and meet the experts who are flying our satellites and spacecrafts at the European Space Operations Centre (ESOC) in Darmstadt, Germany. Why does an astronaut need to know about the handrails of the International Space Station before every spacewalk? What happens if a spacecraft is on a collision course with a faraway planet? How can sun radiation impact astronauts and…our electricity grids? Andreas’ encounters at ESOC will give you all the answers. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413180000 +0200" stop="20240413183000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">FIRE - An ESA documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this enthralling new ESA documentary, explore how people on the frontline are using space to better monitor and fight the flames. Follow the incredible stories of the firefighters who dealt with unprecedented fires in Gironde, France, and the forest officers using satellite data to plan for the forests’ recovery. Journey into the heart of Earth's elemental might and discover how space is changing the game for monitoring volcanic eruptions too – including one of the world’s most studied volcano, Mount Etna. FIRE is the first episode of ESA’s new series centred around the elements and showcases how Earth observation has become crucial to those fighting the effects of climate change on the ground. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413183000 +0200" stop="20240413190000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Working at ESA</title>
    <desc lang="en">What is it like to work at a space agency? With its 22 Member States and more than 2600 staff members working across Europe in nine different locations, ESA is a unique place to work. Between 2020 and 2030, 44% of the ESA workforce will retire and ESA has been riding a recruitment wave. In this programme, the Human Resources department answers all your questions on working at ESA. Meet also some of ESA’s workforce including Young Graduate Trainees who explain some of the projects they’re involved in and what it’s like to work in space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413190000 +0200" stop="20240413193000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space health</title>
    <desc lang="en">Living in space does impact the health of astronauts and they undergo rigorous training exercises to keep fit in zero gravity. But how does space research help improve the health of populations on Earth? In this programme, find out how research carried out on the ISS advances our medical knowledge on ageing, hibernation, muscles or even blood vessels. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413193000 +0200" stop="20240413200000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space Round Up #3</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens next for the new 2022 class of ESA astronauts? Which recent launch to a faraway planet – and its moons – got everyone excited? And which anniversary did we celebrate on 12 March? Get all the answers and more in our third edition of Space Round Up – your news gateway to space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240413200000 +0200" stop="20240414000000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relax with a selection of dazzling imagery from space. (Duration 04:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
</tv>

