<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">

<tv source-info-name="ESA Web TV One guide by TV" source-info-url="https://www.esa.int/ESA_Multimedia/ESA_Web_TV">
  <channel id="ESAWebTVOne.int">
    <display-name>ESA Web TV One</display-name>
    <url>https://www.esa.int/ESA_Multimedia/ESA_Web_TV</url>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422010000 +0200" stop="20240422080000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Wake up in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Start your day with spectacular imagery from space. (Duration 07:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422080000 +0200" stop="20240422083000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Connecting and navigating</title>
    <desc lang="en">From satcoms to GPS, learn how satellites help you find where you are, get you where you want to go, and help you stay connected. This programme introduces space’s part in the 5G revolution and the benefits of satellite communication technology from crisis management to aviation. Take a look back on the development of Europe’s own global satellite navigation system, Galileo. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422083000 +0200" stop="20240422090000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space Round Up #3</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens next for the new 2022 class of ESA astronauts? Which recent launch to a faraway planet – and its moons – got everyone excited? And which anniversary did we celebrate on 12 March? Get all the answers and more in our third edition of Space Round Up – your news gateway to space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422090000 +0200" stop="20240422093000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Celebrating the International Space Station</title>
    <desc lang="en">For more than 20 years, ESA astronauts have joined other crew members on board the International Space Station. More than 240 people have lived and worked on the orbital outpost, carrying our essential research to advance our scientific knowledge in space, but also on Earth. In this special programme recorded for the 20th anniversary of the station, join the very first European astronaut on board Umberto Guidoni, together with Tim Peake, Thomas Pesquet and many others, as they reflect on the station’s remarkable achievements. Watch them recall the best moments of their time on board, including filming strikes from thunderstorms on Earth from the ISS cupola or even dressing up for Halloween. Finally, they share their thoughts on what space exploration might look like in the next 20 years. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422093000 +0200" stop="20240422100000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Euclid's first images: the dazzling edge of darkness</title>
    <desc lang="en">One space telescope launched in July 2023. Five stunning images released a couple of months later. In this programme, relive the moment ESA revealed to the world the first images of the Euclid spacecraft. Never before has a telescope been able to create such  full-colour images of the cosmos across such a large patch of the sky. Five images that show that the telescope is ready for its mission to create the most extensive 3D map of the Universe yet and uncover some of its hidden secrets – especially regarding the nature of dark energy and dark matter. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422100000 +0200" stop="20240422113000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Graduation ceremony of ESA’s Class of 2022 Astronauts</title>
    <desc lang="en">ESA astronaut candidates Sophie Adenot, Pablo Álvarez Fernández, Rosemary Coogan, Raphaël Liégeois and Marco Sieber took up duty at the European Astronaut Centre one year ago to be trained to the highest level of standards as specified by the International Space Station partners. After successful completion of basic training, they will be graduate on Monday 22 April. Also concluding a year of astronaut basic training is Australian astronaut candidate Katherine Bennell-Pegg, who has trained alongside ESA’s candidates and will also graduate with the Class of 2022. (Duration 01:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422113000 +0200" stop="20240422114500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Matthias’s launch</title>
    <desc lang="en">…and liftoff! ESA astronaut Matthias Maurer launched into space in November 2021 for a mission called 'Cosmic Kiss'. He flew alongside three NASA astronauts collectively known as “Crew-3”, on board a SpaceX Crew Dragon spacecraft. Watch Matthias’s last moments before launch, his first reaction as he reaches zero gravity, his docking to the ISS and the final hatch opening. Minimal editing, sometimes no sound at all, pure moments: this is Rough Cut. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422114500 +0200" stop="20240422120000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">An astronaut at mission control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Before ESA astronaut Andreas Mogensen launched to the International Space Station for his second mission in space called Huginn, he agreed to come and meet the experts who are flying our satellites and spacecrafts at the European Space Operations Centre (ESOC) in Darmstadt, Germany. Why does an astronaut need to know about the handrails of the International Space Station before every spacewalk? What happens if a spacecraft is on a collision course with a faraway planet? How can sun radiation impact astronauts and…our electricity grids? Andreas’ encounters at ESOC will give you all the answers. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422120000 +0200" stop="20240422121500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Rough Cut: the spacewalk</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mingle with astronauts Thomas Pesquet and Shane Kimbrough as they don their spacesuits and venture outside the ISS for one of the three spacewalks they conducted together in June 2021. The duo worked to install new rollout solar arrays to power the International Space Station. Open the airlock hatch and join them for an out of this world experience. Minimal editing, natural sound: just the heart of the action. This is Rough Cut. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422121500 +0200" stop="20240422124500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Working at ESA</title>
    <desc lang="en">What is it like to work at a space agency? With its 22 Member States and more than 2600 staff members working across Europe in nine different locations, ESA is a unique place to work. Between 2020 and 2030, 44% of the ESA workforce will retire and ESA has been riding a recruitment wave. In this programme, the Human Resources department answers all your questions on working at ESA. Meet also some of ESA’s workforce including Young Graduate Trainees who explain some of the projects they’re involved in and what it’s like to work in space. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422124500 +0200" stop="20240422131500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Dealing with space debris</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the space highways set to become busier, keeping space clean is a top priority. Discover the ESA initiatives to detect and manage debris, including how spacecraft operators steer satellites back into Earth’s atmosphere. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422131500 +0200" stop="20240422141500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Lo spazio in italiano – Space in Italian</title>
    <desc lang="en">Scopri le attività spaziali europee nella tua lingua.Questo programma offre una panoramica su alcune delle attività dell'ESA. Rivedi il rientro a Terra dalla Stazione Spaziale Internazionale dell'astronauta Luca Parmitano lo scorso anno, e scopri la Luna con il nostro amico alieno, Paxi. Visita lo stabilimento italiano del lanciatore Vega e il centro ESA per l'Osservazione della Terra appena fuori Roma. Scopri come il satellite Cheops studia i pianeti distanti, e fai un giro dei servizi igienici della Stazione Spaziale Internazionale con Samantha Cristoforetti. Al termine di questo programma, Luca Parmitano dà un messaggio speciale sul significato del successo. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422141500 +0200" stop="20240422143000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ExoMars - Back on track for the Red Planet</title>
    <desc lang="en">A year has passed since the launch of the rover to the Red Planet was put on hold, and then cancelled, because of events on Earth. But the work has not stopped for the ExoMars teams. In this programme we travel back to Turin, Italy to talk to the teams involved. New tests are being conducted on the rover’s Earth twin, while the real rover remains carefully stored in its ultra-clean room – where ultra-precise procedures remain in place, as our cameraman Francesco finds out once more. The ExoMars Rosalind Franklin mission has now a target launch date of 2028 for the trip to Mars. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422143000 +0200" stop="20240422150000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Return to the Moon: the Artemis journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">More than 50 years after Neil Armstrong set foot on the surface of the Moon, our natural satellite is once again a prime goal of space exploration. Europe has joined USA and other nations to prepare the way for new lunar landings. The Artemis programme aims to establish permanent stations on and around our Moon. Humans will very likely walk again on the Moon in the coming decade – including European astronauts. ESA’s contribution to the Artemis programme is the European Service Module – the module that will provide electricity, water, air for the Orion spacecraft – as well as keeping it at the right temperature and on course. Want to know more about Artemis I, II, III and more? Watch this programme. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422150000 +0200" stop="20240422151500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">The incredible Adventures of the Hera Mission</title>
    <desc lang="en">Suitable for kids and adults alike, the five episodes of this cartoon series tell the story of the Hera mission, due to launch in October 2024. Following the DART mission’s impact with the Dimorphos asteroid last year – modifying its orbit and sending a plume of debris thousands of kilometres out into space – Hera will return to Dimorphos to perform a close-up survey of the crater left by DART. Hera will be Europe and humankind's first investigation of a planetary defence technique aimed at deflecting asteroids and avoid a collision with Earth. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422151500 +0200" stop="20240422154500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Hubble highlights</title>
    <desc lang="en">Revisit some of the NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope’s biggest science discoveries from its three decades in operation. This programme kicks off with an introduction to the ‘Mother of Hubble’ Nancy Roman, then takes us on a tour of some of the telescope’s big finds. Explore how Hubble’s observations will be complemented by those of the upcoming NASA/ESA/CSA James Webb Space Telescope. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422154500 +0200" stop="20240422160000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ISS Lifestyle</title>
    <desc lang="en">What’s it like to live in space? Join astronauts at 400 km high on the International Space Station. From meals to sleeping to cutting hair, ESA astronauts give us an insider’s view of life in space. It’s not all fun and games –conducting experiments on themselves is part of the job! (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422160000 +0200" stop="20240422170000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Leadership at Mission Control</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Head of Mission Operations Paolo Ferri as he takes us through major events in his career at ESA, solving the unexpected problems that are part of any space endeavour.  Paolo describes three missions that suffered unexpected and potentially fatal flaws: Smart-1, Cluster and Exosat, and how on-the-ground knowledge, innovation and ingenuity prevented their untimely demise, allowing the science to go on. Recounting his personal experiences, he illustrates the importance of effective communication, as well as leadership, coaching and learning – and lesson learned while working under pressure. For the full set of Paolo’s master class, see our Videos on Demand. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422170000 +0200" stop="20240422180000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Das Weltall in Ihrer Sprache – Space in German</title>
    <desc lang="en">Entdecken Sie die europäischen Weltraumaktivitäten in deutscher Sprache. Lernen Sie die Mission Cosmic Kiss des deutschen ESA-Astronauten Matthias Maurer kennen. Seine Mission soll im Herbst 2021 mit dem Start zur ISS beginnen. In Zusammenarbeit mit dem Deutsches Zentrum für Luft- und Raumfahrt und der Deutschen Raumfahrtagentur im DLR  können sie mit Alexander Gerst die Geheimnisse der Schwerelosigkeit erkunden. Entdecken Sie außerdem unser Sonnensystem und den Mond mit unserem außerirdischen Freund Paxi, oder finden Sie es heraus wie Europa das Problem des Weltraummülls angeht. (Duration 01:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422180000 +0200" stop="20240422181500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">ROUGH CUT: Samantha in space</title>
    <desc lang="en">Spend some time with Samantha Cristoforetti as she carries out the daily activities of an astronaut on the International Space Station (ISS): floating in space and conducting experiments in zero gravity, even doing some gardening and performing a spacewalk! This summer, Samantha became the first European woman to put a spacesuit on and exit the airlock of the ISS. In this programme, relive the slow and meticulous tasks a spacewalker must carry out including, on this occasion, some works on the European Robotic Arm. Rough Cut is the programme that lets you immerse yourself into key moments, without any commentary nor music. Only natural sounds and often, just the silence of our Universe. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422181500 +0200" stop="20240422184500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Stories from the lab</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Materials and Electrical Components Laboratory at ESA’s ESTEC establishment in the Netherlands supports ESA projects at all stages of development. In this 30-minute programme, discover how experts found solution for a variety of issues from a stuck mobile gantry to Gaia’s failed memory modules. See how ‘beta cloth’ fibre was tested for resilience for the Aeolus mission, and how engineers research how spacecraft material respond to the extreme environment of space over time. The lab is an impartial authority – decades of accumulated experience to back up project teams, equipped to carry out a wide variety of tests in-house, or turn to a network of external facilities when required. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422184500 +0200" stop="20240422191500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">On the hunt for the riskiest asteroid</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a 50-metre asteroid threatens to strike Earth? In the movies, a superhero would probably save humanity at the last minute – but in reality? Enter Rosa Jesse, our Space Safety Editor and the detective in charge of finding out how risky this new asteroid really is. Initial observations showed 2021 QM1 – the asteroid’s official name – had a chance of striking Earth in 2052, but it soon became invisible as the Sun’s glare got in the way of observations and the asteroid moved away from Earth. Rosa investigates and meets the real people in charge of scrutinising our skies: the asteroid hunters from ESA’s Near-Earth Object Coordination Centre. (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422191500 +0200" stop="20240422194500 +0200">
    <title lang="en">MELT</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rising temperatures, melting ice…How will glaciers look over the coming decades? “It all depends on what humans are doing now in terms of greenhouse gas emissions”: this is the message one scientist delivered during an ESA-led expedition to the Gorner Glacier in Switzerland filmed during summer 2021. Put your boots on and join ESA astronaut Luca Parmitano, glaciologists and climate experts on the ice! (Duration 00:30:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422194500 +0200" stop="20240422200000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">A colourful journey through our Universe with James Webb</title>
    <desc lang="en">It is the largest, most powerful telescope ever launched into space: the James Webb Space Telescope! Following Hubble Space Telescope’s footsteps, James Webb is unveiling the secrets of the creation of the Universe and making breakthrough discoveries in multiple fields of astronomy. Have you ever wondered what the early Universe looked like? Would you like to discover new galaxies?  Let’s travel back in time, dive into our origins and look at the striking infrared images of the most distant universe we have ever seen …so far. (Duration 00:15:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
  <programme channel="ESAWebTVOne.int" start="20240422200000 +0200" stop="20240423000000 +0200">
    <title lang="en">Space out</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relax with a selection of dazzling imagery from space. (Duration 04:00:00)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Science &amp; Technology</category>
    <icon src="https://images2.imgbox.com/b3/fa/yGoBOxzK_o.png" />
  </programme>
</tv>

