<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-07-31 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240730233002+0000" stop="20240731002321+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Middle Distance</title>
    <desc lang="en">The stories behind the key moments in middle distance running at the Olympic Games, including stars like Paavo Nurmi and Maria Mutola.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/weswph1l0navqhgryspy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731002321+0000" stop="20240731005442+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault, Treasures of the Olympics | Full Length</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the first time, Historian Greg Jenner and Olympian Jeanette Kwayke are given full access to go behind the scenes of the world’s greatest and most secure sporting collections to uncover the Treasures of the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/eukojzzuifvlt9pxm3pr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731005442+0000" stop="20240731005727+0000">
    <title lang="en">Greg and Jeanette go behind the scenes at the Olympic Museum | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg Jenner and Jeanette Kwayke are left alone one night at the Olympic Museum and get to discover its unique sporting collection. The public space is stretched over 3000 square meters. But they’ve been given the keys of what happens below the galleries. Long corridors and secret rooms where 90.000 items are kept, collated, preserved, and restored.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pnz9wspft7j3miitoqxi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731005727+0000" stop="20240731010312+0000">
    <title lang="en">Derek Redmond makes an incredible donation from Barcelona 1992 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg and Jeanette get to meet Olympic Legend Derek Redmond, one of the most emotional stories in the History the Games. In the best form he’s shown since he broke the British record, Derek is going for a gold or silver medal at Barcelona 1992. But in the semi-final, an injury will decide otherwise. The rest is part of History as his father joins him on the track in a highly emotional finish.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wmvzjzjetnozeu2rwgqw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731010312+0000" stop="20240731023715+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rulon | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">At the 2000 Olympic Games, American wrestler Rulon Gardner beat the unbeatable and became an overnight sensation. But what came after the ‘Miracle on the Mat’ was even more unpredictable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qwzxffsmpbcfufiy08dh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731023715+0000" stop="20240731030619+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Begins</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games fast approaching, three of the best gymnasts in the world gear up for the most important year of their lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dkphy5ybiigyfgbdq9oq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731030619+0000" stop="20240731033424+0000">
    <title lang="en">Competition Season</title>
    <desc lang="en">Morgan and Angelina attempt to handle the pressure of the world stage. Will they succeed? Yile has a point to prove in training.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ppi2us5lcunmzzmlcimc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731033424+0000" stop="20240731040404+0000">
    <title lang="en">The World Championships 2019</title>
    <desc lang="en">The World Championships are here. The three gymnasts learn whether they’re selected for their national teams. All the drama from the biggest competition of the season. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vwvf4yaio4p7hqodtlcg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731040404+0000" stop="20240731044140+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teahupo'o Surf Camp | Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrills and spills as seven surfers join an ISA surf camp at Teahupo'o, Tahiti's famed surf spot and the surfing venue for the Olympic Games Paris 2024. Determined to conquer the Olympic wave, they face their fears, push the boundaries and challenge the raw power of nature.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jgfybidumyctl4uc7lvu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731044140+0000" stop="20240731051455+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731051455+0000" stop="20240731054200+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Boys and B-Girls Take The Spotlight | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">As breaking prepares to make its Olympics debut in Paris 2024, we go inside the lives and regimens of the top breakers in the world leading up to the games. We meet b-boy Victor and b-girl Nicka who have secured Olympic spots, along with Olympic hopeful b-girl Anti still battling her way to the top. They all meet up in Los Angeles for one of the top event of the scene.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fwxkuqavk3lizzafvwh9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731054200+0000" stop="20240731060225+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Family Affair | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head to Pullela Gopichand’s home as the family reflects on how far they have come. Pullela’s daughter Gayatri is put through her paces. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zfpoc7aqhh1lwuzjbr4b"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731060000+0000" stop="20240731065420+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Sprinters</title>
    <desc lang="en">A journey through the essential stories of the Olympic Games, focusing on the sprints in athletics, including Jesse Owens and Carl Lewis.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/a10ssakopgyui2lshtxf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731065420+0000" stop="20240731070314+0000">
    <title lang="en">Michael: No rest on the road to Olympic gold | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Take a look inside Michael Norman’s rigid routine as he prepares to redeem himself with an Olympic gold in the 400m distance at Paris 2024 this summer. While he is visiting his first track and field community, with family and fiancee all behind him, the American sprinter is dedicated to excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/czmk0qtmxfpna25t2i4t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731070314+0000" stop="20240731071157+0000">
    <title lang="en">Phil: breaking barriers to represent his community | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Canadian Breaker Phil ‘Wizard’ Kim, who comes from a traditional Korean family, takes to the streets of Vancouver, where he remembers how he fell in love with breaking and recounts his relentless journey to do what he loves the most : to dance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/v5q27smoc56yyvktpcxx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731071157+0000" stop="20240731072112+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ale: the Mexican diver trying to keep it all in synch | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Alejandra Orozco, two-time Olympic medallist in diving for Mexico, makes her fourth return to the Olympics at Paris 2024. More in sync than ever with her diving partner, Gabriela Agundez, and her family, she takes us back to where it all began: the family farm in the outskirt of Guadaljara. With the support of a loving family, hard work and dedication, she is hoping to reach the pinnacle of her career with Gold this Summer surrounded by her loved ones.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zmfuvbeujwgei666ihwi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731072112+0000" stop="20240731073016+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ni Nengah: a role model and a hero for Indonesia | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">She is Indonesia’s premiere Paralympic powerlifter and the country’s pride. A two-time Paralympic medallist, she is a mentor for the team as she prepares for her next objective: taking gold at Paris 2024 this summer. Although a recent injury puts all her work at risk, she is confident she will rise to the challenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yqud48fm2bapbaqqzjjq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731073016+0000" stop="20240731080716+0000">
    <title lang="en">Victory for Us | The Untold Story of India’s First Surf Team</title>
    <desc lang="en">El Salvador, World Surfing Games 2023, the Indian Surf Team participates for the very first time in an international event chasing their Olympic Qualification. This is the story of that journey, where those kids that once started surfing with broken boards reach an international stage for the first time, where they meet their surfing idols and earn experience for upcoming competitions. Watch it now!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/oabh9q5cjmkxiq0ngoio"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731080716+0000" stop="20240731082129+0000">
    <title lang="en">From NYC to Alaska, meet the pioneers and US champion | Breaking Life </title>
    <desc lang="en">As the birthplace of a global hip-hop movement, we meet some of the pioneers of Breaking in New-York City. While Kid Glyde shares his passion for breaking with the next generation at his Harlem studio, three thousand miles away in Anchorage Alaska, B-Boy Icey Ives, two-time US national champion, melts the ice with his local crew Frozen Flow while being a community leader, a teacher and a role model for the youth living in extremely challenging conditions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dovd8hi3ceymcdhls5v8"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731082129+0000" stop="20240731083755+0000">
    <title lang="en">French breakers set the scene for Paris 2024 Olympic Games| Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">France is a cultural melting pot. It’s also one of the biggest countries for Breaking with more than a thousand battles every year and some of the greatest international competitions. It’s also in Paris 2024 that Breaking will make its Olympic debut.
Dany Dann came to France from French Guyana to pursue a life in dance. Now, he juggles early morning shifts as a nurse, daily training and being a father – always with an eye on the next battle. Now reigning national champion, he trains with French national team members B-Girl Carlota and B-Boy Marlone for the WDSF World Breaking Championship in Paris.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/amx9sswjndootv2aps3j"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731083755+0000" stop="20240731085709+0000">
    <title lang="en">Young breakers take over the streets of Medellin | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">Colombia used to be one of the most dangerous countries in the world but has found new life through a revival in urban arts, becoming a global creative mecca. 
B-Girl Luma and 4Eskuela hip hop school, where she learnt Breaking and is now a teacher, have been instrumental to this change in Medellin (Colombia). But it’s not been an easy journey for Luma who also had her doubts about what she can really achieve through dancing. By winning international dance events around the world, she is now confident it gave her a career and a drive, also when teaching young kids in her neighbourhood. She is keen to participate to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iddfhrgah2b2pkoabbbd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731085709+0000" stop="20240731091402+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s growing breaking scene makes room for B-Girls | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s Breaking scene started in the early 2000’s and has since exploded in popularity. While mostly male dominated, women are increasingly accepted and celebrated in the Indian Breaking scene.
We meet B-Girl Jo, the two-time BC One India champion from Bangalore, as she travels alone to Mumbai. There, she meets her friend Flying Machine who organizes a community celebration event where B-Girls have a chance to battle it out. As a leader for Indian female hip-hop dancers, Jo reflects on her position in the society. With her own hip-hop and yoga studio and inspired by the challenges she’s already had to overcome, she examines her journey with both excitement and wisdom.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/njacmonn1ac4hzxkqjo0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731091402+0000" stop="20240731093028+0000">
    <title lang="en">Dakar breakers see new opportunities with Olympic debut| Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a classical and traditional African dance background, B-Boy Zaza is a key member of Power Crew, one of the most successful crew in Senegal. Joined by his young brother Emma, their crew is more like a family and made them travel to major global events. Now a teacher, tasked with navigating the challenges of his community, the dance gives him hope for a brighter future. With Paris 2024 and Dakar Youth Olympic Games in 2026, the elders and next generation alike to build their own future and for the sport as it takes roots in Senegal. Organized by the local dance federation, they participate in the Battle National, featuring some of Senegal’s best emerging talents. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/udhmfruynxxufbeoi4pc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731093028+0000" stop="20240731093925+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: the long and bumpy road to Olympic gold | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thirteen years after his Olympic debut, the British diver finally landed the gold medal that was missing from his collection.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uiluzuv9rhtucenqzoyr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731093925+0000" stop="20240731094625+0000">
    <title lang="en">Sakura Yosozumi: a skateboarding bloom that blossoms into Olympic gold | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the 19-year-old  Sakura, skateboarding started as a way to play with her brother and ended with the first Olympic gold medal in women's park skateboarding.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sdsjjijo3jqprclchwul"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731094625+0000" stop="20240731095317+0000">
    <title lang="en">Armand Duplantis:  flying high and smashing records | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sweden's Armand "Mondo" Duplantis confirmed his status as the best pole vaulter in the world by seizing his first Olympic pole vault title by storm.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/w5gmtxfnru4kglrubxes"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731095317+0000" stop="20240731100122+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rebeca Andrade: an Olympic fairytale | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian gymnast Rebeca Andrade's long and bleak climb from the favelas of Sao Paulo to the podium in Tokyo is a true Olympic fairytale.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pd2oa3ihqmeogxhwlsog"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731100122+0000" stop="20240731105536+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Cycling</title>
    <desc lang="en">Journey through the exciting Olympic Games glories on the track and road with cycling in its early days through to Chris Hoy and Team GB.

 </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sbnu4dmjo1qgln4tqy1w"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731105536+0000" stop="20240731112526+0000">
    <title lang="en">France’s Tony Estanguet I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of France’s three-time gold medallist Tony Estanguet, who is now leading the Paris 2024 team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b6izxpaomx4gffamxdqu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731112526+0000" stop="20240731115315+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ethiopia’s Derartu Tulu I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of the first black African female gold medallist Derartu Tulu, who is now leading Ethiopia’s national athletics team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qvj58o7hhlsxkfjepxv9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731115315+0000" stop="20240731121605+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Boys and B-Girls Take The Spotlight | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">As breaking prepares to make its Olympics debut in Paris 2024, we go inside the lives and regimens of the top breakers in the world leading up to the games. We meet b-boy Victor and b-girl Nicka who have secured Olympic spots, along with Olympic hopeful b-girl Anti still battling her way to the top. They all meet up in Los Angeles for one of the top event of the scene.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fwxkuqavk3lizzafvwh9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731121605+0000" stop="20240731124057+0000">
    <title lang="en">Nicka takes it to the next level | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">As b-girl Nicka continues her intense preparation for the Games, Anti is about to take on a new opponent at the WDSF Breaking for Gold Series in Hong Kong: Japanese b-girl Ayane, whose brother b-boy Shigekix has already confirmed his spot on Team Japan. The energy in Hong Kong is intense as Ayane tries to make a final push to reach the Olympic Qualifiying Series.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pqvabpybcovdejw3xk2p"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731124057+0000" stop="20240731130413+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayane and Shigekix, a breaking family | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meet London-based b-girl Stefani who dances for Ukraine. Even though Ukraine’s breaking team is scattered across the globe, it doesn't dampen her spirit — she's all about having fun. Stefani faces b-girl Ayane at Hong Kong. Back in Japan, brother and sister breaking duo Shigekix and Ayane started breaking together. Along the last two years of competition, Shigekix is emerging as a favourite for a medal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aernq7xbxjm3lgtsqy3l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731130413+0000" stop="20240731132244+0000">
    <title lang="en">Who will join B-boy Victor for Team USA | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Victor has secured a spot on Team USA. Who else will make it to Paris 2024? Jeffro is training with b-girl Logistix in Colorado Springs for a pre-Olympic festival in Japan. Each of our world class breakers gears up for the Olympic Qualifier Series and then the ultimate challenge: Olympic Games Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gmepych2lmnulrgigzun"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731132244+0000" stop="20240731141713+0000">
    <title lang="en">Becoming an Olympic Legend | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after his famous tally of seven Olympic gold medals and seven world records, legendary swimmer Mark Spitz makes an emotional return to Munich Olympic Park and the swimming pool, where his life was changed forever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fu8b8krwuc98ozzpiroo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731141713+0000" stop="20240731142843+0000">
    <title lang="en">France's Sevens captain targets gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Backed by a great team and high perfornming coaches, Carla's quest for Olympic gold symbolizes the rise of women's rugby since Rio 2016. From competing with boys to leading her nation to Silver in Tokyo 2020, the French rugby Seven squad’s captain inspires resilience and dedication on the road to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wx3cbtavgwlobv8mubju"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731142843+0000" stop="20240731144126+0000">
    <title lang="en">Niklas Kaul - medal contender for Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Despite an incredible 2019 season, winning gold at the World Championships and setting a world’s best record, decathlete Niklas Kaul from Germany faced challenges at Tokyo 2020 due to an injury sustained in the high jump event. After focusing on recovery and preparing for future competitions, he reached an impressive 4th place at the European Championships in Roma, which puts him back in a position to medal at Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/k08y1355m32h27ghmwxj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731144126+0000" stop="20240731145159+0000">
    <title lang="en">Leonardo Fabbri’s success is rooted in family support | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">From his early athletic beginnings to his emotional 22.34m throw, Leonardo's journey is marked by family support and a dream of Olympic success. Despite setbacks, his determination remains unshaken as he aims for glory at Paris 2024. The Tuscan shot putter won gold at the European Championships, setting a championship record and placing him as a serious contender for the coming games. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxqemihgzmjzz9xokxbs"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731145159+0000" stop="20240731150216+0000">
    <title lang="en">Matteo Zurloni Italy’s world champion climbs to the top | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into the remarkable journey of Matteo Zurloni, from small town dreamer to Olympic contender. He won the speed event at the 2023 IFSC Climbing World Championships and earning a shot at Olympic glory. Follow his ascent from humble beginnings to the dizzying heights of international competition, where every climb is a test of skill, courage, and the relentless pursuit of excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sju6a1o423a4twjhziik"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731150216+0000" stop="20240731151428+0000">
    <title lang="en">Norwegian duo are targeting back-to-back Olympic Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reigning World and Olympic Champions Christian Sørum and Anders Mol are dominating beach volleyball. Their partnership, rooted in a Viking mentality, has kept them atop the sport for six years. They are now preparing for a historic back-to-back Olympic gold at Paris 2024 to honour Christian's mother's legacy.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dtt3kmg82b6kunoo91cr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731151428+0000" stop="20240731160749+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Marathon</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best moments from the Olympic Games’ ultimate endurance events with stories from Emil Zatopek and Frank Shorter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dxjn2qu7uybyharsdyfe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731160749+0000" stop="20240731161116+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | John John Florence</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer John John Florence in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o49zaq7clzyfapxm4rkp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731161116+0000" stop="20240731161453+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Tatiana Weston-Webb</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Tatiana Weston-Webb in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iparo4a2kdkieozgsqmy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731161453+0000" stop="20240731161828+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Leonardo Fioravanti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Leonardo Fioravanti in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b0ivgyth6osxesm3ble4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731161828+0000" stop="20240731162233+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Lucca Mesinas</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Lucca Mesinas in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qzxanv6qtxj1ofgg1wdb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731162233+0000" stop="20240731162636+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Teresa Bonvalot</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Teresa Bonvalot in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lh3nbve3ghphl6mrjvk5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731162636+0000" stop="20240731163022+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Shino Matsuda</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Shino Matsuda in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/syrzxzlo7rd8pttd94lf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731163022+0000" stop="20240731163431+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Jordy Smith</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Jordy Smith in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ap7cqzepivid4ymykqcq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731163431+0000" stop="20240731163718+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Griffin Colapinto</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Griffin Colapinto in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/j4fwv1dcrsprk5ap23mg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731163718+0000" stop="20240731164106+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Rio Waida</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Rio Waida in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zijwlnuy0h2k3xoza1cm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731164106+0000" stop="20240731164506+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Brisa Hennessy﻿</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Brisa Hennessy﻿ in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/udrl0f8nveinlr0irxia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731164506+0000" stop="20240731170112+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Family Affair | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head to Pullela Gopichand’s home as the family reflects on how far they have come. Pullela’s daughter Gayatri is put through her paces. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zfpoc7aqhh1lwuzjbr4b"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731170112+0000" stop="20240731171322+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Rise of the Doubles Players | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s doubles players are thriving lately. We hang out with the charismatic men’s team of Satwick and Shetty, and follow Sikki Reddy through rehabilitation.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/izmk6egybas8dl4t5ede"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731171322+0000" stop="20240731172720+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Future of Indian Badminton | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pullela Gopichand looks towards the future with the latest batch of young students at the academy, some of whom rise at 3am to learn to play badminton.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/shrpedfvhf3y40sjm177"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731172720+0000" stop="20240731182043+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Invisible Bond | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">Discover the invisible bond that forges the relationship between an athlete with visual impairment and his guide. This bond transcends the field of play developed by trust, friendship, and the unwavering desire of achieving Paralympic glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkyxtc7pq7xnkemo5yiy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731182043+0000" stop="20240731190559+0000">
    <title lang="en">Running in North Korea | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">A new Original documentary that captures the incredible journey of Aimee Fuller and Mirjam Jaeger as they travel to Pyongyang to participate in the 2019 Mangyongdae Prize International Marathon and meet fellow Olympians from the Democratic People’s Republic of Korea.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qnfzvbwntvw6t2sdaf74"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731190559+0000" stop="20240731195811+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 2 : The Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/oxtlxdyhszwe4fvoseos"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731195811+0000" stop="20240731201638+0000">
    <title lang="en">Manuel: the next big thing in Angola’s favorite sport | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young basketball player from Angola shows us what the sport means to him and dreams of the endelless posibilities the future holds.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ofk3z4p9mfglypjkepr9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731201638+0000" stop="20240731203244+0000">
    <title lang="en">Miyanda: the lioness of Southafica’s BMX scene | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Miyanda Masseti is the highest ranked female BMX rider in Africa, shows us what inspires her to keep pushing and opening new possibilities for future female BMX riders in Africa.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ce6pgaujuftmx9lth3we"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731203244+0000" stop="20240731205127+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ornella: knocking down social prejudices pursuing her Olympic dream | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the first female boxer to represent her country, Ornella shows us why it’s important for the world to see more female African boxers on the global stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dob7vauikkp9fiqjge6t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731205127+0000" stop="20240731214707+0000">
    <title lang="en">Gold Medals Relived | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">US athletic comeback star Dave Wottle, Germany’s celebrated gymnast Karin Janz, acclaimed sprinter Valeriy Borzov, and nine-time Olympic medallist Ludmilla Tourischeva revisit their gold medal journeys during Munich 1972.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q2qupehpqfcq4l36umky"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731214707+0000" stop="20240731220106+0000">
    <title lang="en">Basketball vs Cricket with Akanksha Singh and Jemimah Rodrigues | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can cricketer Jemimah Rodrigues score a free throw shot? What happens when a basketball player attempts to bat in cricket? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ctzws273hfpt7skledzt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731220106+0000" stop="20240731221229+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs Cricket with Pravin Jadhav and Yuzvendra Chahal | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">How hard is it for a cricketer to pull the bow string? What are the skills that an Olympic archer can transfer to his cricket game? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ynssukgleu9u6s6pwjo7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731221229+0000" stop="20240731222350+0000">
    <title lang="en">Badminton vs Cricket with Srikanth Kidambi and Yuzvendra Chahal | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can cricketers play badminton? And what happens when India’s badminton champion Srikanth Kidambi swaps his racket for a cricket bat? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/axll28zcqcxyinsu9msm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731222350+0000" stop="20240731223353+0000">
    <title lang="en">The graceful journey of Olympic champion, Jessica von Bredow-Werndl | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jessica’s dream became reality at Tokyo 2020 with two Olympic Gold medals in dressage in the individual and team event. But her incredible bond with her horse, Dalera, is forged by hard work and an implacable discipline at Aubenhausen world-class riding centre. With her title back on the line at Paris 2024, she opens the doors of her family estate and reflects, with her family and her team, on an emotional journey full of joy and determination.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xu0cyawsztf22bgtsakb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731223353+0000" stop="20240731224103+0000">
    <title lang="en">French kiteboarding prodigee on her way to gold at Paris | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lauriane Nolot, the current world champion, aims for Gold at Paris 2024 on the shores of Marseille where Formula Kite will make its Olympic debut. Hailing from Camps-la-Source, an hour away from the Olympic venue, she climbs the ranks with determination from family get-aways to world podium. Her impressive journey propels her to the pinnacle of her sport, ready to shine on the Olympic stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kkplajzadqmx0pzuhdxn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731224103+0000" stop="20240731225054+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iris Tió is key to Spain’s next gold in Artistic Swimming | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iris Tió Casas joined the senior national team at 15, living away from her parents most of the time. Four years later she competed in Tokyo where she was the youngest on the team. For Paris 2024, she will be crucial to the team’s chances, aiming for gold at Paris 2024. Her journey reflects immense dedication, resilience, and a dream realized through hard work. She will compete in the team as well as in the duet event with her partner Alissa Ozhogina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q1jnizm1gk98xjwmefzr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731225054+0000" stop="20240731230336+0000">
    <title lang="en">Helen Glover eyes Paris 2024 for her fourth Olympics | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">After winning back-to-back gold in London 2012 and Rio 2016, Helen Glover made a remarkable come-back in Tokyo 2020, being the first mother to row for Britain. She and partner Polly Swann finished fourth. Helen now has her sights on Paris 2024 where she should be competing in the Women's four event, focusing on adding another Olympic medal to her impressive career for Team GB.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qnrah2gqd1m9hmhtizsv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731230336+0000" stop="20240731235539+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Aquatics</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best diving, swimming and water polo stories from throughout Olympic history including Dawn Fraser, Greg Louganis and Michael Phelps.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vydzinqyv16sh5trwq8a"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731235539+0000" stop="20240801000313+0000">
    <title lang="en">Jeanette gets to hold Cathy Freeman spikes from Sydney 2000 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">As they continue travelling in time in ‘The Vault’, Jeanette is taken to the Running Shoes Collection. She discovers the oldest spikes from the 19th century and is handed over Cathy Freeman’s shoes from Sydney 2000, when she won Gold in the 400 meters. Patricia, the Collections Manager, explains her how special the colours of those shoes are. Then we get to hear from Cathy herself how special was that night in Sydney for her whole nation. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yokv9gsbu6bxiowzbx7c"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801000313+0000" stop="20240801000916+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘Robin Hood’ caught on camera for the first at Tokyo 2020 | The Vault </title>
    <desc lang="en">Archer specialists say one chance in few thousands but on camera it is the first time ever a ‘Robin Hood’ shot is recorded live! Now on public display, Greg discovers this rare artefact with Stephanie, one of the Museum curators. Shot by the Korean pair, An San and Kim Je-deok in the mixed event, they won Gold in that first-ever event at the Olympics. An san went on winning three Gold medals in Tokyo, demonstrating the dominance of South Korea in this discipline. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zt0pl5oeg7r70znej4eg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801000916+0000" stop="20240801002403+0000">
    <title lang="en">Forging India’s Badminton Champions | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head to the hustle of Hyderabad to meet India’s badminton legend Pullela Gopichand and hear of his champion-building dream. Insights from legends such as Saina Nehwal, Sai Praneeth and Kidambi Srikanth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmvup5pj6r0yeet7vupe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801002403+0000" stop="20240801004156+0000">
    <title lang="en">Youth take Centre Stage | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head behind the scenes and hang out with of some of India’s rising badminton talent.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/m7g04law6ojlfsbbjc8s"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801004156+0000" stop="20240801021341+0000">
    <title lang="en">The People’s Fighters | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">The powerful story of how a revolutionary boxing experiment produced Teofilo Stevenson and a legacy of Cuban success at the Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/n57vgpifgvxtrgl2eg5o"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801021341+0000" stop="20240801024318+0000">
    <title lang="en">It’s Not All Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">The off-season allows a brief break from gymnastics for Angelina. Training intensifies for a fired-up Morgan, while Yile reaches breaking point. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/cxnlm5ovbqqdrxxygvtt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801024318+0000" stop="20240801031325+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Interruption</title>
    <desc lang="en">The COVID-19 pandemic rocks the gymnasts’ schedules. The Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games are heartbreakingly postponed. The three gymnasts remain determined to chase their Olympic dreams. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o3p14hxx8rx4v06ujtrz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801031325+0000" stop="20240801040920+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : The story of the torch</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 3 : The Olympic spirit : The story of the torch.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/d9hqaosoc2lciqdjhidc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801040920+0000" stop="20240801050408+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 2 : The Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/oxtlxdyhszwe4fvoseos"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801050408+0000" stop="20240801060239+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can NBA and Dream Team star Laettner teach this team to win?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team USA and NBA legend Christian Laettner shows the Garinger High School varsity basketball team how they can improve their game.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/isyf33697ado3urpz3i0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801060000+0000" stop="20240801065402+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rise of Women Olympians</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 1 : The story of Women at the Games, Rise of Women Olympians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxcua384ycbgx9v2zjyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801065402+0000" stop="20240801070627+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801070627+0000" stop="20240801071802+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Girl India aims for historic gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow India's remarkable journey from hometown studio of La Hague to the Olympic stage. While she qualified for the Games at the European Championships, with her unique style blending raw energy and finesse, she faces formidable rivals on her quest for breaking glory. Will her unmatched determination and skill make history at the Olympics where the sport is making its debut at Paris 2024?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fgps2zdjfhlhkjt0cnid"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801071802+0000" stop="20240801073205+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kauli Vaast’s Tahitian roots make him a favourite for Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Witness Kauli Vaast's journey from his childhood Tahitian shores to the world stage. Surrounded by his family and long time friend and mentor Jeremy Flores, he refines his craft at Teahupo'o impressive pipe where he will compete on hometurf for an Olympic Gold medal in surfing. Driven by passion and cheered on by those who believe in his dream, he balances the thrill of competition with the warmth of a unique community.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/atn7hr8mywzvlqx35qmf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801073205+0000" stop="20240801074242+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801074242+0000" stop="20240801075418+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801075418+0000" stop="20240801080420+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801080420+0000" stop="20240801081134+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801081134+0000" stop="20240801082148+0000">
    <title lang="en">World Cup winner from Argentinian football dynasty | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a father, uncle and two older brothers all professionals, Alexis Mac Allister was destined for a life in football. All three brothers even achieved their dream of playing on the same team for Argentinos Juniors, which saw young Maradona starts his legendary career and played with their father in the late 70’s. As a very fine member of this Argentinian football dynasty, Mac Allister is aiming to weave his midfield magic at the World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/scynz4fdr9pfdyi28oq1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801082148+0000" stop="20240801083107+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801083107+0000" stop="20240801084205+0000">
    <title lang="en">The New-Zealand striker who made his dreams come true | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">As one of only six kiwis to ever to play in Premier League, Chris Wood has achieved more than he could have ever imagined. Schooled by his football playing sister, Chris moved to England at the age of 15 and made his Premier League debut at 17. After a challenging period of loan moves, Wood met success with Millwall and a personal achievement at London 2012. Now a regular striker at Newcastle United, Wood’s New Zealand has just missed out on World Cup qualification. Arguably the nation’s greatest ever player, he has sights set on another great stage, Paris 2024 where he would be participating in the Olympics for the 3rd time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b60painhtemnajlhqfs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801084205+0000" stop="20240801085014+0000">
    <title lang="en">Talented midfielder Louza sets hope for Paris 2024 | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">The talented midfielder from Watford was desperately unlucky and suffered ligament damage ruling him out of the World Cup selection for Morocco. A product of Nantes F.C. football academy, he joined the UK Premier League as well as debuting and scoring at his first game with the national team. At just 23, he now sets his hopes on Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jpojslmkvpt1kli3bnhd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801085014+0000" stop="20240801090423+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs weightlifting with Shimizu Satoshi &amp; Takao Hiroaki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Olympic boxing bronze medallist snatch 40 kg on his first attempt? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxffrstaqlasgzgnrqtc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801090423+0000" stop="20240801091904+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs race walk with Kanie Miki &amp; Tanii Takayuki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a race walk champion tries to shoot an arrow?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qy9tevadjqoobtb1haoo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801091904+0000" stop="20240801092205+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Japan's 16-year-old sport climbing sensation | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mori Ai started climbing walls when she was eight.  After competing and winning the World Championships, she is focused on being one of the world's top climbers. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iyvfdf4j6tv9v6r0iyyb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801092205+0000" stop="20240801092507+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Japan's table tennis belongs to this 13-year-old prodigy | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Harimoto Miwa's older brother Tomokazu has been the face of Japanese table tennis. Still, he is not the only Harimoto shouldering the hopes of a nation as Miwa is making a name of her own. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlq8b9bzzojdlziqbks1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801092507+0000" stop="20240801092803+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801092803+0000" stop="20240801093051+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093051+0000" stop="20240801093348+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093348+0000" stop="20240801093608+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093608+0000" stop="20240801093801+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093801+0000" stop="20240801094154+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801094154+0000" stop="20240801101138+0000">
    <title lang="en">Netherlands’ Pieter van den Hoogenband (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dutch swimming legend Pieter van den Hoogenband won seven Olympic medals. Now, he’s helping others swim their fastest. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxt20vauetnhtdxbhvn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801101138+0000" stop="20240801103947+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801103947+0000" stop="20240801104406+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801104406+0000" stop="20240801113641+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801113641+0000" stop="20240801114727+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801114727+0000" stop="20240801115720+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801115720+0000" stop="20240801120255+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japan’s historic 4x100m team trades Beijing bronze for reallocated silver</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 2008, the Japanese men’s relay team won their country’s first-ever men’s Olympic medal on the track. But after the first-place Jamaican squad forfeited their gold due to a doping violation, Naoki Tsukahara, Shingo Suetsugu, Shinji Takahira and Nobuharu Asahara moved up to silver.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ms9z8dqi2lp0ldrwexb4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801120255+0000" stop="20240801121059+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801121059+0000" stop="20240801121651+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801121651+0000" stop="20240801122153+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801122153+0000" stop="20240801122651+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801122651+0000" stop="20240801123337+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801123337+0000" stop="20240801124038+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801124038+0000" stop="20240801125405+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801125405+0000" stop="20240801130535+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801130535+0000" stop="20240801131701+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801131701+0000" stop="20240801132916+0000">
    <title lang="en">Lyla Nourtier: you can succeed - France / Weighlifting I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lyla is a 15 year old weightlifter  from a small village in France without much access to sports. We meet her at a turning point in her life as she plans to leave home to pursue her dream. She joins an elite sport and education program where she is the first ever female weightlifter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjzbaetxwitdiurxb4av"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801132916+0000" stop="20240801133828+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can imagining success actually help you achieve it? | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Learn how these visualization techniques practiced by some of the world’s greatest Olympians could help you overcome the challenges in your day to day life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u7lyx1vw3goxwe3xgnto"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801133828+0000" stop="20240801141037+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801141037+0000" stop="20240801141713+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a pioneering Egyptian swimmer broke boundaries and inspired the world</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Golden Fish”, Rania Elwani tells how her determination as an Olympic swimmer was matched only by her commitment to peruse her career as a doctor.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uvbg6uso2jsmt7irbn32"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801141713+0000" stop="20240801142242+0000">
    <title lang="en">How an Olympic champion swimmer almost drowned at London 1948</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Sinking Dream”, Greta Andersen shares how her quest for a second gold was cut short when she blacked. But it didn’t define her career.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/clebcrcrrpzrvirw3vsf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801142242+0000" stop="20240801151611+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic and Arsenal legend save a football team from relegation?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cameroon &amp; Arsenal football legend Lauren coaches a struggling amateur league team from East London. Will he help them avoid relegation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rqfkn2zfzfgwog1hgosj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801151611+0000" stop="20240801161055+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Jackie Silva get this Brazilian volleyball team to defeat their rival?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian Olympic gold medalist Jackie Silva lends her expertise to a Rio indoor volleyball team as they try to win their first event ever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mwcu5tq4upkl1jm6icfc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801161055+0000" stop="20240801170258+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Triathlon, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brothers Alistair and Jonny Brownlee race against the world's best in the 2012 Olympic men's triathlon. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ix1a4g7jedfs5yoeic2m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801170258+0000" stop="20240801171115+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801171115+0000" stop="20240801171629+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801171629+0000" stop="20240801172319+0000">
    <title lang="en">World Cup winner from Argentinian football dynasty | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a father, uncle and two older brothers all professionals, Alexis Mac Allister was destined for a life in football. All three brothers even achieved their dream of playing on the same team for Argentinos Juniors, which saw young Maradona starts his legendary career and played with their father in the late 70’s. As a very fine member of this Argentinian football dynasty, Mac Allister is aiming to weave his midfield magic at the World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/scynz4fdr9pfdyi28oq1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801172319+0000" stop="20240801172913+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801172913+0000" stop="20240801173618+0000">
    <title lang="en">The New-Zealand striker who made his dreams come true | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">As one of only six kiwis to ever to play in Premier League, Chris Wood has achieved more than he could have ever imagined. Schooled by his football playing sister, Chris moved to England at the age of 15 and made his Premier League debut at 17. After a challenging period of loan moves, Wood met success with Millwall and a personal achievement at London 2012. Now a regular striker at Newcastle United, Wood’s New Zealand has just missed out on World Cup qualification. Arguably the nation’s greatest ever player, he has sights set on another great stage, Paris 2024 where he would be participating in the Olympics for the 3rd time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b60painhtemnajlhqfs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801173618+0000" stop="20240801174211+0000">
    <title lang="en">Talented midfielder Louza sets hope for Paris 2024 | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">The talented midfielder from Watford was desperately unlucky and suffered ligament damage ruling him out of the World Cup selection for Morocco. A product of Nantes F.C. football academy, he joined the UK Premier League as well as debuting and scoring at his first game with the national team. At just 23, he now sets his hopes on Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jpojslmkvpt1kli3bnhd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801174211+0000" stop="20240801175409+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs weightlifting with Shimizu Satoshi &amp; Takao Hiroaki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Olympic boxing bronze medallist snatch 40 kg on his first attempt? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxffrstaqlasgzgnrqtc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801175409+0000" stop="20240801180432+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs race walk with Kanie Miki &amp; Tanii Takayuki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a race walk champion tries to shoot an arrow?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qy9tevadjqoobtb1haoo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801180432+0000" stop="20240801180733+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Japan's 16-year-old sport climbing sensation | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mori Ai started climbing walls when she was eight.  After competing and winning the World Championships, she is focused on being one of the world's top climbers. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iyvfdf4j6tv9v6r0iyyb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801180733+0000" stop="20240801181035+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Japan's table tennis belongs to this 13-year-old prodigy | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Harimoto Miwa's older brother Tomokazu has been the face of Japanese table tennis. Still, he is not the only Harimoto shouldering the hopes of a nation as Miwa is making a name of her own. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlq8b9bzzojdlziqbks1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801181035+0000" stop="20240801190258+0000">
    <title lang="en">Speed and grace</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 2 : The story of Women at the Games, Speed and grace.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zzs8tfcep2xnog47vvcj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801190258+0000" stop="20240801190754+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801190754+0000" stop="20240801191042+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801191042+0000" stop="20240801191340+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801191340+0000" stop="20240801191855+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801191855+0000" stop="20240801192411+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801192411+0000" stop="20240801192835+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801192835+0000" stop="20240801195632+0000">
    <title lang="en">Netherlands’ Pieter van den Hoogenband (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dutch swimming legend Pieter van den Hoogenband won seven Olympic medals. Now, he’s helping others swim their fastest. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxt20vauetnhtdxbhvn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801195632+0000" stop="20240801202232+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801202232+0000" stop="20240801203102+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801203102+0000" stop="20240801212237+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801212237+0000" stop="20240801213618+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801213618+0000" stop="20240801215143+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801215143+0000" stop="20240801220127+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japan’s historic 4x100m team trades Beijing bronze for reallocated silver</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 2008, the Japanese men’s relay team won their country’s first-ever men’s Olympic medal on the track. But after the first-place Jamaican squad forfeited their gold due to a doping violation, Naoki Tsukahara, Shingo Suetsugu, Shinji Takahira and Nobuharu Asahara moved up to silver.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ms9z8dqi2lp0ldrwexb4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801220127+0000" stop="20240801221556+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801221556+0000" stop="20240801222448+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801222448+0000" stop="20240801223208+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801223208+0000" stop="20240801223902+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801223902+0000" stop="20240801224615+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801224615+0000" stop="20240801225407+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801225407+0000" stop="20240801230826+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801230826+0000" stop="20240801232239+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801232239+0000" stop="20240801233647+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801233647+0000" stop="20240801235145+0000">
    <title lang="en">Lyla Nourtier: you can succeed - France / Weighlifting I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lyla is a 15 year old weightlifter  from a small village in France without much access to sports. We meet her at a turning point in her life as she plans to leave home to pursue her dream. She joins an elite sport and education program where she is the first ever female weightlifter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjzbaetxwitdiurxb4av"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801235145+0000" stop="20240802000254+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can imagining success actually help you achieve it? | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Learn how these visualization techniques practiced by some of the world’s greatest Olympians could help you overcome the challenges in your day to day life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u7lyx1vw3goxwe3xgnto"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
