<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2025-05-31 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250530232927+0000" stop="20250531012840+0000">
    <title lang="en">ESP v ARG - Men's Preliminaries - Basketball | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This Preliminary Round Game took place on 29/07/2021 at the Saitama Super Arena, Saitama. Final score ESP 81:71 ARG.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uhzrgrylyedatkdt822q"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531012840+0000" stop="20250531035402+0000">
    <title lang="en">Trap Finals - Shooting | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 29/07/2021 at the Asaka Shooting Range, Tokyo. Rehak Stefecekova (SVK) claimed the Gold in the Women's Trap and Liptak (CZE) in the Men's Trap competiton.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/py4idcqxvplwz6cxsgbt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531035402+0000" stop="20250531040228+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531040228+0000" stop="20250531041219+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iris Tió is key to Spain’s next gold in Artistic Swimming | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iris Tió Casas joined the senior national team at 15, living away from her parents most of the time. Four years later she competed in Tokyo where she was the youngest on the team. For Paris 2024, she will be crucial to the team’s chances, aiming for gold at Paris 2024. Her journey reflects immense dedication, resilience, and a dream realized through hard work. She will compete in the team as well as in the duet event with her partner Alissa Ozhogina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q1jnizm1gk98xjwmefzr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531041219+0000" stop="20250531042255+0000">
    <title lang="en">Helen Glover eyes Paris 2024 for her fourth Olympics | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">After winning back-to-back gold in London 2012 and Rio 2016, Helen Glover made a remarkable come-back in Tokyo 2020, being the first mother to row for Britain. She and partner Polly Swann finished fourth. Helen now has her sights on Paris 2024 where she should be competing in the Women's four event, focusing on adding another Olympic medal to her impressive career for Team GB.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qnrah2gqd1m9hmhtizsv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531042255+0000" stop="20250531043204+0000">
    <title lang="en">France's Sevens captain targets gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Backed by a great team and high perfornming coaches, Carla's quest for Olympic gold symbolizes the rise of women's rugby since Rio 2016. From competing with boys to leading her nation to Silver in Tokyo 2020, the French rugby Seven squad’s captain inspires resilience and dedication on the road to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wx3cbtavgwlobv8mubju"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531043204+0000" stop="20250531044234+0000">
    <title lang="en">Niklas Kaul - medal contender for Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Despite an incredible 2019 season, winning gold at the World Championships and setting a world’s best record, decathlete Niklas Kaul from Germany faced challenges at Tokyo 2020 due to an injury sustained in the high jump event. After focusing on recovery and preparing for future competitions, he reached an impressive 4th place at the European Championships in Roma, which puts him back in a position to medal at Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/k08y1355m32h27ghmwxj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531044234+0000" stop="20250531045107+0000">
    <title lang="en">Leonardo Fabbri’s success is rooted in family support | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">From his early athletic beginnings to his emotional 22.34m throw, Leonardo's journey is marked by family support and a dream of Olympic success. Despite setbacks, his determination remains unshaken as he aims for glory at Paris 2024. The Tuscan shot putter won gold at the European Championships, setting a championship record and placing him as a serious contender for the coming games. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxqemihgzmjzz9xokxbs"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531045107+0000" stop="20250531050051+0000">
    <title lang="en">Matteo Zurloni Italy’s world champion climbs to the top | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into the remarkable journey of Matteo Zurloni, from small town dreamer to Olympic contender. He won the speed event at the 2023 IFSC Climbing World Championships and earning a shot at Olympic glory. Follow his ascent from humble beginnings to the dizzying heights of international competition, where every climb is a test of skill, courage, and the relentless pursuit of excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sju6a1o423a4twjhziik"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531050051+0000" stop="20250531051203+0000">
    <title lang="en">Norwegian duo are targeting back-to-back Olympic Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reigning World and Olympic Champions Christian Sørum and Anders Mol are dominating beach volleyball. Their partnership, rooted in a Viking mentality, has kept them atop the sport for six years. They are now preparing for a historic back-to-back Olympic gold at Paris 2024 to honour Christian's mother's legacy.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dtt3kmg82b6kunoo91cr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531051203+0000" stop="20250531060248+0000">
    <title lang="en">Viktoriia: Ukraine’s Gymnastics Hope</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the bombs dropped in her hometown of Kyiv and her father left home to fight in the war, Ukrainian rhythmic gymnast Viktoriia Onopriienko battled daily to make her dream – competing in Paris 2024 – come true. This documentary showcases her grit, resilience and determination in her inspiring journey to compete at the Olympic Games. Discover the indomitable spirit of this young athlete as she prepares to represent Ukraine on the world stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yulo58mhebnhzqdn48mp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531060000+0000" stop="20250531075617+0000">
    <title lang="en">CAN v FRA - Women's Bronze Medal Match | London 2012 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The women's Bronze Medal Match took place on 09/08/2012 at the City of Coventry Stadium, Coventry. Canada claimed the Bronze with a 1:0 win over France</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zw3rl9jvkuhxy39mgggw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531075617+0000" stop="20250531084820+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Football Final, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two great football nations, Brazil and Germany, clashed in an epic gold medal final featuring Neymar against twins Lars and Sven Bender. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kvwla9fb6nnbtvdzw5ay"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531084820+0000" stop="20250531090518+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘We’re the Best Team in New York City’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">City soccer is very special in New-York City and MLK sits at the top, with 19 titles in 25 years. The team is off to a new season and gunning for its 20th title. Coach Jake and assistant Kamani welcome the team for their first practice and super-pro prospect Carlos Lainez is back from Spain. TThey will soon play the top Ohio State team. After a rough start, the team is taking shape but it’s a 16 match competition before the play-offs begin.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jkledz0yuuypaxfwd3xu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531090518+0000" stop="20250531092656+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Guy in the Mirror is Usually the One Stopping You’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Carlos Junior, the team captain and best pro prospect has 13 brothers and sisters, 4 are living with him and his dad in the Bronx. A semi-pro club in Spain offered him a contract but he made the promise to Jake and his MLK family to get them that 20th win. Maynor, also from Honduras, is taking care of his disabled mother. After a shaky start to the season, he comes into his own against Upper West Side rival Beacon.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bqaakxjnat3fcicgvfvj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531092656+0000" stop="20250531115453+0000">
    <title lang="en">BRA v MEX - Men's Gold Medal Match | London 2012 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Gold Medal Match took place on 11/08/2012 at the Wembley Stadium, London. Mexico claimed the Gold with a 2:1 win against Brazil</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/j27e1ibec83p7dote9lc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531115453+0000" stop="20250531140335+0000">
    <title lang="en">AUS v USA - Women's Bronze Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 05/08/2021 at the Ibaraki Kashima Stadium, Kashima. The USA claimed the Bronze with a 4:3 win over Australia</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/h2aeerf8nk3thkjhuiv9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531140335+0000" stop="20250531142212+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘Bacon, Egg and Cheese’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">David Reyes Aka D. Dotty is a burly defender but he is juggling soccer and a burgeoning rap career with the need to help his family earn money in a tough Bronx neighbourhood. He often comes late or tired to the pitch. As the team moves up the rankings, Coach Jake is getting nervous and talks about his past troubles with addiction.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fmh1epkngm7ngg3unml5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531142212+0000" stop="20250531143845+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘This is What We Live For’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">MLK finally enters the playoffs. Three more games separate the team from their goal but their starting goalkeeper is now suspended. Assistant coach Kimani, both the kids’ chief on-field instructor and off-field confidant, manages to keep the team in balance. His patience combined with Jake’s drive are a perfect match. Defender Vakaba, who has come to New York City to fulfil his dream, joins the team and becomes an essential part of its success.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dp63tlka8kzbj8dfsbhk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531143845+0000" stop="20250531145718+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘You Not Really about it’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">MLK high school has been unstoppable this year. They are about to achieve an undefeated season. But Coach Jake is getting increasingly tense. While some players like Charles are doing great both at school and on the team, others like goalkeeper Raymond are struggling to keep their nerves, putting the whole team at risks. Raymond is trying to live up to the dreams and expectations of his father, a talented goalkeeper himself who never made it pro. Soon the team faces a decisive game which will determine the number one seed in the playoffs.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/if7vuj7ifiybsfkhwmuh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531145718+0000" stop="20250531152204+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Only Game that Matter is the Last One’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can we tell a King player from another player just by his look?. A storybook season must end in storybook fashion. But as MLK is leading in semi-final, top player Carlos get a yellow card against their long-time rivals Beacon. Jake's obsession is now turning into superstition as he makes a final call that will soon turn the team fortune. Maynor, who had seemed to struggle in front of the goal since the start of the season, is proving to be a decisive striker.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wcyl9ogeioantt1eg57k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531152204+0000" stop="20250531174003+0000">
    <title lang="en">MEX v JPN - Men's Bronze Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 06/08/2021 at the Saitama Stadium, Saitama. Mexico claimed Bronze with a 3:1 victory against Japan</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/no3avlpdnhnfmo1u0mfx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531174003+0000" stop="20250531183206+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Football Final, Atlanta 1996</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mighty football nation Argentina in an Olympic final against Nigeria hoping to become the first major football champion from Africa. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vnt0fpbnbzdd5ev5rkpm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531183206+0000" stop="20250531220244+0000">
    <title lang="en">BRA v ESP - Men's Gold Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 07/08/2021 at the International Stadium Yokohama, Yokohama. Brazil claimed Gold with a 2:1 victory after extra time against Spain.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uvkmq656qhj30huoiypa"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531220244+0000" stop="20250531235458+0000">
    <title lang="en">KOR v JPN - Men's Bronze Medal Match | London 2012 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Bronze Medal Match took place on 10/08/2012 at the Millenium Stadium, Cardiff. South Korea claimed the Bronze medal with a 2:1 victory over Japan.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nddfczit0hmbbfsmzvw6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531235458+0000" stop="20250531235849+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet coach Matthew Booth</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meet Olympic hero and star coach of the Olympic Channel’s The Z Team, Matthew Booth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ir9jnppizgzeyyinx3pq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250531235849+0000" stop="20250601001533+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic legend turn around Hout Bay's football team?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team South Africa Olympic footballing legend Matthew Booth tries to turn around the fortunes of a struggling local football team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fabhsixoqln5ppcdriye"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601001533+0000" stop="20250601035841+0000">
    <title lang="en">SWE v CAN - Women's Gold Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 06/08/2021 at the olympic Stadium, Tokyo. Canada claimed the Gold with a 3:2 Penatly Shoot-Out win over Sweden</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vax2rzi82lhzldkesxmh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601035841+0000" stop="20250601045302+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Football Final, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two great football nations, Brazil and Germany, clashed in an epic gold medal final featuring Neymar against twins Lars and Sven Bender. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kvwla9fb6nnbtvdzw5ay"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601045302+0000" stop="20250601050115+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rubensson, the offensive midfielder for Sweden | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With 75 Caps for Sweden, Olympic Silver Medallist in Rio 2016 Elin Rubensson is a special talent. Growing up in Mariaholm near Malmö, she joined the national team at 19. She participated in the FIFA World Cup 2015 but it’s only in 2019 that the team reached third place, losing against Netherlands in semi-final. Elin could not participate in Tokyo as she gave birth to a little boy. She is now at her best to help Sweden bring home the world title as well as looking ahead for Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nljtrwdkkktfw1iaszoq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601050115+0000" stop="20250601051040+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kiwi defender who survived it all, ready for World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rebekah Stott, who plays for Brighton &amp; Hove Albion in the English FA Women's Super League, is also a veteran of two Olympics and cancer survivor. She was sidelined by her illness and missed Tokyo 2020 but she is now back stronger than ever on New Zealand’s national team and looking forward to an emotional home World Cup as well as becoming a three-time Olympian next summer in Paris.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kpq2ruarbit90kwnvkxt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601051040+0000" stop="20250601051951+0000">
    <title lang="en">Atletico Madrid's darling is key to Colombia success | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her parents sacrificed everything to give her a chance to achieve her dream of becoming a professional player. From a farming village in the middle of Colombia to being the best number 10 of her country, Leicy Santos’ story is an amazing journey. She left alone to Bogota at 12 and at 15 years old, she was called into the national team. She participated in Rio 2016 Olympics. After winning the first ever professional women’s championship in 2017 with Santa Fe, in 2019, she was the first ever Colombian Player to be signed for a European team, first Colombian player to score in the Champions League and MVP in 2019/20 for Atletico Madrid. She now targets top 3 at FIFA Women’s World Cup 2023. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjnvbb8i31yj4uvkuwix"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601051951+0000" stop="20250601053650+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘We’re the Best Team in New York City’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">City soccer is very special in New-York City and MLK sits at the top, with 19 titles in 25 years. The team is off to a new season and gunning for its 20th title. Coach Jake and assistant Kamani welcome the team for their first practice and super-pro prospect Carlos Lainez is back from Spain. TThey will soon play the top Ohio State team. After a rough start, the team is taking shape but it’s a 16 match competition before the play-offs begin.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jkledz0yuuypaxfwd3xu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601053650+0000" stop="20250601060243+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Guy in the Mirror is Usually the One Stopping You’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Carlos Junior, the team captain and best pro prospect has 13 brothers and sisters, 4 are living with him and his dad in the Bronx. A semi-pro club in Spain offered him a contract but he made the promise to Jake and his MLK family to get them that 20th win. Maynor, also from Honduras, is taking care of his disabled mother. After a shaky start to the season, he comes into his own against Upper West Side rival Beacon.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bqaakxjnat3fcicgvfvj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601060000+0000" stop="20250601082928+0000">
    <title lang="en">USA v JPN - Women's Gold Medal Match | London 2012 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The women's Gold Medal Match took place on 09/08/2012 at the Wembley Stadium, London. The United States claimed the Gold medal with a 2:1 victory over Japan</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/to2mztpnafdfgpikgbs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601082928+0000" stop="20250601092247+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women’s Football Final, Sydney 2000</title>
    <desc lang="en">In its second Olympic appearance, Norway's stars are pitted against the USA, consistently the dominant nation in women’s football.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ztgmjflzygqvkzqwxfcy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601092247+0000" stop="20250601111640+0000">
    <title lang="en">KOR v JPN - Men's Bronze Medal Match | London 2012 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Bronze Medal Match took place on 10/08/2012 at the Millenium Stadium, Cardiff. South Korea claimed the Bronze medal with a 2:1 victory over Japan.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nddfczit0hmbbfsmzvw6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601111640+0000" stop="20250601141020+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Football Final | Rio 2016 | Great Olympic Moments</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relive one of the greatest Olympic Moments and watch as the host Brazil wins the gold medal over Germany in a 5:4 penalty shootout during the men's football final at the Rio Summer Olympic Games in 2016</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p7trmh0hxlwufmcptxsf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601141020+0000" stop="20250601141833+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rubensson, the offensive midfielder for Sweden | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With 75 Caps for Sweden, Olympic Silver Medallist in Rio 2016 Elin Rubensson is a special talent. Growing up in Mariaholm near Malmö, she joined the national team at 19. She participated in the FIFA World Cup 2015 but it’s only in 2019 that the team reached third place, losing against Netherlands in semi-final. Elin could not participate in Tokyo as she gave birth to a little boy. She is now at her best to help Sweden bring home the world title as well as looking ahead for Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nljtrwdkkktfw1iaszoq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601141833+0000" stop="20250601142758+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kiwi defender who survived it all, ready for World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rebekah Stott, who plays for Brighton &amp; Hove Albion in the English FA Women's Super League, is also a veteran of two Olympics and cancer survivor. She was sidelined by her illness and missed Tokyo 2020 but she is now back stronger than ever on New Zealand’s national team and looking forward to an emotional home World Cup as well as becoming a three-time Olympian next summer in Paris.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kpq2ruarbit90kwnvkxt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601142758+0000" stop="20250601143709+0000">
    <title lang="en">Atletico Madrid's darling is key to Colombia success | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her parents sacrificed everything to give her a chance to achieve her dream of becoming a professional player. From a farming village in the middle of Colombia to being the best number 10 of her country, Leicy Santos’ story is an amazing journey. She left alone to Bogota at 12 and at 15 years old, she was called into the national team. She participated in Rio 2016 Olympics. After winning the first ever professional women’s championship in 2017 with Santa Fe, in 2019, she was the first ever Colombian Player to be signed for a European team, first Colombian player to score in the Champions League and MVP in 2019/20 for Atletico Madrid. She now targets top 3 at FIFA Women’s World Cup 2023. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjnvbb8i31yj4uvkuwix"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601143709+0000" stop="20250601144608+0000">
    <title lang="en">Brighton keeper from Australia in fourth World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lydia Williams grew up in an Aboriginal community in the middle of Western Australia. At 11, she moved to Canberra. Her mum who was from the US signed her up for football. The local club that she joined only had one position left in division one: goalkeeper. She lost her father at 15 and put all her efforts into football. She was 16 when she made her debut for Australia and 19 at her first World Cup. Rio 2016 Olympics was a special moment for her since Cathy Freeman had always inspired her. Having competed in three world cups and two Olympic Games, she has now reached 100 caps, no doubt that this home competition will be very special for her.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/l91wpakmc9ikzma1igzj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601144608+0000" stop="20250601145325+0000">
    <title lang="en">Brand leads a new generation of players for Germany | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jule Brand is a fast, skillful and versatile midfielder for VfL Wolfsburg who is ready to shine at FIFA Women’s World Cup 2023. She is one of the best young talents in Germany and has the potential to become one of the best in the world.She played football on boys’ team from an early age until she signed for Hoffenheim at 16 years old. She was 14 when the German team won Gold at Rio 2016 Olympics and it inspired her to pursue a professional career. She scored on her first appearance in the national team in 2021 and was selected for Euro 2022 and really made her name on the international stage. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ncyghsnrqwvxwct00ujm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601145325+0000" stop="20250601150115+0000">
    <title lang="en">Zambia sensation ready to strike at World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Barbra Banda, Zambia’s national team striker, made Olympic history at Tokyo 2020, being the first player — man or woman — to score three goals in back-to-back games. She is probably the greatest football talent in the country, inspiring a whole generation of young women. She began playing on the streets of Lusaka where it was taboo for women to play football. She ended up joining one of the biggest clubs, the Green Buffaloes, before being the first player in Zambia to play in Europe followed by Super League club Shanghai Shengli where she is the top scorer. She is now ready to lead her nation in their first ever World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fk8o7efvwzzxklcpnefi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601150115+0000" stop="20250601184939+0000">
    <title lang="en">SWE v CAN - Women's Gold Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 06/08/2021 at the olympic Stadium, Tokyo. Canada claimed the Gold with a 3:2 Penatly Shoot-Out win over Sweden</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vax2rzi82lhzldkesxmh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601184939+0000" stop="20250601222214+0000">
    <title lang="en">BRA v ESP - Men's Gold Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 07/08/2021 at the International Stadium Yokohama, Yokohama. Brazil claimed Gold with a 2:1 victory after extra time against Spain.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uvkmq656qhj30huoiypa"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601222214+0000" stop="20250601222804+0000">
    <title lang="en">Manchester City midfielder to repeat Japan success | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yui Hasegawa is amazing on the ball. An amazing dribbler. One of the best technical players in the world and she is just starting her journey. Hasegawa came through the ranks at Nippon TV Beleza, a team she joined in 2009 as a 12-year-old, gradually progressing to the first team. She amassed over 100 appearances for the senior side of Nippon TV Beleza between 2013 &amp; 2019. Her goal was to be established in Japan first. Milan came with an offer. This was the perfect starting going to Europe. She fulfilled one of her dreams playing at Tokyo 2020 Olympics. She now sees the World Cup as an opportunity to repeat Japan’s 2011 title. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/snuorr90rk2iuo5ysp98"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601222804+0000" stop="20250601223542+0000">
    <title lang="en">Haiti prodigy qualifies her team to first World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Melchie Dumornay is one of the most promising talents in world football. She is taking the French league by storm scoring 22 goals in 38 appearances. Her two goals for Haiti have made history, qualifying the team for their first-ever Women’s World Cup. At 15, she was already playing in the Haitian 1st division and became the league’s top scorer. Reaching U20 national team, 50 clubs wanted Dumornay, clubs in Asia, Europe, US. But Durmonay would choose Reims in the French league. A club renowned for its ability to nurture and develop young talents while offering them the chance to compete in one of Europe’s top leagues. No one was expecting “les Grenadières” to qualify for the World Cup, so who knows what can happen. Melchie hopes that the team will continue to develop and one day be part of the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ya4rrfpmdsgto1g6mkfj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601223542+0000" stop="20250601224228+0000">
    <title lang="en">French top scorer is back on the team to win title | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Eugenie Le Sommer is now back on national team with new coach Herve Renard, who made sensation with Saudi Arabia at FIFA Men’s World Cup. She is national team top scorer with 88 goals. With her club, Olympique Lyonnais, she has won 29 titles including 8 Champions Leagues but no major title with the French national team yet. After missing out Euro 2022, she is now back on the team and optimistic France is a favourite to win the world title at FIFA World Cup 2023. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ygbvvmw4rrl5bntljxud"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601224228+0000" stop="20250601225103+0000">
    <title lang="en">Geyse, Brazil’s shooting star | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ferreira is a powerful striker who lives to score goals, as reflected by her incredible stats. She can shoot with both feet and few defenders are able to match her phenomenal speed. She is the youngest of a family of six siblings. Spotted by a sport teacher as she was playing on the beach, she would take a 4-hour bus to get to training and back until she was called on U20 national team. She signed for Benfica in 2017 ended up with 49 goals in only 30 games. After 56 appearances and 30 goals in 2 seasons at Madrid CFF, she joined Barcelona in 2022. Tokyo 2020 is the highlight of her international career so far but she is ready to give it all for the Seleção at FIFA Women’s World Cup 2023. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixefhcrdskjnfjxfvbii"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601225103+0000" stop="20250601230052+0000">
    <title lang="en">US Captain determined to give it all to defend title | World at their Feet </title>
    <desc lang="en">Lindsey Horan is one of the first US players to have joined a European club as she decided to skip college and become professional at 18 when joining PSG. The normal path for any US footballer was College and then playing for one of the US teams. She overcame tough times and by the end of her time in PSG she had scored 46 goals in 58 appearances. She left Europe for Portland to achieve her dream of playing at the Olympics in Rio 2016. Winning the 2019 World Cup with the team was definitely a key moment but she sees her Bronze medal in Tokyo 2020 as the highlight of her international career so far.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/f8d8jphcq15loq2oyxhj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250601230052+0000" stop="20250602010902+0000">
    <title lang="en">AUS v USA - Women's Bronze Medal Match - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 05/08/2021 at the Ibaraki Kashima Stadium, Kashima. The USA claimed the Bronze with a 4:3 win over Australia</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/h2aeerf8nk3thkjhuiv9"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
