<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-08-08 00:00:02">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240807232105+0000" stop="20240808001505+0000">
    <title lang="en">Speed and grace</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 2 : The story of Women at the Games, Speed and grace.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zzs8tfcep2xnog47vvcj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808001505+0000" stop="20240808001802+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808001802+0000" stop="20240808002050+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808002050+0000" stop="20240808002347+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808002347+0000" stop="20240808002607+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808002607+0000" stop="20240808002800+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808002800+0000" stop="20240808002948+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808002948+0000" stop="20240808005547+0000">
    <title lang="en">Netherlands’ Pieter van den Hoogenband (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dutch swimming legend Pieter van den Hoogenband won seven Olympic medals. Now, he’s helping others swim their fastest. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxt20vauetnhtdxbhvn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808005547+0000" stop="20240808012500+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808012500+0000" stop="20240808012919+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808012919+0000" stop="20240808022400+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808022400+0000" stop="20240808023447+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808023447+0000" stop="20240808024439+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808024439+0000" stop="20240808025243+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808025243+0000" stop="20240808025835+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808025835+0000" stop="20240808030337+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808030337+0000" stop="20240808030835+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808030835+0000" stop="20240808031336+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808031336+0000" stop="20240808032143+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808032143+0000" stop="20240808033314+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808033314+0000" stop="20240808034444+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808034444+0000" stop="20240808035610+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808035610+0000" stop="20240808041334+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mariah: A Boxer’s Dream | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">16-year-old Navajo boxer Mariah Bahe is fighting against all odds to become the first female Native American Olympic boxer.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/adq0dixjiqcurvfd9flg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808041334+0000" stop="20240808043937+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s Abhinav Bindra I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of India’s first-ever individual gold medallist, Abhinav Bindra, and how he is now helping others fulfil their dreams.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jvq4mokfj4krqfodpabl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808043937+0000" stop="20240808050517+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Boys and B-Girls Take The Spotlight | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">As breaking prepares to make its Olympics debut in Paris 2024, we go inside the lives and regimens of the top breakers in the world leading up to the games. We meet b-boy Victor and b-girl Nicka who have secured Olympic spots, along with Olympic hopeful b-girl Anti still battling her way to the top. They all meet up in Los Angeles for one of the top event of the scene.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fwxkuqavk3lizzafvwh9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808050517+0000" stop="20240808060233+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Cycling</title>
    <desc lang="en">Journey through the exciting Olympic Games glories on the track and road with cycling in its early days through to Chris Hoy and Team GB.

 </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sbnu4dmjo1qgln4tqy1w"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808060000+0000" stop="20240808065215+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Golf Individual Stroke Play, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Golf's return to the Olympic Games after more than a century is marked by a dramatic contest that is only decided on the 18th hole. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sijui0wbubhikig0milf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808065215+0000" stop="20240808070957+0000">
    <title lang="en">Table Tennis vs Cricket with Sharath Kamal and Harbhajan Singh | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can bowler Harbhajan Singh make use of his spinning skills in table tennis? What happens when a table tennis champion becomes a cricket bowler? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c4zwpcdwf2owihv6a6wu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808070957+0000" stop="20240808072136+0000">
    <title lang="en">Shooting vs Cricket with Manu Bhaker and Smriti Mandhana | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens in the battle of precision between cricket and shooting? The challenge is on, as Smriti Mandhana and Manu Bhaker swap the pistols and bats. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pxn7nrwwg05zmutrvbkf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808072136+0000" stop="20240808073337+0000">
    <title lang="en">Hockey vs Cricket with Savita Punia and Smriti Mandhana | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s national hockey team goalkeeper Savita Punia swaps her hockey stick for a cricket bat. Can her skills in hockey help her become a better cricketer? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kxcq88bkf4lboaxwjgsi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808073337+0000" stop="20240808074357+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808074357+0000" stop="20240808075320+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Girl India aims for historic gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow India's remarkable journey from hometown studio of La Hague to the Olympic stage. While she qualified for the Games at the European Championships, with her unique style blending raw energy and finesse, she faces formidable rivals on her quest for breaking glory. Will her unmatched determination and skill make history at the Olympics where the sport is making its debut at Paris 2024?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fgps2zdjfhlhkjt0cnid"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808075320+0000" stop="20240808080113+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kauli Vaast’s Tahitian roots make him a favourite for Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Witness Kauli Vaast's journey from his childhood Tahitian shores to the world stage. Surrounded by his family and long time friend and mentor Jeremy Flores, he refines his craft at Teahupo'o impressive pipe where he will compete on hometurf for an Olympic Gold medal in surfing. Driven by passion and cheered on by those who believe in his dream, he balances the thrill of competition with the warmth of a unique community.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/atn7hr8mywzvlqx35qmf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808080113+0000" stop="20240808081437+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808081437+0000" stop="20240808082303+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808082303+0000" stop="20240808091506+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Middle Distance</title>
    <desc lang="en">The stories behind the key moments in middle distance running at the Olympic Games, including stars like Paavo Nurmi and Maria Mutola.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/weswph1l0navqhgryspy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808091506+0000" stop="20240808094506+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault, Treasures of the Olympics | Full Length</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the first time, Historian Greg Jenner and Olympian Jeanette Kwayke are given full access to go behind the scenes of the world’s greatest and most secure sporting collections to uncover the Treasures of the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/eukojzzuifvlt9pxm3pr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808094506+0000" stop="20240808094751+0000">
    <title lang="en">Greg and Jeanette go behind the scenes at the Olympic Museum | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg Jenner and Jeanette Kwayke are left alone one night at the Olympic Museum and get to discover its unique sporting collection. The public space is stretched over 3000 square meters. But they’ve been given the keys of what happens below the galleries. Long corridors and secret rooms where 90.000 items are kept, collated, preserved, and restored.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pnz9wspft7j3miitoqxi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808094751+0000" stop="20240808095336+0000">
    <title lang="en">Derek Redmond makes an incredible donation from Barcelona 1992 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg and Jeanette get to meet Olympic Legend Derek Redmond, one of the most emotional stories in the History the Games. In the best form he’s shown since he broke the British record, Derek is going for a gold or silver medal at Barcelona 1992. But in the semi-final, an injury will decide otherwise. The rest is part of History as his father joins him on the track in a highly emotional finish.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wmvzjzjetnozeu2rwgqw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808095336+0000" stop="20240808112620+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rulon | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">At the 2000 Olympic Games, American wrestler Rulon Gardner beat the unbeatable and became an overnight sensation. But what came after the ‘Miracle on the Mat’ was even more unpredictable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qwzxffsmpbcfufiy08dh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808112620+0000" stop="20240808115310+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Begins</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games fast approaching, three of the best gymnasts in the world gear up for the most important year of their lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dkphy5ybiigyfgbdq9oq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808115310+0000" stop="20240808121959+0000">
    <title lang="en">Competition Season</title>
    <desc lang="en">Morgan and Angelina attempt to handle the pressure of the world stage. Will they succeed? Yile has a point to prove in training.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ppi2us5lcunmzzmlcimc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808121959+0000" stop="20240808124904+0000">
    <title lang="en">The World Championships 2019</title>
    <desc lang="en">The World Championships are here. The three gymnasts learn whether they’re selected for their national teams. All the drama from the biggest competition of the season. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vwvf4yaio4p7hqodtlcg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808124904+0000" stop="20240808132641+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teahupo'o Surf Camp | Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrills and spills as seven surfers join an ISA surf camp at Teahupo'o, Tahiti's famed surf spot and the surfing venue for the Olympic Games Paris 2024. Determined to conquer the Olympic wave, they face their fears, push the boundaries and challenge the raw power of nature.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jgfybidumyctl4uc7lvu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808132641+0000" stop="20240808142217+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Olympic Series: The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 4 : The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nsou8dw7a1xyj4omjz1v"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808142217+0000" stop="20240808143055+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ezra: A high-jumper finds community and another chance | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">As high-jump reigning World Champion, Ezra Frech prepares to return to the Paralympics for the second time. He reflects on his remarkable journey with his father and together with his mother, he takes us to meet their wider and beloved Californian community as they organize a unique event for adaptative sports in Los Angeles.    </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/glkk5ayzlsowdw4hqp5r"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808143055+0000" stop="20240808144010+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ferdinand: The Beast from the East returns to his roots | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Known as the ‘Fastest Man in Africa’ for his prowess in the 100m, Ferdinand Omanyala is setting his sights on becoming the fastest man in the world at Paris 2024. We follow him as he travels back to his hometown of Kitale in Kenya to get the blessings he needs from his peers and uncover the remarkable story of his origins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/n0xacw0mcphquast8plp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808144010+0000" stop="20240808144910+0000">
    <title lang="en">Nikoloz: The judo World Champion from two nations | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Nikoloz Sherazadishvili’s family moved him from Georgia to Spain at a young age, his father instilled a love of judo in him. He quickly felt at home at the local club of Brunete, in the outskirt of Madrid, where everything started with his first coach Quino Ruiz. As he gears up for his second Olympics, surrounded by his family and friends, he’s competing on the mat for Spain but also holding Georgia and the memory of his father close to his heart.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/odhgywsetbejzoilsrvd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808144910+0000" stop="20240808145717+0000">
    <title lang="en">Carlota: Proving herself and her sport to the world | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young female breaker for France, Carlota Dudek is training to qualify for the Olympics to showcase her unique style to the world, inherited from her mother Cuban origin. We travel with her from Paris to her hometown in the heart of Provence where her life-long dance journey began.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dkdz4nhhsilyl5ybnuuk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808145717+0000" stop="20240808155034+0000">
    <title lang="en">Triumph and Tragedy | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an emotional journey with his son and grandson, Finland’s Lasse Virén revisits the spot where he rose to his feet after a dramatic fall to win gold. The next day, the spirit of Munich was shattered when a terror attack at the Olympic Village took the lives of 11 Israeli athletes and coaches – a day of tragedy as told by an Israeli survivor, Shaul Ladany, and the gold medallists from around the world who bore witness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ishr6vmaunsc38joibk6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808155034+0000" stop="20240808155748+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ginter is the defensive rock for Germany at World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">He was the youngest player in the Germany squad which went on to win the World Cup in 2014. Silver medallist at Rio 2016 Olympic Games, he played for Borussia Dortmund and Borussia Mönchengladbach before moving back to his hometown club of SC Freiburg. But behind a very friendly and family man, he is the defensive rock to take Germany to a new glory in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/roelsvrejxtmaoug58h0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808155748+0000" stop="20240808160455+0000">
    <title lang="en">David Raum is the new Mannschaft’s shooting star | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Written off and sent to play in the second Bundesliga in Germany, Raum helped to propel his club to first division. After joining the national team at Tokyo 2020, he made a meteoric rise to RB Leipzig. He is now part of the senior national team and ready to shatter his opponents’ defense at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/epevots1k6i7aw1lrlc4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808160455+0000" stop="20240808161355+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kouyaté's fearless road to World Cup is a life lesson | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cheikhou Kouyaté left Senegal as a teenager to begin his football journey at F.C. Brussels. London 2012 was instrumental to his integration in the national team, followed by solid moves to West Ham United and Crystal Palace. His last years success at African Cup of Nations propelled him to the next level at Nottingham Forest. He is now gearing up with the Lions for the World Cup hoping to make history.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qo7ivzqvwhcvh4ckhvxw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808161355+0000" stop="20240808161939+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s number one keeper ready to shine at World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Establishing yourself as the number one keeper for Spain is no easy feat but thats what Unai Simón has been doing for two years now. As he recovered from his mistake at UEFA Euro 2020, he went on to win a silver medal at Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games. He is now aiming to earn a new title with the Spanish team at the World Cup 2022 in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bwiiibbus2tu3lcbmqvd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808161939+0000" stop="20240808162547+0000">
    <title lang="en">Bednarek leads a new generation of players for Poland | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jan Bednarek is a strong and skillful centre back who now plays for Aston Villa. He was raised in a family obsessed with football, including his brother Filip, who plays professionally as a goalkeeper in their home country. Poland’s last success in an international tournament was winning Silver at the Barcelona 1992 Olympic Games but a new generation of players is ready to take the 2022 World Cup by storm. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sxxilaklylefxgj3hqhk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808162547+0000" stop="20240808163309+0000">
    <title lang="en">Elaine Thompson-Herah: One sprint to rule them all | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">How Elaine Thompson-Herah became the undisputed sprinting queen and the first woman to win the 100-200m double gold at consecutive Olympics. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qdby3yncfcftbkyozw3g"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808163309+0000" stop="20240808163913+0000">
    <title lang="en">Neeraj Chopra: Throws his way into a nation's heart | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Neeraj Chopra makes Olympic history with the first-ever Olympic gold medal in track-and-field for India.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ykmpivgc38aypmepxgkr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808163913+0000" stop="20240808164603+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ariarne Titmus: Splashing into swimming royalty | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">How Ariarne Titmus went from chasing gold to being the one to beat after nail bitter 200m and 400m freestyle victories in Tokyo2020</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ah0nyrk1wk9y8i9rk663"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808164603+0000" stop="20240808165317+0000">
    <title lang="en">Carissa Moore: Carrying surfers' aloha spirit to the top of the podium | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">How native Hawaiian Carissa Moore, honoured generations of surfers by winning the sport's first Olympic gold medal. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hhjod91kr6o9vvd33vio"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808165317+0000" stop="20240808174827+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Gymnastics</title>
    <desc lang="en">Glorious gymnastics moments spanning the history of the Olympic Games, including Olga Korbut, Nadia Comaneci and Yukio Endo.
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zhv3fy9vle8wby95tagn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808174827+0000" stop="20240808181430+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s Abhinav Bindra I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of India’s first-ever individual gold medallist, Abhinav Bindra, and how he is now helping others fulfil their dreams.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jvq4mokfj4krqfodpabl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808181430+0000" stop="20240808184214+0000">
    <title lang="en">United States’ Natalie Coughlin I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of twelve-time medallist, Natalie Coughlin, and what she is doing now.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/l6jswjaygevyr7yfuyck"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808184214+0000" stop="20240808190842+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japan’s Nomura Tadahiro I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of Japan’s three-time gold medallist Nomura Tadahiro, and what he is doing now.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wrjayuolzgvxu7qk3kec"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808190842+0000" stop="20240808200701+0000">
    <title lang="en">Nuffin for Nuffin | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">Forty-five years after their first and only Olympic medal, Bermuda's hopes of glory now rest on the shoulders of a new generation of boxers. See how these young boxers overcome adversity and struggle beyond the ropes to keep this tiny island nation's Olympic dreams alive.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/t9vrzq7ddwpt7dyaegcs"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808200701+0000" stop="20240808205911+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Olympic spirit : Greek gift, the ancient games</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 1 : The Olympic spirit : Greek gift, the ancient games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vthkhgivtxusjbpp3nhj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808205911+0000" stop="20240808211650+0000">
    <title lang="en">Khalifa: An Olympic dream in the heart of Africa’s football powerhouse | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young Ghanian football player takes us into his world. Through his community, family and team we learn why football is so important to him and what he hopes to accomplish one day.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vgqzngvj1o4cwr6mqjs6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808211650+0000" stop="20240808213241+0000">
    <title lang="en">Aya: the first female swimmer to represent Gabon at the Olympics | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">An Olympic swimmer overcomes her tragic past and is determined to keep swimming. We see the inspiring relationship she has with her father as they train for future competitions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ln7ihg4fero3yvf6n1ia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808213241+0000" stop="20240808214951+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayomide: Born in a canoe, now a Nigerian rowing star | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her mother gave birth to her inside a canoe some 20 years ago. Ayomide Bello grew up to become the first female canoeist from Nigeria to qualify for the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hvr9skjd78d5ohz9hody"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808214951+0000" stop="20240808224134+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Dutch hockey legend Ellen Hoog help a team who doesn’t score win?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three-time Olympic medalist Ellen Hoog tries to restore winning ways for a U19 girls hockey team in the Netherlands.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lzhihdlidj98geankcez"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808224134+0000" stop="20240808233332+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can USA's rugby coach Mike Friday transform India’s U17 female rugby team?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team USA coach Mike Friday travels to Mumbai to train the Indian U17 Rugby 7's women's side, aiming to qualify for the Youth Olympics. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xsthuzyub8b7sx88gqxv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240808233332+0000" stop="20240809002541+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can this Finnish Olympic ice hockey legend change a Chinese team’s fortune?</title>
    <desc lang="en">See how 1988 Olympic silver medalist Rexi Ruotsalainen imparts his knowledge and expertise on the Huijia Green Dragons of Beijing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/djwdzjukr6slwbdrcjpj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809002541+0000" stop="20240809012037+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Dutch hockey legend Ellen Hoog help a team who doesn’t score win?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three-time Olympic medalist Ellen Hoog tries to restore winning ways for a U19 girls hockey team in the Netherlands.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lzhihdlidj98geankcez"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809012037+0000" stop="20240809021437+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can USA's rugby coach Mike Friday transform India’s U17 female rugby team?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team USA coach Mike Friday travels to Mumbai to train the Indian U17 Rugby 7's women's side, aiming to qualify for the Youth Olympics. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xsthuzyub8b7sx88gqxv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809021437+0000" stop="20240809030909+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can this Finnish Olympic ice hockey legend change a Chinese team’s fortune?</title>
    <desc lang="en">See how 1988 Olympic silver medalist Rexi Ruotsalainen imparts his knowledge and expertise on the Huijia Green Dragons of Beijing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/djwdzjukr6slwbdrcjpj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809030909+0000" stop="20240809040112+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Basketball Final, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the closest finish in 40 years, the USA played Spain for the men's basketball gold medal, in a thrilling rematch. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxghggiuz8etqdt6y6lb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809040112+0000" stop="20240809041841+0000">
    <title lang="en">Khalifa: An Olympic dream in the heart of Africa’s football powerhouse | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young Ghanian football player takes us into his world. Through his community, family and team we learn why football is so important to him and what he hopes to accomplish one day.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vgqzngvj1o4cwr6mqjs6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809041841+0000" stop="20240809043433+0000">
    <title lang="en">Aya: the first female swimmer to represent Gabon at the Olympics | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">An Olympic swimmer overcomes her tragic past and is determined to keep swimming. We see the inspiring relationship she has with her father as they train for future competitions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ln7ihg4fero3yvf6n1ia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809043433+0000" stop="20240809045132+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayomide: Born in a canoe, now a Nigerian rowing star | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her mother gave birth to her inside a canoe some 20 years ago. Ayomide Bello grew up to become the first female canoeist from Nigeria to qualify for the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hvr9skjd78d5ohz9hody"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809045132+0000" stop="20240809054529+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809054529+0000" stop="20240809060255+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs Cricket with Vikas Krishan Yadav and Harbhajan Singh | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can a boxer bat? And does a bowler have the power and precision to throw a punch? India’s cricket legend Harbhajan Singh swaps sports for one day with boxing champion Vikas Krishan Yadav.    </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bsdt80yxg811liiyb6zt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809060000+0000" stop="20240809065524+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Marathon, Atlanta 1996</title>
    <desc lang="en">Atlanta's marathon proved to be historic not only due to its unlikely champion, but also thanks to the narrowest winning Olympic margin. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/i86exgspgp1yh1twa9d4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809065524+0000" stop="20240809082445+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rulon | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">At the 2000 Olympic Games, American wrestler Rulon Gardner beat the unbeatable and became an overnight sensation. But what came after the ‘Miracle on the Mat’ was even more unpredictable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qwzxffsmpbcfufiy08dh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809082445+0000" stop="20240809083606+0000">
    <title lang="en">Badminton vs Cricket with Srikanth Kidambi and Yuzvendra Chahal | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can cricketers play badminton? And what happens when India’s badminton champion Srikanth Kidambi swaps his racket for a cricket bat? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/axll28zcqcxyinsu9msm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809083606+0000" stop="20240809084608+0000">
    <title lang="en">The graceful journey of Olympic champion, Jessica von Bredow-Werndl | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jessica’s dream became reality at Tokyo 2020 with two Olympic Gold medals in dressage in the individual and team event. But her incredible bond with her horse, Dalera, is forged by hard work and an implacable discipline at Aubenhausen world-class riding centre. With her title back on the line at Paris 2024, she opens the doors of her family estate and reflects, with her family and her team, on an emotional journey full of joy and determination.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xu0cyawsztf22bgtsakb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809084608+0000" stop="20240809085650+0000">
    <title lang="en">French kiteboarding prodigee on her way to gold at Paris | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lauriane Nolot, the current world champion, aims for Gold at Paris 2024 on the shores of Marseille where Formula Kite will make its Olympic debut. Hailing from Camps-la-Source, an hour away from the Olympic venue, she climbs the ranks with determination from family get-aways to world podium. Her impressive journey propels her to the pinnacle of her sport, ready to shine on the Olympic stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kkplajzadqmx0pzuhdxn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809085650+0000" stop="20240809090642+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iris Tió is key to Spain’s next gold in Artistic Swimming | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iris Tió Casas joined the senior national team at 15, living away from her parents most of the time. Four years later she competed in Tokyo where she was the youngest on the team. For Paris 2024, she will be crucial to the team’s chances, aiming for gold at Paris 2024. Her journey reflects immense dedication, resilience, and a dream realized through hard work. She will compete in the team as well as in the duet event with her partner Alissa Ozhogina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q1jnizm1gk98xjwmefzr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809090642+0000" stop="20240809092053+0000">
    <title lang="en">Helen Glover eyes Paris 2024 for her fourth Olympics | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">After winning back-to-back gold in London 2012 and Rio 2016, Helen Glover made a remarkable come-back in Tokyo 2020, being the first mother to row for Britain. She and partner Polly Swann finished fourth. Helen now has her sights on Paris 2024 where she should be competing in the Women's four event, focusing on adding another Olympic medal to her impressive career for Team GB.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qnrah2gqd1m9hmhtizsv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809092053+0000" stop="20240809101256+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Aquatics</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best diving, swimming and water polo stories from throughout Olympic history including Dawn Fraser, Greg Louganis and Michael Phelps.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vydzinqyv16sh5trwq8a"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809101256+0000" stop="20240809101940+0000">
    <title lang="en">Greg discovers some of the rarest photos of Chamonix 1924 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg and Photography curator Audrey unveil the story of Sonja Henie, a Norwegian Figure skater, and the youngest athlete to participate to the first Olympic Winter Games in Chamonix in 1924. She was 11. Her performance together with other events been immortalized by Auguste Couttet. He was a local photographer using glass plate photography at the time. Sonja later became a film star in Hollywood.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/esqvs5q6zh4jqobvhivq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809101940+0000" stop="20240809102458+0000">
    <title lang="en">Jeanette gets to hold Cathy Freeman spikes from Sydney 2000 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">As they continue travelling in time in ‘The Vault’, Jeanette is taken to the Running Shoes Collection. She discovers the oldest spikes from the 19th century and is handed over Cathy Freeman’s shoes from Sydney 2000, when she won Gold in the 400 meters. Patricia, the Collections Manager, explains her how special the colours of those shoes are. Then we get to hear from Cathy herself how special was that night in Sydney for her whole nation. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yokv9gsbu6bxiowzbx7c"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809102458+0000" stop="20240809103031+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Moschino dress from Torino 2006 regains its full splendour | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fashion and design have always played a key role in the Olympic History. In Torino 2006, Moschino studio designed a piece of art for Miss Italia to wear in the Opening Ceremony. Jeanette connects with former Head Designer JoAnn Tan to get the full story behind the dress. Angelo is finishing the restoration just in time to put the dress back on display and lit it again for the first time in 15 years, in front of Jeanette.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bchmyenq0afmfolb6v9g"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809103031+0000" stop="20240809103435+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘Robin Hood’ caught on camera for the first at Tokyo 2020 | The Vault </title>
    <desc lang="en">Archer specialists say one chance in few thousands but on camera it is the first time ever a ‘Robin Hood’ shot is recorded live! Now on public display, Greg discovers this rare artefact with Stephanie, one of the Museum curators. Shot by the Korean pair, An San and Kim Je-deok in the mixed event, they won Gold in that first-ever event at the Olympics. An san went on winning three Gold medals in Tokyo, demonstrating the dominance of South Korea in this discipline. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zt0pl5oeg7r70znej4eg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809103435+0000" stop="20240809104921+0000">
    <title lang="en">Forging India’s Badminton Champions | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head to the hustle of Hyderabad to meet India’s badminton legend Pullela Gopichand and hear of his champion-building dream. Insights from legends such as Saina Nehwal, Sai Praneeth and Kidambi Srikanth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmvup5pj6r0yeet7vupe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809104921+0000" stop="20240809110615+0000">
    <title lang="en">Youth take Centre Stage | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head behind the scenes and hang out with of some of India’s rising badminton talent.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/m7g04law6ojlfsbbjc8s"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809110615+0000" stop="20240809123627+0000">
    <title lang="en">The People’s Fighters | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">The powerful story of how a revolutionary boxing experiment produced Teofilo Stevenson and a legacy of Cuban success at the Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/n57vgpifgvxtrgl2eg5o"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809123627+0000" stop="20240809130318+0000">
    <title lang="en">It’s Not All Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">The off-season allows a brief break from gymnastics for Angelina. Training intensifies for a fired-up Morgan, while Yile reaches breaking point. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/cxnlm5ovbqqdrxxygvtt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809130318+0000" stop="20240809133221+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Interruption</title>
    <desc lang="en">The COVID-19 pandemic rocks the gymnasts’ schedules. The Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games are heartbreakingly postponed. The three gymnasts remain determined to chase their Olympic dreams. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o3p14hxx8rx4v06ujtrz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809133221+0000" stop="20240809142426+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Sprinters</title>
    <desc lang="en">A journey through the essential stories of the Olympic Games, focusing on the sprints in athletics, including Jesse Owens and Carl Lewis.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/a10ssakopgyui2lshtxf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809142426+0000" stop="20240809143533+0000">
    <title lang="en">Michael: No rest on the road to Olympic gold | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Take a look inside Michael Norman’s rigid routine as he prepares to redeem himself with an Olympic gold in the 400m distance at Paris 2024 this summer. While he is visiting his first track and field community, with family and fiancee all behind him, the American sprinter is dedicated to excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/czmk0qtmxfpna25t2i4t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809143533+0000" stop="20240809144417+0000">
    <title lang="en">Phil: breaking barriers to represent his community | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Canadian Breaker Phil ‘Wizard’ Kim, who comes from a traditional Korean family, takes to the streets of Vancouver, where he remembers how he fell in love with breaking and recounts his relentless journey to do what he loves the most : to dance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/v5q27smoc56yyvktpcxx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809144417+0000" stop="20240809145331+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ale: the Mexican diver trying to keep it all in synch | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Alejandra Orozco, two-time Olympic medallist in diving for Mexico, makes her fourth return to the Olympics at Paris 2024. More in sync than ever with her diving partner, Gabriela Agundez, and her family, she takes us back to where it all began: the family farm in the outskirt of Guadaljara. With the support of a loving family, hard work and dedication, she is hoping to reach the pinnacle of her career with Gold this Summer surrounded by her loved ones.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zmfuvbeujwgei666ihwi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809145331+0000" stop="20240809150235+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ni Nengah: a role model and a hero for Indonesia | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">She is Indonesia’s premiere Paralympic powerlifter and the country’s pride. A two-time Paralympic medallist, she is a mentor for the team as she prepares for her next objective: taking gold at Paris 2024 this summer. Although a recent injury puts all her work at risk, she is confident she will rise to the challenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yqud48fm2bapbaqqzjjq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809150235+0000" stop="20240809153700+0000">
    <title lang="en">Victory for Us | The Untold Story of India’s First Surf Team</title>
    <desc lang="en">El Salvador, World Surfing Games 2023, the Indian Surf Team participates for the very first time in an international event chasing their Olympic Qualification. This is the story of that journey, where those kids that once started surfing with broken boards reach an international stage for the first time, where they meet their surfing idols and earn experience for upcoming competitions. Watch it now!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/oabh9q5cjmkxiq0ngoio"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809153700+0000" stop="20240809155113+0000">
    <title lang="en">From NYC to Alaska, meet the pioneers and US champion | Breaking Life </title>
    <desc lang="en">As the birthplace of a global hip-hop movement, we meet some of the pioneers of Breaking in New-York City. While Kid Glyde shares his passion for breaking with the next generation at his Harlem studio, three thousand miles away in Anchorage Alaska, B-Boy Icey Ives, two-time US national champion, melts the ice with his local crew Frozen Flow while being a community leader, a teacher and a role model for the youth living in extremely challenging conditions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dovd8hi3ceymcdhls5v8"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809155113+0000" stop="20240809160739+0000">
    <title lang="en">French breakers set the scene for Paris 2024 Olympic Games| Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">France is a cultural melting pot. It’s also one of the biggest countries for Breaking with more than a thousand battles every year and some of the greatest international competitions. It’s also in Paris 2024 that Breaking will make its Olympic debut.
Dany Dann came to France from French Guyana to pursue a life in dance. Now, he juggles early morning shifts as a nurse, daily training and being a father – always with an eye on the next battle. Now reigning national champion, he trains with French national team members B-Girl Carlota and B-Boy Marlone for the WDSF World Breaking Championship in Paris.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/amx9sswjndootv2aps3j"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809160739+0000" stop="20240809162409+0000">
    <title lang="en">Young breakers take over the streets of Medellin | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">Colombia used to be one of the most dangerous countries in the world but has found new life through a revival in urban arts, becoming a global creative mecca. 
B-Girl Luma and 4Eskuela hip hop school, where she learnt Breaking and is now a teacher, have been instrumental to this change in Medellin (Colombia). But it’s not been an easy journey for Luma who also had her doubts about what she can really achieve through dancing. By winning international dance events around the world, she is now confident it gave her a career and a drive, also when teaching young kids in her neighbourhood. She is keen to participate to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iddfhrgah2b2pkoabbbd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809162409+0000" stop="20240809164341+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s growing breaking scene makes room for B-Girls | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s Breaking scene started in the early 2000’s and has since exploded in popularity. While mostly male dominated, women are increasingly accepted and celebrated in the Indian Breaking scene.
We meet B-Girl Jo, the two-time BC One India champion from Bangalore, as she travels alone to Mumbai. There, she meets her friend Flying Machine who organizes a community celebration event where B-Girls have a chance to battle it out. As a leader for Indian female hip-hop dancers, Jo reflects on her position in the society. With her own hip-hop and yoga studio and inspired by the challenges she’s already had to overcome, she examines her journey with both excitement and wisdom.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/njacmonn1ac4hzxkqjo0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809164341+0000" stop="20240809170007+0000">
    <title lang="en">Dakar breakers see new opportunities with Olympic debut| Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a classical and traditional African dance background, B-Boy Zaza is a key member of Power Crew, one of the most successful crew in Senegal. Joined by his young brother Emma, their crew is more like a family and made them travel to major global events. Now a teacher, tasked with navigating the challenges of his community, the dance gives him hope for a brighter future. With Paris 2024 and Dakar Youth Olympic Games in 2026, the elders and next generation alike to build their own future and for the sport as it takes roots in Senegal. Organized by the local dance federation, they participate in the Battle National, featuring some of Senegal’s best emerging talents. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/udhmfruynxxufbeoi4pc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809170007+0000" stop="20240809170743+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: the long and bumpy road to Olympic gold | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thirteen years after his Olympic debut, the British diver finally landed the gold medal that was missing from his collection.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uiluzuv9rhtucenqzoyr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809170743+0000" stop="20240809171444+0000">
    <title lang="en">Sakura Yosozumi: a skateboarding bloom that blossoms into Olympic gold | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the 19-year-old  Sakura, skateboarding started as a way to play with her brother and ended with the first Olympic gold medal in women's park skateboarding.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sdsjjijo3jqprclchwul"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809171444+0000" stop="20240809172135+0000">
    <title lang="en">Armand Duplantis:  flying high and smashing records | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sweden's Armand "Mondo" Duplantis confirmed his status as the best pole vaulter in the world by seizing his first Olympic pole vault title by storm.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/w5gmtxfnru4kglrubxes"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809172135+0000" stop="20240809173153+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rebeca Andrade: an Olympic fairytale | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian gymnast Rebeca Andrade's long and bleak climb from the favelas of Sao Paulo to the podium in Tokyo is a true Olympic fairytale.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pd2oa3ihqmeogxhwlsog"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809173153+0000" stop="20240809175819+0000">
    <title lang="en">France’s Tony Estanguet I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of France’s three-time gold medallist Tony Estanguet, who is now leading the Paris 2024 team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b6izxpaomx4gffamxdqu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809175819+0000" stop="20240809182734+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ethiopia’s Derartu Tulu I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of the first black African female gold medallist Derartu Tulu, who is now leading Ethiopia’s national athletics team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qvj58o7hhlsxkfjepxv9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809182734+0000" stop="20240809191946+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 2 : The Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/oxtlxdyhszwe4fvoseos"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809191946+0000" stop="20240809193957+0000">
    <title lang="en">Manuel: the next big thing in Angola’s favorite sport | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young basketball player from Angola shows us what the sport means to him and dreams of the endelless posibilities the future holds.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ofk3z4p9mfglypjkepr9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809193957+0000" stop="20240809195517+0000">
    <title lang="en">Miyanda: the lioness of Southafica’s BMX scene | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Miyanda Masseti is the highest ranked female BMX rider in Africa, shows us what inspires her to keep pushing and opening new possibilities for future female BMX riders in Africa.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ce6pgaujuftmx9lth3we"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809195517+0000" stop="20240809201001+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ornella: knocking down social prejudices pursuing her Olympic dream | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the first female boxer to represent her country, Ornella shows us why it’s important for the world to see more female African boxers on the global stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dob7vauikkp9fiqjge6t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809201001+0000" stop="20240809210543+0000">
    <title lang="en">Gold Medals Relived | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">US athletic comeback star Dave Wottle, Germany’s celebrated gymnast Karin Janz, acclaimed sprinter Valeriy Borzov, and nine-time Olympic medallist Ludmilla Tourischeva revisit their gold medal journeys during Munich 1972.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q2qupehpqfcq4l36umky"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809210543+0000" stop="20240809211942+0000">
    <title lang="en">Basketball vs Cricket with Akanksha Singh and Jemimah Rodrigues | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can cricketer Jemimah Rodrigues score a free throw shot? What happens when a basketball player attempts to bat in cricket? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ctzws273hfpt7skledzt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809211942+0000" stop="20240809213105+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs Cricket with Pravin Jadhav and Yuzvendra Chahal | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">How hard is it for a cricketer to pull the bow string? What are the skills that an Olympic archer can transfer to his cricket game? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ynssukgleu9u6s6pwjo7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809213105+0000" stop="20240809214226+0000">
    <title lang="en">Badminton vs Cricket with Srikanth Kidambi and Yuzvendra Chahal | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can cricketers play badminton? And what happens when India’s badminton champion Srikanth Kidambi swaps his racket for a cricket bat? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/axll28zcqcxyinsu9msm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809214226+0000" stop="20240809215229+0000">
    <title lang="en">The graceful journey of Olympic champion, Jessica von Bredow-Werndl | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jessica’s dream became reality at Tokyo 2020 with two Olympic Gold medals in dressage in the individual and team event. But her incredible bond with her horse, Dalera, is forged by hard work and an implacable discipline at Aubenhausen world-class riding centre. With her title back on the line at Paris 2024, she opens the doors of her family estate and reflects, with her family and her team, on an emotional journey full of joy and determination.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xu0cyawsztf22bgtsakb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809215229+0000" stop="20240809220323+0000">
    <title lang="en">French kiteboarding prodigee on her way to gold at Paris | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lauriane Nolot, the current world champion, aims for Gold at Paris 2024 on the shores of Marseille where Formula Kite will make its Olympic debut. Hailing from Camps-la-Source, an hour away from the Olympic venue, she climbs the ranks with determination from family get-aways to world podium. Her impressive journey propels her to the pinnacle of her sport, ready to shine on the Olympic stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kkplajzadqmx0pzuhdxn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809220323+0000" stop="20240809221314+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iris Tió is key to Spain’s next gold in Artistic Swimming | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Iris Tió Casas joined the senior national team at 15, living away from her parents most of the time. Four years later she competed in Tokyo where she was the youngest on the team. For Paris 2024, she will be crucial to the team’s chances, aiming for gold at Paris 2024. Her journey reflects immense dedication, resilience, and a dream realized through hard work. She will compete in the team as well as in the duet event with her partner Alissa Ozhogina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q1jnizm1gk98xjwmefzr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809221314+0000" stop="20240809222350+0000">
    <title lang="en">Helen Glover eyes Paris 2024 for her fourth Olympics | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">After winning back-to-back gold in London 2012 and Rio 2016, Helen Glover made a remarkable come-back in Tokyo 2020, being the first mother to row for Britain. She and partner Polly Swann finished fourth. Helen now has her sights on Paris 2024 where she should be competing in the Women's four event, focusing on adding another Olympic medal to her impressive career for Team GB.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qnrah2gqd1m9hmhtizsv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809222350+0000" stop="20240809231831+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can NBA and Dream Team star Laettner teach this team to win?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team USA and NBA legend Christian Laettner shows the Garinger High School varsity basketball team how they can improve their game.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/isyf33697ado3urpz3i0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240809231831+0000" stop="20240810001305+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Russia’s rhythmic gymnast Margarita Mamun transform this Z Team?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic gold medalist Margarita Mamun tries to turn around the fortunes of Moscow’s Pirouette Gymnastics team. Is one week enough?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlnv2wdbo39syeajuoxa"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
