<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2025-10-26 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251025235518+0000" stop="20251026000509+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026000509+0000" stop="20251026001418+0000">
    <title lang="en">France's Sevens captain targets gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Backed by a great team and high perfornming coaches, Carla's quest for Olympic gold symbolizes the rise of women's rugby since Rio 2016. From competing with boys to leading her nation to Silver in Tokyo 2020, the French rugby Seven squad’s captain inspires resilience and dedication on the road to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wx3cbtavgwlobv8mubju"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026001418+0000" stop="20251026002244+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026002244+0000" stop="20251026003304+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026003304+0000" stop="20251026005040+0000">
    <title lang="en">Pamela Rosa: The Champion | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pamela Rosa from São Paulo, Brazil, is a former women’s world champion in skateboarding. With two X-Games wins and four other podium finishes, she represented Brazil in skateboarding's Olympic debut. Despite an injury in Tokyo, she reclaimed the world champion title in 2021. As a key member of the Brazilian national team, Pamela continues to be one of the most recognizable and formidable skaters in the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/r0j731fwy4kw0rnwjrdq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026005040+0000" stop="20251026010421+0000">
    <title lang="en">GRLSWIRL: A Global Skate Sisterhood | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lucy Osinski, a former ballerina, discovered new power on a skateboard and founded GRLSWIRL in 2018. This all-female skate sisterhood, born in Venice Beach, embraces femininity in skating. With chapters around the world, Lucy visits Paris to highlight the vibrant community and inspiring vision of GRLSWIRL.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yp6xlqt608ahqdqicdlc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026010421+0000" stop="20251026012001+0000">
    <title lang="en">Funa Nakayama: The Groundbreaker | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hailing from Toyama City, Funa Nakayama has quickly risen through the skateboarding ranks. At just 18, she's competed in top contests worldwide, earning accolades, including a bronze medal in the 2020 Tokyo Olympics. Follow Funa's journey of hard work, skill, and dedication as she breaks new ground in skateboarding.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fmeqt3znvclebptpucuh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026012001+0000" stop="20251026013815+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘We’re the Best Team in New York City’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">City soccer is very special in New-York City and MLK sits at the top, with 19 titles in 25 years. The team is off to a new season and gunning for its 20th title. Coach Jake and assistant Kamani welcome the team for their first practice and super-pro prospect Carlos Lainez is back from Spain. TThey will soon play the top Ohio State team. After a rough start, the team is taking shape but it’s a 16 match competition before the play-offs begin.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jkledz0yuuypaxfwd3xu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026013815+0000" stop="20251026015953+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Guy in the Mirror is Usually the One Stopping You’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Carlos Junior, the team captain and best pro prospect has 13 brothers and sisters, 4 are living with him and his dad in the Bronx. A semi-pro club in Spain offered him a contract but he made the promise to Jake and his MLK family to get them that 20th win. Maynor, also from Honduras, is taking care of his disabled mother. After a shaky start to the season, he comes into his own against Upper West Side rival Beacon.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bqaakxjnat3fcicgvfvj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026015953+0000" stop="20251026021826+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘You Not Really about it’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">MLK high school has been unstoppable this year. They are about to achieve an undefeated season. But Coach Jake is getting increasingly tense. While some players like Charles are doing great both at school and on the team, others like goalkeeper Raymond are struggling to keep their nerves, putting the whole team at risks. Raymond is trying to live up to the dreams and expectations of his father, a talented goalkeeper himself who never made it pro. Soon the team faces a decisive game which will determine the number one seed in the playoffs.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/if7vuj7ifiybsfkhwmuh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026021826+0000" stop="20251026023459+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘This is What We Live For’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">MLK finally enters the playoffs. Three more games separate the team from their goal but their starting goalkeeper is now suspended. Assistant coach Kimani, both the kids’ chief on-field instructor and off-field confidant, manages to keep the team in balance. His patience combined with Jake’s drive are a perfect match. Defender Vakaba, who has come to New York City to fulfil his dream, joins the team and becomes an essential part of its success.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dp63tlka8kzbj8dfsbhk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026023459+0000" stop="20251026030045+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Only Game that Matter is the Last One’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can we tell a King player from another player just by his look?. A storybook season must end in storybook fashion. But as MLK is leading in semi-final, top player Carlos get a yellow card against their long-time rivals Beacon. Jake's obsession is now turning into superstition as he makes a final call that will soon turn the team fortune. Maynor, who had seemed to struggle in front of the goal since the start of the season, is proving to be a decisive striker.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wcyl9ogeioantt1eg57k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026030045+0000" stop="20251026032257+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘Bacon, Egg and Cheese’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">David Reyes Aka D. Dotty is a burly defender but he is juggling soccer and a burgeoning rap career with the need to help his family earn money in a tough Bronx neighbourhood. He often comes late or tired to the pitch. As the team moves up the rankings, Coach Jake is getting nervous and talks about his past troubles with addiction.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fmh1epkngm7ngg3unml5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026032257+0000" stop="20251026045038+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: 1.6 Seconds | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">This feature documentary dives into the life of the UK’s diving legend. From Beijing 2008 to his gold medal in Tokyo 2020 and final Olympics in Paris 2024, Daley shares his personal journey, the pressures, losses, and triumphs that defined his career. Exclusive footage and candid moments reveal a story of resilience and growth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xgpfd7xks6xvxhiuxs2n"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026045038+0000" stop="20251026052401+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Helen Glover, Paris 2024 Costumes, Olympic Refugee Boxer</title>
    <desc lang="en">British rowing sensation Helen Glover comes to The Vault to donate her kit from Paris 2024 and recounts her incredible come back while being a mum of two. Jeannette unveils the incredible costumes from the Paris 2024 ceremonies. Rob stumbles on one of the most precious and largest items of the collection, a two-men rowing scull from Paris 1924 and discovers the surprising story of the unknown French boy who was the coxswain.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/srx3fdo0esgjzfokwugg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026052401+0000" stop="20251026060244+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Rebeca Andrade, rare items from the cancelled Tokyo 1940 Games, Olympic torches &amp; swimwear throughout the years</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rebeca Andrade and Simon Biles leotards back-to-back in The Vault take us to the amazing world of gymnastics at the Olympics. We meet the Brazilian queen of gymnastics in training in San Paolo who shared her emotion in dethroning the American legend in the Floor event at Paris 2024 in her sparkling yellow kit. Rob explores a small but very rare collection of objects from the cancelled 1940 Tokyo Games while Jeannette finds herself in the Olympic torch room.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lczdrrx57arpnsq9y5cu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026060000+0000" stop="20251026060700+0000">
    <title lang="en">Lauryn Williams’ Suits Prove She is Mastering More Than One Sport | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">How does an Olympic sprinter become a bobsleigh champion? Lauryn Williams stunned the world by winning medals at both the Summer and Winter Olympic Games. Through one of her rare kits, we discover her incredible switch from track to ice and her personal Olympic journey. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/g6deg1kp6ucdd9ebqiqy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026060700+0000" stop="20251026064047+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Matthias Steiner, Olympic timekeeping, Sky Brown, Dream Team</title>
    <desc lang="en">Weightlifting legend Matthias Steiner comes to The Vault to share his incredible stories and discover his kit on display at the Olympic Museum for the first time. Sky Brown who donated her skateboard shares her emotion in winning a medal at Tokyo 2020. Jeannette discovers the magic eye camera from London 1948 while Rob finds Michael Jordan’s iconic shoes from Barcelona 1992 which leads him to an unexpected “other dream team” story linking the Olympic and the Grateful Dead.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/adgrtr2e7jltxve9e3ve"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026064047+0000" stop="20251026071601+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Greg Louganis, Hollywood, Beach Volleyball, Mascots</title>
    <desc lang="en">As we uncover Los Angeles 1984 Olympics memorabilia, we get to travel to the home of diving legend Greg Louganis to discover his emotional Olympic journey. The Summer Games are back in L.A. in 2028 but Hollywood made the Games a star-studded show from as early as Los Angeles 1932, from celebrity appearances to Olympians becoming movie stars. In The Vault, Jeannette finds a very special beach volleyball from Paris 2024 and Rob surprises her as they discover The Vault’s incredible mascots collection.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xdtjzlepkibq2zzog1su"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026071601+0000" stop="20251026074116+0000">
    <title lang="en">Last Touches Before the Start of the Season</title>
    <desc lang="en">The teams are prepping for one of the first major competitions of the season. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bbjjwjwchi4pvuqnkic4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026074116+0000" stop="20251026080639+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Top Teams Face Off</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the Grand Prix season intensifies, the Academy’s top teams find themselves competing against each other in what can be a rehearsal to what’s to come at the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dwa1f9f5cqzaxyuicb9j"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026080639+0000" stop="20251026083233+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Ends with Triumph at Beijing 2022</title>
    <desc lang="en">This episode chronicles the Beijing 2022 experience of our six teams as their months of training and preparation culminates in success at the Olympic Ice Dance competition. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/v1576252711/primary/ajmwvaqrlzp7k9smjesk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026083233+0000" stop="20251026101230+0000">
    <title lang="en">SEVENSECONDS, the dream of flying | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Monsterbakken, literally the Monster Hill, is the largest ski flying hill in the world. When you sit on the take-off bar, the adrenaline level is equivalent to a panic attack and yet it is the declared goal of our two main characters to sit on this bar and plunge into the void at the first official women's ski flying event in history.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ip7og8tp9bjexnvpswr7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026101230+0000" stop="20251026113441+0000">
    <title lang="en">Winter Tracks | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">Winter Tracks enters the world of six unique athletes as they prepare for Beijing 2022 and offers an authentic and emotional look at what it truly takes to be an Olympian.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ygekimzm41cdjxcnunqf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026113441+0000" stop="20251026120217+0000">
    <title lang="en">From The Top Episode 4: Nathan Chen and Hayley Kiyoko</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic figure skater Nathan Chen meets music star Hayley Kiyoko. She runs him through the choreography for one of her tracks, before they hit the ice-skating rink and attempt to implement the new choreography moves to surprising results. Hayley and Nathan also discuss their community responsibilities and open up about what it means for them to be Asian American role models. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nk7oeipa8e2estkb6gz4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026120217+0000" stop="20251026120934+0000">
    <title lang="en">Being a Community Role Model | Nathan Chen and Hayley Kiyoko | From The Top</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hayley and Nathan discuss their community responsibilities and open up about what it means for them to be Asian American role models. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/tfl7z9w76q2zdomfy7xa"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026120934+0000" stop="20251026133937+0000">
    <title lang="en">Picabo | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">A charismatic tour-de-force, American Picabo Street took the alpine skiing world by storm in the 1990’s by winning Olympic silver and gold. But beneath the bravado and success lay a turbulent and complicated home life. Co-directed by Frank Marshall and Lindsey Vonn.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zjezy37styke1x0pd77o"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026133937+0000" stop="20251026135329+0000">
    <title lang="en">The first Mexican Olympic figure skater in 30 years | Winter Tracks</title>
    <desc lang="en">When he competes in next Olympic Winter Games, Donovan Carrillo will be the first figure skater from Mexico to do so in 30 years. In a country with barely any Olympic size rinks, he is an artist who believes figure skating has given him the perfect platform to express himself. He moved away from his hometown and family when he was 13. Living with his coach, Gregorio Núñez, a father-like figure, to further his training. Together, they have overcome huge obstacles including lack of resources, funding and recent COVID restrictions to finally qualify for the Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qrkvbx9mndmb30z7zxdw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026135329+0000" stop="20251026140511+0000">
    <title lang="en">Wrapping Up the Grand Prix Season | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the sixth and final Grand Prix completed, coach Marie-France Dubreuil reflects on what each of the teams have achieved so far. Zach is curious about Madison and Adrian’s wedding plans. Gabriella makes an intriguing prediction about the Beijing 2022 Winter Olympics podium. 

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xvbysyllh4a083m8tjkl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026140511+0000" stop="20251026141523+0000">
    <title lang="en">From Helsinki to Vegas | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">Back from Finland, the teams are prepping for the beginning of the ice dancing Grand Prix season. Four of the teams compete in Skate America 2021 in Vegas, where Madi and Zach defend their title, and Madi and Evan try to go for the win. Lilah and Guillaume talk about the homophobic remarks that came out of Finland. 

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.  
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/efpymy6guzupuk2awvec"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026141523+0000" stop="20251026141856+0000">
    <title lang="en">Fynn Bullock: The Multitalented Snowboarder</title>
    <desc lang="en">American wakeboarder and an elite snowboarder, Fynn Bullock, wishes both his sports were Olympic sports. He explains how doing two sports at an elite level has shaped him as an athlete and the person he is today. 
Music track: Skeletons, Easy Life

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqbnocxedgtkkjhdxglb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026141856+0000" stop="20251026142358+0000">
    <title lang="en">Katie Ormerod, fully recovered and ready for Beijing 2022</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team GB’s Olympic medal hope, Katie Ormerod, started snowboarding on dry slopes when she was five years old. Few years later, she became the first female snowboarder to land a double cork 1080. Ormerod is eager to compete in Beijing 2022 after a last-minute injury had put her Olympic dream on hold in PyeongChang 2018.
Music track: Hot Hot, Bree Runway
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ih59bdguansjq7mxx8wq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026142358+0000" stop="20251026142922+0000">
    <title lang="en">Freestyle Ski Star Kelly Sildaru is Ready for Beijing 2022</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a knee injury stopped her from competing in PyeongChang 2018, Estonian skier Kelly Sildaru pushed hard to recover and come back strong to win gold at the Olympic Youth Winter Games in Lausanne 2020. Driven by the love for her sport, the Estonian star skier says her next mission is Beijing 2022.   
Music track: Distorted Light Beam, Bastille
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uqadv3dxldxhpznwm23s"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026142922+0000" stop="20251026143339+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Johannes Klaebo, the cross-country ski sensation from Norway</title>
    <desc lang="en">Norway’s top cross-country skier Johannes Klaebo was once the world’s youngest male to win a FIS World Cup, a World Championship, and an Olympic medal in his sport. What his story and how he is aiming for gold at Beijing 2022. 
Music track: Black Magic, Jonasu
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/j5pkuiplhuaadjfbhbxw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026143339+0000" stop="20251026143808+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mia Clerc, Madagascar’s first female Olympic skier</title>
    <desc lang="en">The inspiring story of Malagasy skier Mialitiana Clerc and how she wants her Olympic journey to inspire her nation. She is excited to represent her country of birth again in Beijing 2022. 
Music track: Mirror, Sigrid
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nnakqp5fcjkae7s97x28"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026143808+0000" stop="20251026144233+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kevin Rolland: France’s spectacular freestyle skier</title>
    <desc lang="en">France’s freestyle skier and halfpipe expert, Kevin Rolland, speaks about recovering from severe injury, the thrill of freestyle riding, and getting ready to compete at the Olympic Winter Games Beijing 2022.
Music Track: Tokyo Drifting, Glass Animals

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dhy0e9jefrkhrppqtbqb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026144233+0000" stop="20251026145701+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Great Start to the Season | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">It’s the teams’ first chance of the season to try their brand-new ice dancing programs in competition and in front of a live audience. Olivia and Adrian have a decisive performance for their Olympic qualification. Gabriella and Guillaume compete for the first time in 20 months. Madison and Evan get to see how the crowd react to try their new program. Lilah and Lewis are in for a great start. 

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.  

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vr6ef6cvrfqvmlgksyvi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026145701+0000" stop="20251026150912+0000">
    <title lang="en">Hockey superstar raised on a farm searching for Olympic glory | Winter Tracks</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jenni Hiirikoski is regarded as one of the finest Ice Hockey players of her generation. She is the captain of Finland’s national team and a future Hall of Famer. Until she was a teenager, Jenni had to play with boys. Later whilst her teammates went on to the NHL, Jenni had to balance competing with working a day job despite being one of the best players ever. She now goes into her fourth Olympics in Beijing knowing it could be her last chance to achieve Olympic glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zqgb40vdvnv00breb11m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026150912+0000" stop="20251026152302+0000">
    <title lang="en">Transplant survivor to represent Puerto Rico at next Olympics | Winter Tracks</title>
    <desc lang="en">When William Flaherty was just three years old, he had a bone marrow transplant to save his life. The donor was his brother, Charles. Charles went on to be the first Winter Olympian to represent Puerto Rico in two decades and competed in PyeongChang 2018. Now aged 17, William is preparing to take over for his brother in representing his country at the next Winter Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiedd88fwhq2lk7sbfme"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026152302+0000" stop="20251026153600+0000">
    <title lang="en">Big Last-Minute Changes | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">Madison and Evan take the risk of changing their program’s music in the last minute. Madison and Zach are headed to Boston for their first competition of the season. Olivia and Adrian reflect on the coaches’ disappointment and work on improvements. Laurence and Nikolaj open up about Nikolaj’s injury and road to recovery.  
Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.  
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/d2wlgblhxxzckym8wgcm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026153600+0000" stop="20251026155725+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet this Big, Competitive Ice Dance Family | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meet the six teams training together at the Ice Academy of Montreal in Canada for the Olympic Games Beijing 2022. Gabriella and Guillaume reflect on their PyeongChang experience. Madison and Zach have some on-ice tension and speak about their emotional connection and Scott Moir tells us what it takes to be an Olympic champion.  
Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries chronicling the day-to-day lives of six teams from five countries training at the Ice Academy of Montreal. 

Featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uijnvhrz70qhcaz4nman"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026155725+0000" stop="20251026161232+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Mountain of Problems to Solve | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">It is 5 months until Beijing 2022 and as coach Romain Haguenauer puts it: “There is a mountain of problems to solve” technically, artistically and physically for the athletes to be ready.
In this second episode of the weekly series On Edge, get an intimate look at how the coaching system at the Academy operates and what it takes to prep the athletes’ programs. Madison and Evan reveal their new routine theme and work on the costume design. Olivia and Adrian  perform their new program in front of the coaches and training mates for the first time. 
Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly ice dancing reality docuseries chronicling the day-to-day lives of six teams from five countries training at the Ice Academy of Montreal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/d1nw2ghayfygye87jx8w"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026161232+0000" stop="20251026161546+0000">
    <title lang="en">Aljona Savchenko: the queen who doesn’t give up | Her Game</title>
    <desc lang="en">It took Aljona Savchenko FIVE Olympic Games to win Gold. The pairs figure skater is now looking ahead for a repeat at Beijing 2022.
Featured song: Queen by Loren Gray
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/i0n5tjb0tv2btnufteqe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026161546+0000" stop="20251026170636+0000">
    <title lang="en">Highest Air</title>
    <desc lang="en">The world’s top snowboarders attempt to break the world’s record for how high you can jump out of the halfpipe. Will they succeed? 
Filmed in Saas Fee, Switzerland, in October 2020, the film features snowboarders Scotty James, Ayumu Hirano, Chase Josey, Maddie Mastro, Taylor Gold, Pat Burgener, Leilani Ettel and skier Dylan Marineau.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/im8erhlrsnwnysia6cdm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026170636+0000" stop="20251026171923+0000">
    <title lang="en">Cirque Blanc | Regaining confidence ahead of Cortina</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the third episode of Cirque Blanc, Tiff is hard at work in Crans-Montana whilst Romane embarks upon the long road to recovery. Tessa continues to build momentum, winning her first World Cup race since 2018 and lifting the spirits of the entire French team ahead of the World Championships in Cortina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mif1gqpc6d7uwdgb5mgl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026171923+0000" stop="20251026172416+0000">
    <title lang="en">Halfpipe Hype | The Joy of Riding</title>
    <desc lang="en">The world’s best snowboarders reveal their addiction to going high: the unique sensory feeling of ‘getting air’ jumping out of a halfpipe.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ylnhz4nva1lmyhpwokng"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026172416+0000" stop="20251026173000+0000">
    <title lang="en">Halfpipe Hype | The Science</title>
    <desc lang="en">Athletes, sports scientists, halfpipe builders and snowboard makers reveal the factors that determine how high a rider can air.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/y5gnkfcxm0uyrldxjqei"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026173000+0000" stop="20251026173352+0000">
    <title lang="en">Halfpipe Hype | Highest Ski Air</title>
    <desc lang="en">Canadian Skier Dylan Marineau attempts to break the world record for the highest ski air in a halfpipe.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/axh6q16iehkvpeizzd4x"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026173352+0000" stop="20251026174316+0000">
    <title lang="en">Halfpipe Hype | The Evolution</title>
    <desc lang="en">Featuring epic snowboard airs, the world’s best snowboarders revisit the greatest moments in the history of getting air. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ebrfi3qc5uj5oikvvs9x"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026174316+0000" stop="20251026174827+0000">
    <title lang="en">Halfpipe Hype | The Dangers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Is halfpipe riding the most dangerous Olympic sport? Athletes reveal the dangers and fears they must overcome to succeed. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xxjpjqlibkzels6f6jin"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026174827+0000" stop="20251026175404+0000">
    <title lang="en">Halfpipe Hype | Ayumu Hirano Returns</title>
    <desc lang="en">After chasing his Olympic skateboarding dream, Japan’s two-time Olympic silver medallist Ayumu Hirano is back on his snowboard in search of gold.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sxrsae6ltsgcsqehfgfo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026175404+0000" stop="20251026180821+0000">
    <title lang="en">Cirque Blanc | Injury and pressure in Val d’Isère</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the Cirque Blanc rolls into Val d’Isère for the start of the women’s downhill ski season, the French team has one notable absentee. Romane comes to terms with a season-changing injury, and the pressure is on for Tiffany and Tessa to perform on home soil.
Cirque Blanc is the Olympic Channel’s new original alpine skiing documentary series following France’s top female skiers Tessa Worley, Tiffany Gauthier and Romane Miradoli on the Alpine Ski World Cup circuit 2020/2021.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u28hrhnujtosnbqpt82a"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026180821+0000" stop="20251026191742+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Brilliant Curling Story | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">Led by skip Rhona Martin, five unassuming women from Scotland unite for a shot at Olympic curling glory – and end up capturing the hearts of a nation in the process.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/f27d20h9hfdxe8jcnklv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026191742+0000" stop="20251026193007+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Spanish Duel for the Holiday Season | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's down to the wire as Olivia and Adrian travel to Jaca, Spain, to compete against their rivals for the Spanish Olympic spot. Losing is not an option. Back in Montreal, Madison and Evan who decided to be safe and spend the holidays in Canada, share their hopes and expectations from the coming Olympic Games.

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opv0dwyt6dlh2kte3c8z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026193007+0000" stop="20251026194412+0000">
    <title lang="en">Cirque Blanc | The World Championships</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the fourth and final episode of Cirque Blanc, the French team heads to the 2021 World Championships in Cortina, whilst coping with the pressures that COVID brings. Tessa and Tiff battle it out in Italy, while Romane is putting in the efforts to get back to full fitness and begins to look ahead to life after injury.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gaavb0ska3gxyhk6d4bc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026194412+0000" stop="20251026195659+0000">
    <title lang="en">Cirque Blanc | Regaining confidence ahead of Cortina</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the third episode of Cirque Blanc, Tiff is hard at work in Crans-Montana whilst Romane embarks upon the long road to recovery. Tessa continues to build momentum, winning her first World Cup race since 2018 and lifting the spirits of the entire French team ahead of the World Championships in Cortina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mif1gqpc6d7uwdgb5mgl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026195659+0000" stop="20251026201116+0000">
    <title lang="en">Cirque Blanc | Injury and pressure in Val d’Isère</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the Cirque Blanc rolls into Val d’Isère for the start of the women’s downhill ski season, the French team has one notable absentee. Romane comes to terms with a season-changing injury, and the pressure is on for Tiffany and Tessa to perform on home soil.
Cirque Blanc is the Olympic Channel’s new original alpine skiing documentary series following France’s top female skiers Tessa Worley, Tiffany Gauthier and Romane Miradoli on the Alpine Ski World Cup circuit 2020/2021.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u28hrhnujtosnbqpt82a"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026201116+0000" stop="20251026210505+0000">
    <title lang="en">Cirque Blanc | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow France’s elite female speed skiing team as they compete on the Alpine Ski World Cup circuit and deal with the challenges of a season held during the Covid-19 pandemic. The documentary film offers a unique access to the lives and challenges in the world of women’s elite skiing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gsuy89oppcmtgcro2xu9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026210505+0000" stop="20251026213028+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Top Teams Face Off</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the Grand Prix season intensifies, the Academy’s top teams find themselves competing against each other in what can be a rehearsal to what’s to come at the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/v1534934346/primary/tfhpmhdnaizba8ffccqp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026213028+0000" stop="20251026215622+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Ends with Triumph at Beijing 2022</title>
    <desc lang="en">This episode chronicles the Beijing 2022 experience of our six teams as their months of training and preparation culminates in success at the Olympic Ice Dance competition. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aljzqht59afe8rrvf9gs"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026215622+0000" stop="20251026222147+0000">
    <title lang="en">Full House for Beijing 2022</title>
    <desc lang="en">The six ice dancing teams have qualified to go to Beijing 2022. They have few intense weeks to put the final touches on their programs. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jbhx2twtcs2llbwon4fv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026222147+0000" stop="20251026224637+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet this Big Competitive Ice Dance Family</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meet the six teams training together at the Ice Academy of Montreal in Canada for the Olympic Games Beijing 2022. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dwa1f9f5cqzaxyuicb9j"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026224637+0000" stop="20251026230739+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Ends with Triumph at Beijing 2022 | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">This special extra episode of On Edge, chronicles the Beijing 2022 experience of our six teams as their months of training and preparation culminates in success for all of them in the Olympic Ice Dance competition.

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/tudhaqahlx5k55uthvw8"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026230739+0000" stop="20251026232406+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Spanish Duel for the Holiday Season | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's down to the wire as Olivia and Adrian travel to Jaca, Spain, to compete against their rivals for the Spanish Olympic spot. Losing is not an option. Back in Montreal, Madison and Evan who decided to be safe and spend the holidays in Canada, share their hopes and expectations from the coming Olympic Games.

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opv0dwyt6dlh2kte3c8z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251026232406+0000" stop="20251027010330+0000">
    <title lang="en">SEVENSECONDS, the dream of flying | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Monsterbakken, literally the Monster Hill, is the largest ski flying hill in the world. When you sit on the take-off bar, the adrenaline level is equivalent to a panic attack and yet it is the declared goal of our two main characters to sit on this bar and plunge into the void at the first official women's ski flying event in history.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ip7og8tp9bjexnvpswr7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027010330+0000" stop="20251027013259+0000">
    <title lang="en">From The Top Episode 4: Nathan Chen and Hayley Kiyoko</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic figure skater Nathan Chen meets music star Hayley Kiyoko. She runs him through the choreography for one of her tracks, before they hit the ice-skating rink and attempt to implement the new choreography moves to surprising results. Hayley and Nathan also discuss their community responsibilities and open up about what it means for them to be Asian American role models. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nk7oeipa8e2estkb6gz4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027013259+0000" stop="20251027030958+0000">
    <title lang="en">Picabo | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">A charismatic tour-de-force, American Picabo Street took the alpine skiing world by storm in the 1990’s by winning Olympic silver and gold. But beneath the bravado and success lay a turbulent and complicated home life. Co-directed by Frank Marshall and Lindsey Vonn.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zjezy37styke1x0pd77o"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027030958+0000" stop="20251027043455+0000">
    <title lang="en">Winter Tracks | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">Winter Tracks enters the world of six unique athletes as they prepare for Beijing 2022 and offers an authentic and emotional look at what it truly takes to be an Olympian.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ygekimzm41cdjxcnunqf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027043455+0000" stop="20251027050146+0000">
    <title lang="en">From The Top Episode 4: Nathan Chen and Hayley Kiyoko</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic figure skater Nathan Chen meets music star Hayley Kiyoko. She runs him through the choreography for one of her tracks, before they hit the ice-skating rink and attempt to implement the new choreography moves to surprising results. Hayley and Nathan also discuss their community responsibilities and open up about what it means for them to be Asian American role models. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nk7oeipa8e2estkb6gz4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027050146+0000" stop="20251027052709+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Top Teams Face Off</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the Grand Prix season intensifies, the Academy’s top teams find themselves competing against each other in what can be a rehearsal to what’s to come at the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jnpzmlexelerovvzuapa"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027052709+0000" stop="20251027060240+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Ends with Triumph at Beijing 2022</title>
    <desc lang="en">This episode chronicles the Beijing 2022 experience of our six teams as their months of training and preparation culminates in success at the Olympic Ice Dance competition. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/njqw0v9tsmcgmkufwgms"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027060000+0000" stop="20251027082402+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Slopestyle Finals - Snowboard | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The women's slopestyle finals were held at the Phoenix Snow Park on 12 February 2018.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pnhqymguev3wvq8qf5ly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027082402+0000" stop="20251027100504+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Moguls Finals - Freestyle Skiing | PyoengChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The men's moguls finals were held at the Phoenix Snow Park on 12 February 2018.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpfvd5musxjeqywuihqy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027100504+0000" stop="20251027104058+0000">
    <title lang="en">My Great Winter Olympic Moments with Arianna Fontana</title>
    <desc lang="en">Arianna Fontana is the greatest female short track speed skater in Olympic history. Her numbers at the Games speak for themselves; one gold, two silver, and five bronze. In this edition of My Great Winter Olympic Moments she talks about her Tokyo 2020 plans, burnout on ice and life beyond the speed skating ring, with special appearances by her husband and coach Anthony Lobello Jr., Italian Alps, church bells and her beloved Great Dane - Zeus.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bnvtjz3t6jq6tlys8jgy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027104058+0000" stop="20251027105356+0000">
    <title lang="en">Anatomy of a Snowboarder: Hidden strengths of slopestyle star Sven Thorgren</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Swedish snowboarder demonstrates his all-round athleticism in a world-class sports science facility.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mbz8ggmwgnmuj2mkgle8"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027105356+0000" stop="20251027114611+0000">
    <title lang="en">Sliding Madness | A journey on Luge, Speed Skating, Skeleton &amp; Monobob tracks</title>
    <desc lang="en">St. Moritz, Switzerland, January 2020, the Winter Youth Olympic Games. Skeleton, Luge, Speed Skating and Monobob are the four disciplines that are hosted in the Alpine village. Teenage athletes from all around the globe participate for the first time in an Olympic Games, not only the competition is important to them, the friendship between Teams, the camaraderie and the Olympic Spirit embrace these young athletes during these Games leaving them all with an unforgettable experience.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/or0aqgfp3cp5vrzkdmf3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027114611+0000" stop="20251027134357+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Giant Slalom, 1st Run - Alpine Skiing | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The women's giant slalom competition was held at the Yongpyong Alpine Centre on 12 February 2018.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sqpiq4phy6gksmnmy73b"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027134357+0000" stop="20251027155013+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Giant Slalom, 2nd Run - Alpine Skiing | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The women's giant slalom competition was held at the Yongpyong Alpine Centre on 12 February 2018.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yao4opx5etysip01yfsp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027155013+0000" stop="20251027162607+0000">
    <title lang="en">My Great Winter Olympic Moments with Arianna Fontana</title>
    <desc lang="en">Arianna Fontana is the greatest female short track speed skater in Olympic history. Her numbers at the Games speak for themselves; one gold, two silver, and five bronze. In this edition of My Great Winter Olympic Moments she talks about her Tokyo 2020 plans, burnout on ice and life beyond the speed skating ring, with special appearances by her husband and coach Anthony Lobello Jr., Italian Alps, church bells and her beloved Great Dane - Zeus.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bnvtjz3t6jq6tlys8jgy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027162607+0000" stop="20251027171810+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ice Hockey: Team Switzerland Men</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relive PyeongChang 2018 through the eyes of the Men’s Swiss Ice Hockey Team and follow their quest for an Olympic Medal</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hwcgtxgzotfglgrsugcg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027171810+0000" stop="20251027180814+0000">
    <title lang="en">Highest Air</title>
    <desc lang="en">The world’s top snowboarders attempt to break the world’s record for how high you can jump out of the halfpipe. Will they succeed? 
Filmed in Saas Fee, Switzerland, in October 2020, the film features snowboarders Scotty James, Ayumu Hirano, Chase Josey, Maddie Mastro, Taylor Gold, Pat Burgener, Leilani Ettel and skier Dylan Marineau.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/im8erhlrsnwnysia6cdm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027180814+0000" stop="20251027194714+0000">
    <title lang="en">CAN v SUI (Gold Medal) - Mixed Doubles Curling | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The mixed doubles curling Gold Medal Game was held at the Gangneung Curling Centre on 13 February 2018.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/tk0t4yhkb05uix4ivzup"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027194714+0000" stop="20251027215254+0000">
    <title lang="en">USA v SLO (Group B) - Men's Ice Hockey | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This qualification game was held at the Kwandong Hockey Centre on 14 February 2018.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ckzl13qb9ab9y8ngltg9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20251027215254+0000" stop="20251028002035+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Normal Hill - Ski Jumping | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The women's normal hill competition was held on 12 February 2018 at the Alpensia Ski Jump Centre.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ej2s82vgmzgmiq1f1ms4"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
