<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2025-08-15 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250814233730+0000" stop="20250815011020+0000">
    <title lang="en">Personal Best: Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Relive the Paris 2024 Olympic Games through the journeys of eight remarkable athletes who pushed past limits, defied expectations, and inspired the world. Featuring Noah Lyles, Faith Kipyegon, Jack Robinson, Huang Yaqiong and Zheng Siwei, Leon Marchand, Olga Kharlan and Cindy Ngamba.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mbdw8tkwlcxrymf3hndy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815011020+0000" stop="20250815040605+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mat 1: Women's -63kg, Men's -81kg Repechages/Semi-Finals/Finals | Judo | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Women's -63kg and Men's -81kg Finals took place on 30/07/2024 at the Champ-de-Mars Arena, Paris. 
At the Women's -63kg, Andreja Leski (SLO) claimed the Gold medal, Prisca Awiti Alcaraz (MEX) won the Silver, and the Bronze medals went to Laura Fazliu (KOS) and Clarisse Agbegnenou (FRA). 
At the Men's -81kg,Takanori Nagase (JPN) won the Gold medal, Tato Grigalashvili (GEO) took the Silver, and the Bronze medals went to Somon Makhmadbekov (TJK) and Joonhwan Lee (KOR).</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ks7wir7utvmmyxz78dug"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815040605+0000" stop="20250815043438+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's 4x200m Freestyle Relay - Final | Swimming | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's 4x200m Freestyle was held on 30/07/2024 at Paris La Defense Arena. Great Britain claimed the Gold with a  time of 6:59.43, The United States of America took Silver and Australia completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nt0jmer0gfypmez2tjg4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815043438+0000" stop="20250815044859+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet the transgender swim star who’s earned a spot on the men’s team</title>
    <desc lang="en">Schuyler Bailar is a decorated swimmer who was recruited to Harvard as a female, but has found peace after transitioning to a male.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wciesz7sdq2zrutjr07q"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815044859+0000" stop="20250815052743+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Rebeca Andrade, rare items from the cancelled Tokyo 1940 Games, Olympic torches &amp; swimwear throughout the years</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rebeca Andrade and Simon Biles leotards back-to-back in The Vault take us to the amazing world of gymnastics at the Olympics. We meet the Brazilian queen of gymnastics in training in San Paolo who shared her emotion in dethroning the American legend in the Floor event at Paris 2024 in her sparkling yellow kit. Rob explores a small but very rare collection of objects from the cancelled 1940 Tokyo Games while Jeannette finds herself in the Olympic torch room.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lczdrrx57arpnsq9y5cu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815052743+0000" stop="20250815060228+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Begins</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games fast approaching, three of the best gymnasts in the world gear up for the most important year of their lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dkphy5ybiigyfgbdq9oq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815060000+0000" stop="20250815083041+0000">
    <title lang="en">Finals | Cycling BMX | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Cycling BMX Freestyle Finals took place on 31/07/2024 at La Concorde, Paris. In the Women's Final, Deng Yawen (CHN) took the Gold, Perris Benegas (USA) took the Silver, and Natalya Diehm (AUS) took the Bronze. In the Men's Final, Jose Torres Gil (ARG) won Gold, Kieran Darren David Reilly (GBR) won Silver, and Anthony Jeanjean (FRA) won Bronze. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/e7ded2akydmjz2g690sp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815083041+0000" stop="20250815084032+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815084032+0000" stop="20250815090722+0000">
    <title lang="en">From The Top Episode 2: Charlotte Worthington and The Vamps</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic BMX champion Charlotte Worthington meets one of her favourite bands, The Vamps. After attending their concert and hanging our backstage, she invites them for some action at the BMX park. Will they be up for the challenge?  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/z6p6zztovlecfi3dcuhj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815090722+0000" stop="20250815092141+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic Qualifier Series Last Chance to Paris 2024 | BMX Freestyle Budapest</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nikita Ducarroz and Natalya Diehm share friendship and rivalry, while Anthony Jeanjean strategizes and Logan Martin faces disappointment. Jude Jones talks about Olympic ambitions. Emotional highs and lows culminate in heartfelt celebrations and dreams of Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ppct7ocdummbqisc5gyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815092141+0000" stop="20250815093608+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic Qualifier Series Last Chance to Paris 2024 | BMX Freestyle Shanghai </title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch Hannah Roberts striving for gold, Daniel Dhers' spectacular BMX ride, and Queen Villegas' historic journey. Experience the highs, lows, and camaraderie in this thrilling competition. Watch these athletes give their all for a chance to compete in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/shxvi0c6vmhtfase8d2t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815093608+0000" stop="20250815094434+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815094434+0000" stop="20250815114958+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Canoe (C1) Semi-Final &amp; Final | Canoe Slalom | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">This session includes the Semi-Finals for Women's Canoe Slalom . The races took place at Nautical St. White Water, Paris, on 31/07/24.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/eb1rivajuutm73zlz9og"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815114958+0000" stop="20250815121100+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayomide: Born in a canoe, now a Nigerian rowing star | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her mother gave birth to her inside a canoe some 20 years ago. Ayomide Bello grew up to become the first female canoeist from Nigeria to qualify for the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hvr9skjd78d5ohz9hody"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815121100+0000" stop="20250815122318+0000">
    <title lang="en">Daniele Molmenti Cooks with Chef Emanuel Escarello</title>
    <desc lang="en">Italian canoeist champ learns how to prepare a “gold medal” worthy  octopus with chickpeas &amp; saffron</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p2k2lxglqdl6dzzwfi0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815122318+0000" stop="20250815131439+0000">
    <title lang="en">FRA-IRI - Men's Sabre Team Bronze Medal Bout | Fencing | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Sabre Team Bronze Medal Bout between Iran and France took place on 31/07/2024 at the Grand Palais. The French team took the Bronze medal. Final Score FRA 45:25 IRI. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/net3y5ifyp7sqcscph1z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815131439+0000" stop="20250815142831+0000">
    <title lang="en">KOR-HUN - Men's Sabre Team Gold Medal Bout | Fencing | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Sabre Team Gold Medal Bout between The Republic of Korea and Hungary took place on 31/07/2024 at the Grand Palais. The South Korean team took the Gold medal, and the Hungarian one won Silver. Final Score KOR 45:41 HUN. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wrun3fjcmkrfifvywg91"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815142831+0000" stop="20250815143851+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815143851+0000" stop="20250815150424+0000">
    <title lang="en">Fashion Behind The Games: Men</title>
    <desc lang="en">Revisit the most iconic men and how their personal style turned heads at the Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ptjlpuiy2flzgo4qhmqh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815150424+0000" stop="20250815151513+0000">
    <title lang="en">Sports Swap: Karate vs Fencing  with Hiroto Gomyo &amp; Kenta Chida</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can a top Japanese Karate kid fight with a foil? How does a fencer fare when fighting with his feet and hands?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jysrdyn3ut7qvrf3nrhu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815151513+0000" stop="20250815183141+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Individual All-Around Final  | Artistic Gymnastics | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's All-Around Artistic Gymnastics Final took place on 31/07/2024 at the Bercy Arena, Paris. Shinnosuke Oka (JPN) claimed the Gold, Boheng Zhang (CHN) took the Silver, and Ruoteng Xiao (CHN) the Bronze.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ryqm2inx6bckbk6cmeiy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815183141+0000" stop="20250815185832+0000">
    <title lang="en">It’s Not All Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">The off-season allows a brief break from gymnastics for Angelina. Training intensifies for a fired-up Morgan, while Yile reaches breaking point. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/cxnlm5ovbqqdrxxygvtt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815185832+0000" stop="20250815192534+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Interruption</title>
    <desc lang="en">The COVID-19 pandemic rocks the gymnasts’ schedules. The Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games are heartbreakingly postponed. The three gymnasts remain determined to chase their Olympic dreams. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o3p14hxx8rx4v06ujtrz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815192534+0000" stop="20250815201640+0000">
    <title lang="en">All Around | The Tokyo 2020 Journey Ends with Gold</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this final episode of the series All Around, ROC’s Angelina Melnikova revisits the details of her triumph at Tokyo 2020 and looks back at the journey that brought her to win three Olympic medals in artistic gymnastics. USA’s Morgan Hurd and China’s Chen Yile follow the Games from home as they consider their plans for their future in gymnastics and overall life. The episode also looks back at the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games qualifiers.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nfnyf3u9odyuy724ixa5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815201640+0000" stop="20250815230823+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mat 1: Women's -70kg, Men's -90kg Repechages/Semi-Finals/Finals | Judo | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Women's -70kg and Men's -90kg Finals took place on 31/07/2024 at the Champ-de-Mars Arena, Paris.

At the Women's -70kg, Barbara Matic (CRO) claimed the Gold medal, Miriam Butkereit (GER) won the Silver, and the Bronze medals went to Gabriela Willems (BEL) and Michaela Polleres (AUT).

At the Men's -90kg, Lasha Bekauri (GEO) won the Gold medal, Sanshiro Murao (JPN) took the Silver, and the Bronze medals went to Theodoros Tselidis (GRE) and Maxime-Gael Ngayap Hambou (FRA).</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/n9amgizsxreed3be9lbk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250815230823+0000" stop="20250816000141+0000">
    <title lang="en">Transform My Meal: Italy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Four Italian Olympic athletes meet up with world-class chefs in Rome, Udine, Brescia and Piedmont to introduce more variety into their training diet.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/roxs9q6n6goi0aflq9vx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816000141+0000" stop="20250816003604+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's 1500m Freestyle - Final | Swimming | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Women's 1500m Freestyle was held on 31/07/2024 at Paris La Defense Arena. Katie LeDecky (USA) claimed Gold with an Olympic record time of 15:30.02 seconds, Anastasiia Kirpichnikova (FRA) took Silver, and Isabel Gose (GER) completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dhsld5fvfbwdinoyez3b"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816003604+0000" stop="20250816005838+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's 200m Breaststroke - Final | Swimming | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's 200m Breaststroke was held on 31/07/2024 at Paris La Defense Arena. Leon Marchand (FRA) claimed Gold with a new Olympic Record of 2:05.85, Zac Stubblety-Cook (AUS) took Silver and Casper Corbeau (NED) completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hjtgpdtz4gyrvemchnq3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816005838+0000" stop="20250816011700+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's 100m Freestyle - Final | Swimming | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's 100m Freestyle was held on 31/07/2024 at Paris La Defense Arena. Zhanle Pan (CHN) claimed Gold with a new World Record time of 46.40 seconds, Kyle Chalmers (AUS) took Silver, and David Popovici (ROU) completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uo1srdesgxrxnn68narw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816011700+0000" stop="20250816015312+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Julien Alfred, the shoes of Cuba’s wrestling legend, Mexico 1968’s iconic design</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jeannette and Rob discovers Julien Alfred’s kit in The Vault, recently collected at Paris Olympics. The Saint Lucian sprint sensation has overcome many personal challenges to win the first ever gold medal for the Caribbean Island in the 100m final. Rob discovers the magic of a seemingly ordinary dollar bill, in the equestrian community while we learn about the iconic design of Mexico 1968.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mhl2siqoz7uofbgaxony"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816015312+0000" stop="20250816022825+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault: Rebeca Andrade, rare items from the cancelled Tokyo 1940 Games, Olympic torches &amp; swimwear throughout the years</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rebeca Andrade and Simon Biles leotards back-to-back in The Vault take us to the amazing world of gymnastics at the Olympics. We meet the Brazilian queen of gymnastics in training in San Paolo who shared her emotion in dethroning the American legend in the Floor event at Paris 2024 in her sparkling yellow kit. Rob explores a small but very rare collection of objects from the cancelled 1940 Tokyo Games while Jeannette finds herself in the Olympic torch room.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lczdrrx57arpnsq9y5cu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816022825+0000" stop="20250816050716+0000">
    <title lang="en">Finals | Cycling BMX | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Cycling BMX Freestyle Finals took place on 31/07/2024 at La Concorde, Paris. In the Women's Final, Deng Yawen (CHN) took the Gold, Perris Benegas (USA) took the Silver, and Natalya Diehm (AUS) took the Bronze. In the Men's Final, Jose Torres Gil (ARG) won Gold, Kieran Darren David Reilly (GBR) won Silver, and Anthony Jeanjean (FRA) won Bronze. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/e7ded2akydmjz2g690sp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816050716+0000" stop="20250816060242+0000">
    <title lang="en">All Around | The Tokyo 2020 Journey Ends with Gold</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this final episode of the series All Around, ROC’s Angelina Melnikova revisits the details of her triumph at Tokyo 2020 and looks back at the journey that brought her to win three Olympic medals in artistic gymnastics. USA’s Morgan Hurd and China’s Chen Yile follow the Games from home as they consider their plans for their future in gymnastics and overall life. The episode also looks back at the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games qualifiers.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nfnyf3u9odyuy724ixa5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816060000+0000" stop="20250816070646+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Distance | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of an enduring Japanese marathon tradition and a humble champion named Naoko Takahashi who captured her nation’s imagination with a run for the ages at the 2000 Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/t0bphzone9fzs3b5voxe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816070646+0000" stop="20250816102648+0000">
    <title lang="en">Track and Field - Day 9 - Morning | Athletics | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 04/08/2024 at the Stade de France, Paris. It includes the Women's 3000m Steeplechase Round 1, Women's Hammer Throw Qualification - Group A, Women's 200m Round 1, Men's Long Jump Qualification, Women's Hammer Throw Qualification - Group B,Men's 110m Hurdles Round 1, Women's 400m Hurdles Round 1, Men's 400m Round 1</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/v1560868044/primary/mjubgnnakk3lzuxt4xqi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816102648+0000" stop="20250816140839+0000">
    <title lang="en">Track and Field - Day 9 - Afternoon | Athletics | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 04/08/2024 at the Stade de France, Paris. It includes the Finals for Men's 100m, Men's Hammer Throw and Women's Hight Jump, the Semi-Finals for Men's 1500m, Women's 800m, and Men's 100m.
At the Women's High jump Final, the Gold was claimed by Yaroslava Mahuchikh (UKR), Nicola Olyslagers (AUS) took the Silver, and the Bronze went to Iryna Gerashchenko (UKR) and Eleanor Patterson (AUS).
At the Men's Hammer Throw Final, Ethan Katzberg (CAN) took the Gold, while Bence Halasz (HUN) claimed the Silver, and Mykhaylo Kokhan (UKR) won the Bronze. 
Finally, at the Men's 100m Final the Gold medal was claimed by Noah Lyles (USA), while the Silver went to Kishane Thompson (JAM) and the Bronze was taken by Fred Kerley (USA).</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/v1560769087/primary/lmoou5z5xind5vgxm8mr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816140839+0000" stop="20250816162324+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Final | Triathlon | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Triathlon Final took place on day five of the Olympic Games Paris 2024 at Pont Alexandre III on July 31, 2024 in Paris, France.

Alex Yee (GBR) won Gold, Hayden Wilde (NZL) won Silver and Leo Bergere (FRA) won Bronze.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ct2zezllghyyzmadhlrj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816162324+0000" stop="20250816194558+0000">
    <title lang="en">Track and Field - Day 10 - Morning | Athletics | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Track and Field Day 10 Morning Session took place at the Stade de France, France, on 05/08/24. It included Men´s  400m Hurdles Round 1, Men´s Discus Throw Qualification - Group A and B, Women´s Pole Vault Qualification, Women´s 400m Hurdles Repechage Round, Men´s 400m Repechage Round, Women´s 400m Round 1 and Women´s 200m Repechage Round.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ezvsbhdbb8pjlvmqzane"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816194558+0000" stop="20250816234938+0000">
    <title lang="en">Track and Field - Day 10 - Afternoon | Athletics | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Track and Field Day 10 Afternoon Session took place at the Stade de France, France, on 05/08/24. It included the Finals for:
Men´s Pole Vault, in which Armand Duplantis (SWE) claimed the Gold, while the Silver went to Sam Kendricks (USA) and the Bronze, to Emmanouil Karalis (GRE). 
Women's Discus Throw, where we saw Valarie Allman (USA) won the Gold medal, Feng Bin (CHN) won the Silver and Sandra Elkasevic (CRO) took the Bronze.  
Women's 5000m, where Beatrice Chebet (KEN) claimed Gold and Team mate Faith Kipyegon (KEN) Silver, while the Bronze went to Sifan Hassan (NED).
And at the Women's 800m Final, Keely Hodgkisnon (GBR) won the Gold, Tsige Duguma (ETH) Silver, and Mary Moraa (KEN) the Bronze.  
The session also included Men's 3000 Steeplechase Round 1, Men's 200m Round 1, and the Women's 200m Semi-Final.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/f9gok5ytpacjir5moalm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250816234938+0000" stop="20250817005544+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Distance | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of an enduring Japanese marathon tradition and a humble champion named Naoko Takahashi who captured her nation’s imagination with a run for the ages at the 2000 Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/t0bphzone9fzs3b5voxe"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
