<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-05-12 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240511222359+0000" stop="20240512021840+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Combined Finals  - Climbing | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 05/08/2021 at the Aomi Urban Sports Park, Tokyo. It includes the Men's Combined - Speed, Bouldering and Lead Finals and the Victory Ceremony. Gines Lopez (ESP) claimed Gold. Coleman (USA) Silver and Schubert (AUT) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zqzwyvcry7sji2nmnyfw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512021840+0000" stop="20240512023315+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Adrien Raza, the godfather of urban skimboarding | Urbanity</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adrien Raza is a unique and talented skimboarder, who has taken the urban skimboarding scene by storm. From fountains to ramps to stairs, he skims it all!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wzcxc4qrh1xcuo46jcde"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512023315+0000" stop="20240512024328+0000">
    <title lang="en">Johan Tonnoir: parkour’s force of nature | Urbanity</title>
    <desc lang="en">Johan Tonnoir, an athlete and artist who uses Paris’ architecture to defy gravity and who is taking free running to a whole new level.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rkemnahsx2vgafhgvlnn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512024328+0000" stop="20240512030003+0000">
    <title lang="en">From NYC to Alaska, meet the pioneers and US champion | Breaking Life </title>
    <desc lang="en">As the birthplace of a global hip-hop movement, we meet some of the pioneers of Breaking in New-York City. While Kid Glyde shares his passion for breaking with the next generation at his Harlem studio, three thousand miles away in Anchorage Alaska, B-Boy Icey Ives, two-time US national champion, melts the ice with his local crew Frozen Flow while being a community leader, a teacher and a role model for the youth living in extremely challenging conditions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dovd8hi3ceymcdhls5v8"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512030003+0000" stop="20240512031845+0000">
    <title lang="en">French breakers set the scene for Paris 2024 Olympic Games| Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">France is a cultural melting pot. It’s also one of the biggest countries for Breaking with more than a thousand battles every year and some of the greatest international competitions. It’s also in Paris 2024 that Breaking will make its Olympic debut.
Dany Dann came to France from French Guyana to pursue a life in dance. Now, he juggles early morning shifts as a nurse, daily training and being a father – always with an eye on the next battle. Now reigning national champion, he trains with French national team members B-Girl Carlota and B-Boy Marlone for the WDSF World Breaking Championship in Paris.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/amx9sswjndootv2aps3j"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512031845+0000" stop="20240512033724+0000">
    <title lang="en">Young breakers take over the streets of Medellin | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">Colombia used to be one of the most dangerous countries in the world but has found new life through a revival in urban arts, becoming a global creative mecca. 
B-Girl Luma and 4Eskuela hip hop school, where she learnt Breaking and is now a teacher, have been instrumental to this change in Medellin (Colombia). But it’s not been an easy journey for Luma who also had her doubts about what she can really achieve through dancing. By winning international dance events around the world, she is now confident it gave her a career and a drive, also when teaching young kids in her neighbourhood. She is keen to participate to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iddfhrgah2b2pkoabbbd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512033724+0000" stop="20240512060221+0000">
    <title lang="en">Racing Quarter-Finals - Cycling BMX | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">this event took place on 29/07/2021 at the Ariake Urban Sports Park and includes the Women's and Men's Quarterfinals.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/az0ayhsufadoqa7oi0ra"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512060000+0000" stop="20240512061956+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s growing breaking scene makes room for B-Girls | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s Breaking scene started in the early 2000’s and has since exploded in popularity. While mostly male dominated, women are increasingly accepted and celebrated in the Indian Breaking scene.
We meet B-Girl Jo, the two-time BC One India champion from Bangalore, as she travels alone to Mumbai. There, she meets her friend Flying Machine who organizes a community celebration event where B-Girls have a chance to battle it out. As a leader for Indian female hip-hop dancers, Jo reflects on her position in the society. With her own hip-hop and yoga studio and inspired by the challenges she’s already had to overcome, she examines her journey with both excitement and wisdom.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/njacmonn1ac4hzxkqjo0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512061956+0000" stop="20240512063917+0000">
    <title lang="en">Dakar breakers see new opportunities with Olympic debut| Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a classical and traditional African dance background, B-Boy Zaza is a key member of Power Crew, one of the most successful crew in Senegal. Joined by his young brother Emma, their crew is more like a family and made them travel to major global events. Now a teacher, tasked with navigating the challenges of his community, the dance gives him hope for a brighter future. With Paris 2024 and Dakar Youth Olympic Games in 2026, the elders and next generation alike to build their own future and for the sport as it takes roots in Senegal. Organized by the local dance federation, they participate in the Battle National, featuring some of Senegal’s best emerging talents. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/udhmfruynxxufbeoi4pc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512063917+0000" stop="20240512082141+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mixed Teams Finals - Breaking | Buenos Aires 2018 YOG</title>
    <desc lang="en">Held at the Parque Mujeres Argentinas, the finals of the Mixed Team Breaking competition.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fqcualf7l72bktgnrizg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512082141+0000" stop="20240512111435+0000">
    <title lang="en">Freestyle Park Finals - Cycling BMX | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 01/08/2021 at the Ariake Urban Sports Park and includes the Women's and Men's Park Finals ans their Victory Ceremonies. Charlotte Worthington (GBR) won Gold in the Women's final, and Logan Martin (AUS) took the Gold medal in the Men's final.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/crp3hal8mgwe8gsld7ga"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512111435+0000" stop="20240512112757+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512112757+0000" stop="20240512121449+0000">
    <title lang="en">Original Fuel (Film)</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the former Soviet Union, athletes representing young republics have forged their own path to DIY training and Olympic success.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wnuf385kiaaf0rx6mbby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512121449+0000" stop="20240512171824+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Street - Skateboarding | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 26/07/2021 at the Ariake Urban Sports Park, Tokio. It includes the Women's Street Prelims Heats and Finals as well as the Victory Ceremony. Nishiya (JPN) claimed the Gold, Leal (BRA) the Silver and Nakayama (JPN) completed the podium </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hphji0lbjie757rmmtxe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512171824+0000" stop="20240512210743+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Park  - Skateboarding | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 05/08/2021 at the Ariake Urban Sports Park, Tokio. It includes the Men's Park Prelims Heats and Finals as well as the Victory Ceremony. Palmer (AUS) claimed the Gold, Barros (BRA) Silver and Juneau (USA) completed the podiu</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/v1654086099/primary/dsp4cnmciyqfoyblclv6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512210743+0000" stop="20240512211826+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Skateboard Lesson | Sky Brown and Yungblud | From the Top</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sky Brown and Yungblud meet up in Venice Beach, CA, where Sky shows off her athletic prowess and gives Yungblud a lesson in skateboarding basics. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qeeuumukdruyyoxnbwwn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512211826+0000" stop="20240512213009+0000">
    <title lang="en">In Concert | Sky Brown and Yungblud | From the Top</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yungblud leads Sky to a nearby venue where he and his band perform a private concert for her, the first rock concert Sky has ever attended in her life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xv0edlwsbk3ykipgdsvc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512213009+0000" stop="20240512213910+0000">
    <title lang="en">Inspiring a Generation | Sky Brown and Yungblud | From the Top</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sky and Yungblud compare notes on their lives and careers and quickly become friends. Both being inspirational voices for the young generations.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dv0dbgpponfuddtth0gj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512213910+0000" stop="20240512214653+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512214653+0000" stop="20240512214756+0000">
    <title lang="en">Unleash the New | Trailer</title>
    <desc lang="en">Five athletes from the new Olympic and Paralympic sports found their calling through joy, freedom and friendships. Now they are stepping up to represent the sport and community they love on the greatest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q7bre1rmvlotqn6n4vln"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240512214756+0000" stop="20240513020541+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Combined Finals  - Climbing | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 06/08/2021 at the Aomi Urban Sports Park, Tokyo. It includes the Women's Combined - Speed, Bouldering and Lead Finals and the Victory Ceremony. Garnbret (SLO) claimed Gold, Nonaka (JPN) Silver and Noguchi (JPN) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ijtcemla7qimf0nmkzxn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513020541+0000" stop="20240513052015+0000">
    <title lang="en">Racing Semi-Finals &amp; Finals - Cycling BMX | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 30/07/2021 at the Ariake Urban Sports Park and includes the Women's and Men's Semifinals, Finals and their Victory Ceremonies. In the Women's final, Bethany Shriever (GBR) won Gold, Mariana Pajón (COL) Silver, and Merel Smulders (NED) Bronze. In the Men's final, Niek Kimmann (NED) took the Gold medal, Kye Whyte (GBR) Silver and Carlos Alberto Ramírez Yepes completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zhldamqmr562emoxt2sr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513052015+0000" stop="20240513060240+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teahupo'o Surf Camp | Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrills and spills as seven surfers join an ISA surf camp at Teahupo'o, Tahiti's famed surf spot and the surfing venue for the Olympic Games Paris 2024. Determined to conquer the Olympic wave, they face their fears, push the boundaries and challenge the raw power of nature.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jgfybidumyctl4uc7lvu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513060000+0000" stop="20240513061653+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ornella: knocking down social prejudices pursuing her Olympic dream | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the first female boxer to represent her country, Ornella shows us why it’s important for the world to see more female African boxers on the global stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dob7vauikkp9fiqjge6t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513061653+0000" stop="20240513062237+0000">
    <title lang="en">Neymar at age 17</title>
    <desc lang="en">Neymar had only just turned professional in 2009 but his outstanding talent ensured he was expected to become a Brazil football legend.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ztbpfpjhtxy2qkr3piqt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513062237+0000" stop="20240513062919+0000">
    <title lang="en">Veronica Campbell-Brown at age 18</title>
    <desc lang="en">Veronica Campbell-Brown's schooling in her hometown of Clarendon, Jamaica brought discipline and the inspiration to become a sprint legend.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kf3fpmgapukukflnc1nb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513062919+0000" stop="20240513064024+0000">
    <title lang="en">Novak Djokovic at age 21</title>
    <desc lang="en">A day in the life of a 21-year-old Novak Djokovic when he was living and training in Monte Carlo.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lphh4ogo1ulvajfi8qmk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513064024+0000" stop="20240513065658+0000">
    <title lang="en">Former Olympic boxing hopeful looks to make history as a trans fighter</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Manuel returned to competition after transitioning. Can he find challengers to return to the top?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxmwzznjswsx6mj63j0t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513065658+0000" stop="20240513071214+0000">
    <title lang="en">This transgender volleyball player’s path leads to an NCAA women’s team</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow Chloe Anderson as she heads to UC-Santa Cruz and meets her new team-mates for the first time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b0ohi1tpvn8gq1mn16yx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513071214+0000" stop="20240513102019+0000">
    <title lang="en">Quarter Finals, Semi Finals &amp; Finals - Day 11 - Morning Session - Boxing | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 03/08/2021 at the Kokugikan Arena, Tokyo. It includes  the Women's Feather (54-57kg) Final and Victory Ceremony, Quarterfinals of the Women's Light (57-60kg), Men's Fly (48-52kg) and Men's Light (57-63kg) Weight class as well as a Men's Feather (52-57kg) and Men's Heavy (81-91kg) Semifinal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bchnupa2qodr8cwgdtlz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513102019+0000" stop="20240513121510+0000">
    <title lang="en">ESP v USA - Men's Quarter-Final - Basketball | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This Men's Quarterfinal Game took place on 03/08/2021 at the Saitama Super Arena, Saitama. Final Score USA 95:81 ESP</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ofi43xh6zitfkfga9tzk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513121510+0000" stop="20240513151108+0000">
    <title lang="en">MEX v BRA - Men's Semi-Final - Football | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This match took place on 03/08/2021 at the Ibaraki Kashima Stadium, Kashima. Final Score BRA 4:1 MEX (PSO)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vfzb4k59tumcjkvh2mkw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513151108+0000" stop="20240513173856+0000">
    <title lang="en">LAT v CAN &amp; CAN v AUS - Women's Quarter-Finals - Beach Volleyball | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event tookplace on 03/08/2021 at the Shiokaze Park, Tokyo. It includes the Women's Quarterfinal Matches Graudina/Kravcenoka (LAT) v Bansely/Brandie (CAN) &amp; Pavan/Melissa (CAN) v Artacho Del Solar/Clancy (AUS)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gge6zd9gs56da42ivnbb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513173856+0000" stop="20240513175603+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ornella: knocking down social prejudices pursuing her Olympic dream | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the first female boxer to represent her country, Ornella shows us why it’s important for the world to see more female African boxers on the global stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dob7vauikkp9fiqjge6t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513175603+0000" stop="20240513180115+0000">
    <title lang="en">Neymar at age 17</title>
    <desc lang="en">Neymar had only just turned professional in 2009 but his outstanding talent ensured he was expected to become a Brazil football legend.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ztbpfpjhtxy2qkr3piqt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513180115+0000" stop="20240513181222+0000">
    <title lang="en">Novak Djokovic at age 21</title>
    <desc lang="en">A day in the life of a 21-year-old Novak Djokovic when he was living and training in Monte Carlo.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lphh4ogo1ulvajfi8qmk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513181222+0000" stop="20240513182824+0000">
    <title lang="en">Former Olympic boxing hopeful looks to make history as a trans fighter</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pat Manuel returned to competition after transitioning. Can he find challengers to return to the top?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxmwzznjswsx6mj63j0t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513182824+0000" stop="20240513184513+0000">
    <title lang="en">This transgender volleyball player’s path leads to an NCAA women’s team</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow Chloe Anderson as she heads to UC-Santa Cruz and meets her new team-mates for the first time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b0ohi1tpvn8gq1mn16yx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513184513+0000" stop="20240513202546+0000">
    <title lang="en">SWE v ESP - Men's Quarter-Final - Handball | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This Men's Quarterfinal Match took place on 03/08/2021 at the Yoyogi National Stadium, Tokyo. Final Score ESP 34:33 SWE</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pndsrr1owdjlc54ukmtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513202546+0000" stop="20240513230931+0000">
    <title lang="en">NED v HUN &amp; AUS v ROC - Women's Quarter-Finals - Water Polo | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">These Women's Quarterfinal Matches were played on 03/08/2021 at the Tatsumi Water Polo Centre, Tastumi.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/umyi9wgvdo4kv9nmynmu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240513230931+0000" stop="20240514015704+0000">
    <title lang="en">POL v FRA- Men's Quarter-Final - Volleyball | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Men's Quarterfinal Match between Poland and France  took place on 03/08/2021 at the Ariake Arena, Tokyo. Fial Score FRA 3: 2 POL</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lbvvwxwuiqpwq0bjdp2x"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
