<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-12-28 00:00:02">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20241227232719+0000" stop="20241228033327+0000">
    <title lang="en">Team Event, Day 2 - Figure Skating | PyeongChang 2018 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">The event - featuring short dance, women's short program and pairs free skating - was held at the Gangneung Ice Arena on 11 February 2018.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vgglguvhpa80ocm6ihhp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20241228033327+0000" stop="20241228041105+0000">
    <title lang="en">We Are One</title>
    <desc lang="en">This documentary tells the story of the emotional journey of how the Unified Korean Team came to be and its legacy.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/akzvwfvydwr66qu0kpvv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20241228041105+0000" stop="20241228043946+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Malaysia’s first Olympic figure skater made history in PyeongChang</title>
    <desc lang="en">The emotional full story of how Julian Yee trained in a Malaysian mall in order to make history at the 2018 Olympic Winter Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/so9kufixpjeojq26ojuo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20241228043946+0000" stop="20241228050956+0000">
    <title lang="en">From The Top Episode 4: Nathan Chen and Hayley Kiyoko</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic figure skater Nathan Chen meets music star Hayley Kiyoko. She runs him through the choreography for one of her tracks, before they hit the ice-skating rink and attempt to implement the new choreography moves to surprising results. Hayley and Nathan also discuss their community responsibilities and open up about what it means for them to be Asian American role models. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nk7oeipa8e2estkb6gz4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20241228050956+0000" stop="20241228053518+0000">
    <title lang="en">Vancouver 2010 Historical Flashback: Speed Skating Men's 1500m</title>
    <desc lang="en">Before going to Vancouver 2010 we have a quick look back at Lillehammer 1994</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mpoqa9hhfafo3fm1ay9k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20241228053518+0000" stop="20241228060227+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Ends with Triumph at Beijing 2022 | On Edge</title>
    <desc lang="en">This special extra episode of On Edge, chronicles the Beijing 2022 experience of our six teams as their months of training and preparation culminates in success for all of them in the Olympic Ice Dance competition.

Filmed in the last six months leading up to Beijing 2022, On Edge is the Olympic Channel’s first weekly figure skating reality docuseries featuring athletes Madison Chock and Evan Bates (USA), Gabriella Papadakis and Guillaume Cizeron (FRA), Madison Hubbell and Zach Donohue (USA), Olivia Smart and Adrian Diaz (ESP), Laurence Fournier-Beaudry and Nikolaj Sorensen (CAN), Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson (GBR), and coaches Marie-France Dubreuil and Patrice Lauzon, Romain Haguenauer and three time Olympic Gold medallist Scott Moir.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/tudhaqahlx5k55uthvw8"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
