<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-08-01 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240731235539+0000" stop="20240801000313+0000">
    <title lang="en">Jeanette gets to hold Cathy Freeman spikes from Sydney 2000 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">As they continue travelling in time in ‘The Vault’, Jeanette is taken to the Running Shoes Collection. She discovers the oldest spikes from the 19th century and is handed over Cathy Freeman’s shoes from Sydney 2000, when she won Gold in the 400 meters. Patricia, the Collections Manager, explains her how special the colours of those shoes are. Then we get to hear from Cathy herself how special was that night in Sydney for her whole nation. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yokv9gsbu6bxiowzbx7c"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801000313+0000" stop="20240801000916+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘Robin Hood’ caught on camera for the first at Tokyo 2020 | The Vault </title>
    <desc lang="en">Archer specialists say one chance in few thousands but on camera it is the first time ever a ‘Robin Hood’ shot is recorded live! Now on public display, Greg discovers this rare artefact with Stephanie, one of the Museum curators. Shot by the Korean pair, An San and Kim Je-deok in the mixed event, they won Gold in that first-ever event at the Olympics. An san went on winning three Gold medals in Tokyo, demonstrating the dominance of South Korea in this discipline. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zt0pl5oeg7r70znej4eg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801000916+0000" stop="20240801002403+0000">
    <title lang="en">Forging India’s Badminton Champions | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head to the hustle of Hyderabad to meet India’s badminton legend Pullela Gopichand and hear of his champion-building dream. Insights from legends such as Saina Nehwal, Sai Praneeth and Kidambi Srikanth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmvup5pj6r0yeet7vupe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801002403+0000" stop="20240801004156+0000">
    <title lang="en">Youth take Centre Stage | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head behind the scenes and hang out with of some of India’s rising badminton talent.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/m7g04law6ojlfsbbjc8s"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801004156+0000" stop="20240801021341+0000">
    <title lang="en">The People’s Fighters | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">The powerful story of how a revolutionary boxing experiment produced Teofilo Stevenson and a legacy of Cuban success at the Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/n57vgpifgvxtrgl2eg5o"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801021341+0000" stop="20240801024318+0000">
    <title lang="en">It’s Not All Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">The off-season allows a brief break from gymnastics for Angelina. Training intensifies for a fired-up Morgan, while Yile reaches breaking point. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/cxnlm5ovbqqdrxxygvtt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801024318+0000" stop="20240801031325+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Interruption</title>
    <desc lang="en">The COVID-19 pandemic rocks the gymnasts’ schedules. The Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games are heartbreakingly postponed. The three gymnasts remain determined to chase their Olympic dreams. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o3p14hxx8rx4v06ujtrz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801031325+0000" stop="20240801040920+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : The story of the torch</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 3 : The Olympic spirit : The story of the torch.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/d9hqaosoc2lciqdjhidc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801040920+0000" stop="20240801050408+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 2 : The Olympic spirit : De Coubertin's vision, the early modern games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/oxtlxdyhszwe4fvoseos"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801050408+0000" stop="20240801060239+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can NBA and Dream Team star Laettner teach this team to win?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team USA and NBA legend Christian Laettner shows the Garinger High School varsity basketball team how they can improve their game.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/isyf33697ado3urpz3i0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801060000+0000" stop="20240801065402+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rise of Women Olympians</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 1 : The story of Women at the Games, Rise of Women Olympians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxcua384ycbgx9v2zjyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801065402+0000" stop="20240801070627+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801070627+0000" stop="20240801071802+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Girl India aims for historic gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow India's remarkable journey from hometown studio of La Hague to the Olympic stage. While she qualified for the Games at the European Championships, with her unique style blending raw energy and finesse, she faces formidable rivals on her quest for breaking glory. Will her unmatched determination and skill make history at the Olympics where the sport is making its debut at Paris 2024?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fgps2zdjfhlhkjt0cnid"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801071802+0000" stop="20240801073205+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kauli Vaast’s Tahitian roots make him a favourite for Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Witness Kauli Vaast's journey from his childhood Tahitian shores to the world stage. Surrounded by his family and long time friend and mentor Jeremy Flores, he refines his craft at Teahupo'o impressive pipe where he will compete on hometurf for an Olympic Gold medal in surfing. Driven by passion and cheered on by those who believe in his dream, he balances the thrill of competition with the warmth of a unique community.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/atn7hr8mywzvlqx35qmf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801073205+0000" stop="20240801074242+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801074242+0000" stop="20240801075418+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801075418+0000" stop="20240801080420+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801080420+0000" stop="20240801081134+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801081134+0000" stop="20240801082148+0000">
    <title lang="en">World Cup winner from Argentinian football dynasty | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a father, uncle and two older brothers all professionals, Alexis Mac Allister was destined for a life in football. All three brothers even achieved their dream of playing on the same team for Argentinos Juniors, which saw young Maradona starts his legendary career and played with their father in the late 70’s. As a very fine member of this Argentinian football dynasty, Mac Allister is aiming to weave his midfield magic at the World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/scynz4fdr9pfdyi28oq1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801082148+0000" stop="20240801083107+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801083107+0000" stop="20240801084205+0000">
    <title lang="en">The New-Zealand striker who made his dreams come true | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">As one of only six kiwis to ever to play in Premier League, Chris Wood has achieved more than he could have ever imagined. Schooled by his football playing sister, Chris moved to England at the age of 15 and made his Premier League debut at 17. After a challenging period of loan moves, Wood met success with Millwall and a personal achievement at London 2012. Now a regular striker at Newcastle United, Wood’s New Zealand has just missed out on World Cup qualification. Arguably the nation’s greatest ever player, he has sights set on another great stage, Paris 2024 where he would be participating in the Olympics for the 3rd time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b60painhtemnajlhqfs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801084205+0000" stop="20240801085014+0000">
    <title lang="en">Talented midfielder Louza sets hope for Paris 2024 | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">The talented midfielder from Watford was desperately unlucky and suffered ligament damage ruling him out of the World Cup selection for Morocco. A product of Nantes F.C. football academy, he joined the UK Premier League as well as debuting and scoring at his first game with the national team. At just 23, he now sets his hopes on Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jpojslmkvpt1kli3bnhd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801085014+0000" stop="20240801090423+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs weightlifting with Shimizu Satoshi &amp; Takao Hiroaki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Olympic boxing bronze medallist snatch 40 kg on his first attempt? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxffrstaqlasgzgnrqtc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801090423+0000" stop="20240801091904+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs race walk with Kanie Miki &amp; Tanii Takayuki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a race walk champion tries to shoot an arrow?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qy9tevadjqoobtb1haoo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801091904+0000" stop="20240801092205+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Japan's 16-year-old sport climbing sensation | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mori Ai started climbing walls when she was eight.  After competing and winning the World Championships, she is focused on being one of the world's top climbers. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iyvfdf4j6tv9v6r0iyyb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801092205+0000" stop="20240801092507+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Japan's table tennis belongs to this 13-year-old prodigy | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Harimoto Miwa's older brother Tomokazu has been the face of Japanese table tennis. Still, he is not the only Harimoto shouldering the hopes of a nation as Miwa is making a name of her own. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlq8b9bzzojdlziqbks1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801092507+0000" stop="20240801092803+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801092803+0000" stop="20240801093051+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093051+0000" stop="20240801093348+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093348+0000" stop="20240801093608+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093608+0000" stop="20240801093801+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801093801+0000" stop="20240801094154+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801094154+0000" stop="20240801101138+0000">
    <title lang="en">Netherlands’ Pieter van den Hoogenband (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dutch swimming legend Pieter van den Hoogenband won seven Olympic medals. Now, he’s helping others swim their fastest. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxt20vauetnhtdxbhvn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801101138+0000" stop="20240801103947+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801103947+0000" stop="20240801104406+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801104406+0000" stop="20240801113641+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801113641+0000" stop="20240801114727+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801114727+0000" stop="20240801115720+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801115720+0000" stop="20240801120255+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japan’s historic 4x100m team trades Beijing bronze for reallocated silver</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 2008, the Japanese men’s relay team won their country’s first-ever men’s Olympic medal on the track. But after the first-place Jamaican squad forfeited their gold due to a doping violation, Naoki Tsukahara, Shingo Suetsugu, Shinji Takahira and Nobuharu Asahara moved up to silver.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ms9z8dqi2lp0ldrwexb4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801120255+0000" stop="20240801121059+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801121059+0000" stop="20240801121651+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801121651+0000" stop="20240801122153+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801122153+0000" stop="20240801122651+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801122651+0000" stop="20240801123337+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801123337+0000" stop="20240801124038+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801124038+0000" stop="20240801125405+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801125405+0000" stop="20240801130535+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801130535+0000" stop="20240801131701+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801131701+0000" stop="20240801132916+0000">
    <title lang="en">Lyla Nourtier: you can succeed - France / Weighlifting I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lyla is a 15 year old weightlifter  from a small village in France without much access to sports. We meet her at a turning point in her life as she plans to leave home to pursue her dream. She joins an elite sport and education program where she is the first ever female weightlifter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjzbaetxwitdiurxb4av"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801132916+0000" stop="20240801133828+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can imagining success actually help you achieve it? | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Learn how these visualization techniques practiced by some of the world’s greatest Olympians could help you overcome the challenges in your day to day life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u7lyx1vw3goxwe3xgnto"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801133828+0000" stop="20240801141037+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801141037+0000" stop="20240801141713+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a pioneering Egyptian swimmer broke boundaries and inspired the world</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Golden Fish”, Rania Elwani tells how her determination as an Olympic swimmer was matched only by her commitment to peruse her career as a doctor.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uvbg6uso2jsmt7irbn32"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801141713+0000" stop="20240801142242+0000">
    <title lang="en">How an Olympic champion swimmer almost drowned at London 1948</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Sinking Dream”, Greta Andersen shares how her quest for a second gold was cut short when she blacked. But it didn’t define her career.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/clebcrcrrpzrvirw3vsf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801142242+0000" stop="20240801151611+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic and Arsenal legend save a football team from relegation?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cameroon &amp; Arsenal football legend Lauren coaches a struggling amateur league team from East London. Will he help them avoid relegation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rqfkn2zfzfgwog1hgosj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801151611+0000" stop="20240801161055+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Jackie Silva get this Brazilian volleyball team to defeat their rival?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian Olympic gold medalist Jackie Silva lends her expertise to a Rio indoor volleyball team as they try to win their first event ever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mwcu5tq4upkl1jm6icfc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801161055+0000" stop="20240801170258+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Triathlon, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brothers Alistair and Jonny Brownlee race against the world's best in the 2012 Olympic men's triathlon. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ix1a4g7jedfs5yoeic2m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801170258+0000" stop="20240801171115+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801171115+0000" stop="20240801171629+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801171629+0000" stop="20240801172319+0000">
    <title lang="en">World Cup winner from Argentinian football dynasty | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a father, uncle and two older brothers all professionals, Alexis Mac Allister was destined for a life in football. All three brothers even achieved their dream of playing on the same team for Argentinos Juniors, which saw young Maradona starts his legendary career and played with their father in the late 70’s. As a very fine member of this Argentinian football dynasty, Mac Allister is aiming to weave his midfield magic at the World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/scynz4fdr9pfdyi28oq1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801172319+0000" stop="20240801172913+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801172913+0000" stop="20240801173618+0000">
    <title lang="en">The New-Zealand striker who made his dreams come true | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">As one of only six kiwis to ever to play in Premier League, Chris Wood has achieved more than he could have ever imagined. Schooled by his football playing sister, Chris moved to England at the age of 15 and made his Premier League debut at 17. After a challenging period of loan moves, Wood met success with Millwall and a personal achievement at London 2012. Now a regular striker at Newcastle United, Wood’s New Zealand has just missed out on World Cup qualification. Arguably the nation’s greatest ever player, he has sights set on another great stage, Paris 2024 where he would be participating in the Olympics for the 3rd time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b60painhtemnajlhqfs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801173618+0000" stop="20240801174211+0000">
    <title lang="en">Talented midfielder Louza sets hope for Paris 2024 | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">The talented midfielder from Watford was desperately unlucky and suffered ligament damage ruling him out of the World Cup selection for Morocco. A product of Nantes F.C. football academy, he joined the UK Premier League as well as debuting and scoring at his first game with the national team. At just 23, he now sets his hopes on Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jpojslmkvpt1kli3bnhd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801174211+0000" stop="20240801175409+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs weightlifting with Shimizu Satoshi &amp; Takao Hiroaki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Olympic boxing bronze medallist snatch 40 kg on his first attempt? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxffrstaqlasgzgnrqtc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801175409+0000" stop="20240801180432+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs race walk with Kanie Miki &amp; Tanii Takayuki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a race walk champion tries to shoot an arrow?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qy9tevadjqoobtb1haoo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801180432+0000" stop="20240801180733+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Japan's 16-year-old sport climbing sensation | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mori Ai started climbing walls when she was eight.  After competing and winning the World Championships, she is focused on being one of the world's top climbers. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iyvfdf4j6tv9v6r0iyyb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801180733+0000" stop="20240801181035+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Japan's table tennis belongs to this 13-year-old prodigy | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Harimoto Miwa's older brother Tomokazu has been the face of Japanese table tennis. Still, he is not the only Harimoto shouldering the hopes of a nation as Miwa is making a name of her own. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlq8b9bzzojdlziqbks1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801181035+0000" stop="20240801190258+0000">
    <title lang="en">Speed and grace</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 2 : The story of Women at the Games, Speed and grace.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zzs8tfcep2xnog47vvcj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801190258+0000" stop="20240801190754+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801190754+0000" stop="20240801191042+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801191042+0000" stop="20240801191340+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801191340+0000" stop="20240801191855+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801191855+0000" stop="20240801192411+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801192411+0000" stop="20240801192835+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801192835+0000" stop="20240801195632+0000">
    <title lang="en">Netherlands’ Pieter van den Hoogenband (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dutch swimming legend Pieter van den Hoogenband won seven Olympic medals. Now, he’s helping others swim their fastest. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxt20vauetnhtdxbhvn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801195632+0000" stop="20240801202232+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801202232+0000" stop="20240801203102+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801203102+0000" stop="20240801212237+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801212237+0000" stop="20240801213618+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801213618+0000" stop="20240801215143+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801215143+0000" stop="20240801220127+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japan’s historic 4x100m team trades Beijing bronze for reallocated silver</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 2008, the Japanese men’s relay team won their country’s first-ever men’s Olympic medal on the track. But after the first-place Jamaican squad forfeited their gold due to a doping violation, Naoki Tsukahara, Shingo Suetsugu, Shinji Takahira and Nobuharu Asahara moved up to silver.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ms9z8dqi2lp0ldrwexb4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801220127+0000" stop="20240801221556+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801221556+0000" stop="20240801222448+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801222448+0000" stop="20240801223208+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801223208+0000" stop="20240801223902+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801223902+0000" stop="20240801224615+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801224615+0000" stop="20240801225407+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801225407+0000" stop="20240801230826+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801230826+0000" stop="20240801232239+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801232239+0000" stop="20240801233647+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801233647+0000" stop="20240801235145+0000">
    <title lang="en">Lyla Nourtier: you can succeed - France / Weighlifting I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lyla is a 15 year old weightlifter  from a small village in France without much access to sports. We meet her at a turning point in her life as she plans to leave home to pursue her dream. She joins an elite sport and education program where she is the first ever female weightlifter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjzbaetxwitdiurxb4av"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240801235145+0000" stop="20240802000254+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can imagining success actually help you achieve it? | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Learn how these visualization techniques practiced by some of the world’s greatest Olympians could help you overcome the challenges in your day to day life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u7lyx1vw3goxwe3xgnto"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802000254+0000" stop="20240802001217+0000">
    <title lang="en">The inspiring story of the first woman to win an Olympic gold for Australia</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Lithgow Flash”, Marjorie Jackson recalls her early training leading up to two gold medals in 1952 and her life upon returning home.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o8wxabyggsnakkhbjl9m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802001217+0000" stop="20240802002202+0000">
    <title lang="en">The incredible story of the orphan who made it to the Olympic podium</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Game of Life”, Kriss Akabusi shares how he discovered running in the British Army and what it felt like to win silver in LA1984.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zhkr0twlijswtrgjx9ts"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802002202+0000" stop="20240802003349+0000">
    <title lang="en">The story of the basketball legend who never gave up on her Olympic dream</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Queen”, Brazilian legend Hortencia Marcari explains why she came out of retirement only months after giving birth. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fr0u01e6bgquep8bxo8k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802003349+0000" stop="20240802004025+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a pioneering Egyptian swimmer broke boundaries and inspired the world</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Golden Fish”, Rania Elwani tells how her determination as an Olympic swimmer was matched only by her commitment to peruse her career as a doctor.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uvbg6uso2jsmt7irbn32"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802004025+0000" stop="20240802004348+0000">
    <title lang="en">How an Olympic champion swimmer almost drowned at London 1948</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Sinking Dream”, Greta Andersen shares how her quest for a second gold was cut short when she blacked. But it didn’t define her career.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/clebcrcrrpzrvirw3vsf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802004348+0000" stop="20240802013718+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic and Arsenal legend save a football team from relegation?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cameroon &amp; Arsenal football legend Lauren coaches a struggling amateur league team from East London. Will he help them avoid relegation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rqfkn2zfzfgwog1hgosj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802013718+0000" stop="20240802022855+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Jackie Silva get this Brazilian volleyball team to defeat their rival?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian Olympic gold medalist Jackie Silva lends her expertise to a Rio indoor volleyball team as they try to win their first event ever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mwcu5tq4upkl1jm6icfc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802022855+0000" stop="20240802032622+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Triathlon, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brothers Alistair and Jonny Brownlee race against the world's best in the 2012 Olympic men's triathlon. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ix1a4g7jedfs5yoeic2m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802032622+0000" stop="20240802042018+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802042018+0000" stop="20240802043209+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs Cricket with Vikas Krishan Yadav and Harbhajan Singh | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can a boxer bat? And does a bowler have the power and precision to throw a punch? India’s cricket legend Harbhajan Singh swaps sports for one day with boxing champion Vikas Krishan Yadav.    </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bsdt80yxg811liiyb6zt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802043209+0000" stop="20240802044934+0000">
    <title lang="en">Table Tennis vs Cricket with Sharath Kamal and Harbhajan Singh | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can bowler Harbhajan Singh make use of his spinning skills in table tennis? What happens when a table tennis champion becomes a cricket bowler? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c4zwpcdwf2owihv6a6wu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802044934+0000" stop="20240802050424+0000">
    <title lang="en">Shooting vs Cricket with Manu Bhaker and Smriti Mandhana | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens in the battle of precision between cricket and shooting? The challenge is on, as Smriti Mandhana and Manu Bhaker swap the pistols and bats. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pxn7nrwwg05zmutrvbkf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802050424+0000" stop="20240802060220+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can this Finnish Olympic ice hockey legend change a Chinese team’s fortune?</title>
    <desc lang="en">See how 1988 Olympic silver medalist Rexi Ruotsalainen imparts his knowledge and expertise on the Huijia Green Dragons of Beijing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/djwdzjukr6slwbdrcjpj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802060000+0000" stop="20240802065408+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Dutch hockey legend Ellen Hoog help a team who doesn’t score win?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Three-time Olympic medalist Ellen Hoog tries to restore winning ways for a U19 girls hockey team in the Netherlands.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lzhihdlidj98geankcez"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802065408+0000" stop="20240802074911+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can USA's rugby coach Mike Friday transform India’s U17 female rugby team?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Team USA coach Mike Friday travels to Mumbai to train the Indian U17 Rugby 7's women's side, aiming to qualify for the Youth Olympics. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xsthuzyub8b7sx88gqxv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802074911+0000" stop="20240802075238+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | John John Florence</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer John John Florence in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o49zaq7clzyfapxm4rkp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802075238+0000" stop="20240802075615+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Tatiana Weston-Webb</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Tatiana Weston-Webb in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iparo4a2kdkieozgsqmy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802075615+0000" stop="20240802075950+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Leonardo Fioravanti</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Leonardo Fioravanti in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b0ivgyth6osxesm3ble4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802075950+0000" stop="20240802080355+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Lucca Mesinas</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Lucca Mesinas in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qzxanv6qtxj1ofgg1wdb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802080355+0000" stop="20240802080758+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Teresa Bonvalot</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Teresa Bonvalot in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lh3nbve3ghphl6mrjvk5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802080758+0000" stop="20240802081144+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Shino Matsuda</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Shino Matsuda in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/syrzxzlo7rd8pttd94lf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802081144+0000" stop="20240802081553+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Jordy Smith</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Jordy Smith in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ap7cqzepivid4ymykqcq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802081553+0000" stop="20240802081840+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Griffin Colapinto</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Griffin Colapinto in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/j4fwv1dcrsprk5ap23mg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802081840+0000" stop="20240802082227+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Rio Waida</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Rio Waida in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore his journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zijwlnuy0h2k3xoza1cm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802082227+0000" stop="20240802085403+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802085403+0000" stop="20240802090019+0000">
    <title lang="en">See You in Teahupo'o | Brisa Hennessy﻿</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into Olympic dreams with surfer Brisa Hennessy﻿ in “See You in Teahupo'o”. Explore her journey, Olympic experiences, and reflections on the legendary Teahupo'o wave.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/udrl0f8nveinlr0irxia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802090019+0000" stop="20240802095408+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Basketball Final, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the closest finish in 40 years, the USA played Spain for the men's basketball gold medal, in a thrilling rematch. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxghggiuz8etqdt6y6lb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802095408+0000" stop="20240802101354+0000">
    <title lang="en">Khalifa: An Olympic dream in the heart of Africa’s football powerhouse | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young Ghanian football player takes us into his world. Through his community, family and team we learn why football is so important to him and what he hopes to accomplish one day.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vgqzngvj1o4cwr6mqjs6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802101354+0000" stop="20240802103314+0000">
    <title lang="en">Aya: the first female swimmer to represent Gabon at the Olympics | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">An Olympic swimmer overcomes her tragic past and is determined to keep swimming. We see the inspiring relationship she has with her father as they train for future competitions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ln7ihg4fero3yvf6n1ia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802103314+0000" stop="20240802105330+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayomide: Born in a canoe, now a Nigerian rowing star | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her mother gave birth to her inside a canoe some 20 years ago. Ayomide Bello grew up to become the first female canoeist from Nigeria to qualify for the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hvr9skjd78d5ohz9hody"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802105330+0000" stop="20240802114912+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802114912+0000" stop="20240802120103+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs Cricket with Vikas Krishan Yadav and Harbhajan Singh | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can a boxer bat? And does a bowler have the power and precision to throw a punch? India’s cricket legend Harbhajan Singh swaps sports for one day with boxing champion Vikas Krishan Yadav.    </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bsdt80yxg811liiyb6zt"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802120103+0000" stop="20240802121501+0000">
    <title lang="en">Table Tennis vs Cricket with Sharath Kamal and Harbhajan Singh | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can bowler Harbhajan Singh make use of his spinning skills in table tennis? What happens when a table tennis champion becomes a cricket bowler? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c4zwpcdwf2owihv6a6wu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802121501+0000" stop="20240802122639+0000">
    <title lang="en">Shooting vs Cricket with Manu Bhaker and Smriti Mandhana | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens in the battle of precision between cricket and shooting? The challenge is on, as Smriti Mandhana and Manu Bhaker swap the pistols and bats. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pxn7nrwwg05zmutrvbkf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802122639+0000" stop="20240802123841+0000">
    <title lang="en">Hockey vs Cricket with Savita Punia and Smriti Mandhana | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s national hockey team goalkeeper Savita Punia swaps her hockey stick for a cricket bat. Can her skills in hockey help her become a better cricketer? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kxcq88bkf4lboaxwjgsi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802123841+0000" stop="20240802124901+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802124901+0000" stop="20240802125824+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Girl India aims for historic gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow India's remarkable journey from hometown studio of La Hague to the Olympic stage. While she qualified for the Games at the European Championships, with her unique style blending raw energy and finesse, she faces formidable rivals on her quest for breaking glory. Will her unmatched determination and skill make history at the Olympics where the sport is making its debut at Paris 2024?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fgps2zdjfhlhkjt0cnid"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802125824+0000" stop="20240802130616+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kauli Vaast’s Tahitian roots make him a favourite for Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Witness Kauli Vaast's journey from his childhood Tahitian shores to the world stage. Surrounded by his family and long time friend and mentor Jeremy Flores, he refines his craft at Teahupo'o impressive pipe where he will compete on hometurf for an Olympic Gold medal in surfing. Driven by passion and cheered on by those who believe in his dream, he balances the thrill of competition with the warmth of a unique community.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/atn7hr8mywzvlqx35qmf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802130616+0000" stop="20240802131607+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802131607+0000" stop="20240802132433+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teresa Portela Olympic longevity makes her a legend | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marked by determination, Teresa Portela's journey unfolds over six Olympics. From Rio to Tokyo, Portela's pursuit of Olympic glory was balanced between being an elite athlete and the joys of motherhood. In Tokyo, she finally won a long-awaited medal by bringing home silver in the K-1 200 canoe sprint event. Now training for Paris 2024, she will become the first Spanish woman to compete in seven Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wycbjpzqrzxazp4oxulz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802132433+0000" stop="20240802141748+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Middle Distance</title>
    <desc lang="en">The stories behind the key moments in middle distance running at the Olympic Games, including stars like Paavo Nurmi and Maria Mutola.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/weswph1l0navqhgryspy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802141748+0000" stop="20240802145029+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Vault, Treasures of the Olympics | Full Length</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the first time, Historian Greg Jenner and Olympian Jeanette Kwayke are given full access to go behind the scenes of the world’s greatest and most secure sporting collections to uncover the Treasures of the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/eukojzzuifvlt9pxm3pr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802145029+0000" stop="20240802145645+0000">
    <title lang="en">Greg and Jeanette go behind the scenes at the Olympic Museum | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg Jenner and Jeanette Kwayke are left alone one night at the Olympic Museum and get to discover its unique sporting collection. The public space is stretched over 3000 square meters. But they’ve been given the keys of what happens below the galleries. Long corridors and secret rooms where 90.000 items are kept, collated, preserved, and restored.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pnz9wspft7j3miitoqxi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802145645+0000" stop="20240802150500+0000">
    <title lang="en">Derek Redmond makes an incredible donation from Barcelona 1992 | The Vault</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg and Jeanette get to meet Olympic Legend Derek Redmond, one of the most emotional stories in the History the Games. In the best form he’s shown since he broke the British record, Derek is going for a gold or silver medal at Barcelona 1992. But in the semi-final, an injury will decide otherwise. The rest is part of History as his father joins him on the track in a highly emotional finish.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wmvzjzjetnozeu2rwgqw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802150500+0000" stop="20240802163536+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rulon | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">At the 2000 Olympic Games, American wrestler Rulon Gardner beat the unbeatable and became an overnight sensation. But what came after the ‘Miracle on the Mat’ was even more unpredictable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qwzxffsmpbcfufiy08dh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802163536+0000" stop="20240802170424+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Journey Begins</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games fast approaching, three of the best gymnasts in the world gear up for the most important year of their lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dkphy5ybiigyfgbdq9oq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802170424+0000" stop="20240802173328+0000">
    <title lang="en">Competition Season</title>
    <desc lang="en">Morgan and Angelina attempt to handle the pressure of the world stage. Will they succeed? Yile has a point to prove in training.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ppi2us5lcunmzzmlcimc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802173328+0000" stop="20240802180501+0000">
    <title lang="en">The World Championships 2019</title>
    <desc lang="en">The World Championships are here. The three gymnasts learn whether they’re selected for their national teams. All the drama from the biggest competition of the season. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vwvf4yaio4p7hqodtlcg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802180501+0000" stop="20240802184453+0000">
    <title lang="en">Teahupo'o Surf Camp | Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrills and spills as seven surfers join an ISA surf camp at Teahupo'o, Tahiti's famed surf spot and the surfing venue for the Olympic Games Paris 2024. Determined to conquer the Olympic wave, they face their fears, push the boundaries and challenge the raw power of nature.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jgfybidumyctl4uc7lvu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802184453+0000" stop="20240802193912+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Olympic Series: The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 4 : The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nsou8dw7a1xyj4omjz1v"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802193912+0000" stop="20240802194750+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ezra: A high-jumper finds community and another chance | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">As high-jump reigning World Champion, Ezra Frech prepares to return to the Paralympics for the second time. He reflects on his remarkable journey with his father and together with his mother, he takes us to meet their wider and beloved Californian community as they organize a unique event for adaptative sports in Los Angeles.    </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/glkk5ayzlsowdw4hqp5r"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802194750+0000" stop="20240802195705+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ferdinand: The Beast from the East returns to his roots | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Known as the ‘Fastest Man in Africa’ for his prowess in the 100m, Ferdinand Omanyala is setting his sights on becoming the fastest man in the world at Paris 2024. We follow him as he travels back to his hometown of Kitale in Kenya to get the blessings he needs from his peers and uncover the remarkable story of his origins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/n0xacw0mcphquast8plp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802195705+0000" stop="20240802200606+0000">
    <title lang="en">Nikoloz: The judo World Champion from two nations | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Nikoloz Sherazadishvili’s family moved him from Georgia to Spain at a young age, his father instilled a love of judo in him. He quickly felt at home at the local club of Brunete, in the outskirt of Madrid, where everything started with his first coach Quino Ruiz. As he gears up for his second Olympics, surrounded by his family and friends, he’s competing on the mat for Spain but also holding Georgia and the memory of his father close to his heart.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/odhgywsetbejzoilsrvd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802200606+0000" stop="20240802201413+0000">
    <title lang="en">Carlota: Proving herself and her sport to the world | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young female breaker for France, Carlota Dudek is training to qualify for the Olympics to showcase her unique style to the world, inherited from her mother Cuban origin. We travel with her from Paris to her hometown in the heart of Provence where her life-long dance journey began.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dkdz4nhhsilyl5ybnuuk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802201413+0000" stop="20240802202313+0000">
    <title lang="en">Manon: How the bond with her horse changed her life | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two-time medallist in dressage at Tokyo 2020, Manon Claeys shares her inspiring journey back from severe injury to Paralympic podium. After her accident, she thought she would never ride a horse again. Now, together with her cherished horse Katarina, and surrounded by her team and family, she trains to achieve a gold medal at Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/etcobotz6rpz7ccep7qf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802202313+0000" stop="20240802211835+0000">
    <title lang="en">Triumph and Tragedy | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an emotional journey with his son and grandson, Finland’s Lasse Virén revisits the spot where he rose to his feet after a dramatic fall to win gold. The next day, the spirit of Munich was shattered when a terror attack at the Olympic Village took the lives of 11 Israeli athletes and coaches – a day of tragedy as told by an Israeli survivor, Shaul Ladany, and the gold medallists from around the world who bore witness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ishr6vmaunsc38joibk6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802211835+0000" stop="20240802212549+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ginter is the defensive rock for Germany at World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">He was the youngest player in the Germany squad which went on to win the World Cup in 2014. Silver medallist at Rio 2016 Olympic Games, he played for Borussia Dortmund and Borussia Mönchengladbach before moving back to his hometown club of SC Freiburg. But behind a very friendly and family man, he is the defensive rock to take Germany to a new glory in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/roelsvrejxtmaoug58h0"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802212549+0000" stop="20240802213254+0000">
    <title lang="en">David Raum is the new Mannschaft’s shooting star | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Written off and sent to play in the second Bundesliga in Germany, Raum helped to propel his club to first division. After joining the national team at Tokyo 2020, he made a meteoric rise to RB Leipzig. He is now part of the senior national team and ready to shatter his opponents’ defense at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/epevots1k6i7aw1lrlc4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802213254+0000" stop="20240802213857+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kouyaté's fearless road to World Cup is a life lesson | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cheikhou Kouyaté left Senegal as a teenager to begin his football journey at F.C. Brussels. London 2012 was instrumental to his integration in the national team, followed by solid moves to West Ham United and Crystal Palace. His last years success at African Cup of Nations propelled him to the next level at Nottingham Forest. He is now gearing up with the Lions for the World Cup hoping to make history.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qo7ivzqvwhcvh4ckhvxw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802213857+0000" stop="20240802214441+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s number one keeper ready to shine at World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Establishing yourself as the number one keeper for Spain is no easy feat but thats what Unai Simón has been doing for two years now. As he recovered from his mistake at UEFA Euro 2020, he went on to win a silver medal at Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games. He is now aiming to earn a new title with the Spanish team at the World Cup 2022 in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bwiiibbus2tu3lcbmqvd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802214441+0000" stop="20240802215049+0000">
    <title lang="en">Bednarek leads a new generation of players for Poland | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jan Bednarek is a strong and skillful centre back who now plays for Aston Villa. He was raised in a family obsessed with football, including his brother Filip, who plays professionally as a goalkeeper in their home country. Poland’s last success in an international tournament was winning Silver at the Barcelona 1992 Olympic Games but a new generation of players is ready to take the 2022 World Cup by storm. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sxxilaklylefxgj3hqhk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802215049+0000" stop="20240802215811+0000">
    <title lang="en">Elaine Thompson-Herah: One sprint to rule them all | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">How Elaine Thompson-Herah became the undisputed sprinting queen and the first woman to win the 100-200m double gold at consecutive Olympics. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qdby3yncfcftbkyozw3g"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802215811+0000" stop="20240802220415+0000">
    <title lang="en">Neeraj Chopra: Throws his way into a nation's heart | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Neeraj Chopra makes Olympic history with the first-ever Olympic gold medal in track-and-field for India.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ykmpivgc38aypmepxgkr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802220415+0000" stop="20240802221105+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ariarne Titmus: Splashing into swimming royalty | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">How Ariarne Titmus went from chasing gold to being the one to beat after nail bitter 200m and 400m freestyle victories in Tokyo2020</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ah0nyrk1wk9y8i9rk663"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802221105+0000" stop="20240802221818+0000">
    <title lang="en">Carissa Moore: Carrying surfers' aloha spirit to the top of the podium | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">How native Hawaiian Carissa Moore, honoured generations of surfers by winning the sport's first Olympic gold medal. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hhjod91kr6o9vvd33vio"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802221818+0000" stop="20240802231107+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Gymnastics</title>
    <desc lang="en">Glorious gymnastics moments spanning the history of the Olympic Games, including Olga Korbut, Nadia Comaneci and Yukio Endo.
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zhv3fy9vle8wby95tagn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802231107+0000" stop="20240802233909+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s Abhinav Bindra I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of India’s first-ever individual gold medallist, Abhinav Bindra, and how he is now helping others fulfil their dreams.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jvq4mokfj4krqfodpabl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240802233909+0000" stop="20240803000634+0000">
    <title lang="en">United States’ Natalie Coughlin I Legends Live On</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at the Olympic achievements of twelve-time medallist, Natalie Coughlin, and what she is doing now.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/l6jswjaygevyr7yfuyck"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
