<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-08-11 00:00:02">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240810230519+0000" stop="20240811000159+0000">
    <title lang="en">Becoming an Olympic Legend | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after his famous tally of seven Olympic gold medals and seven world records, legendary swimmer Mark Spitz makes an emotional return to Munich Olympic Park and the swimming pool, where his life was changed forever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fu8b8krwuc98ozzpiroo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811000159+0000" stop="20240811001108+0000">
    <title lang="en">France's Sevens captain targets gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Backed by a great team and high perfornming coaches, Carla's quest for Olympic gold symbolizes the rise of women's rugby since Rio 2016. From competing with boys to leading her nation to Silver in Tokyo 2020, the French rugby Seven squad’s captain inspires resilience and dedication on the road to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wx3cbtavgwlobv8mubju"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811001108+0000" stop="20240811002051+0000">
    <title lang="en">Niklas Kaul - medal contender for Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Despite an incredible 2019 season, winning gold at the World Championships and setting a world’s best record, decathlete Niklas Kaul from Germany faced challenges at Tokyo 2020 due to an injury sustained in the high jump event. After focusing on recovery and preparing for future competitions, he reached an impressive 4th place at the European Championships in Roma, which puts him back in a position to medal at Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/k08y1355m32h27ghmwxj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811002051+0000" stop="20240811002838+0000">
    <title lang="en">Leonardo Fabbri’s success is rooted in family support | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">From his early athletic beginnings to his emotional 22.34m throw, Leonardo's journey is marked by family support and a dream of Olympic success. Despite setbacks, his determination remains unshaken as he aims for glory at Paris 2024. The Tuscan shot putter won gold at the European Championships, setting a championship record and placing him as a serious contender for the coming games. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxqemihgzmjzz9xokxbs"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811002838+0000" stop="20240811003741+0000">
    <title lang="en">Matteo Zurloni Italy’s world champion climbs to the top | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dive into the remarkable journey of Matteo Zurloni, from small town dreamer to Olympic contender. He won the speed event at the 2023 IFSC Climbing World Championships and earning a shot at Olympic glory. Follow his ascent from humble beginnings to the dizzying heights of international competition, where every climb is a test of skill, courage, and the relentless pursuit of excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sju6a1o423a4twjhziik"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811003741+0000" stop="20240811004806+0000">
    <title lang="en">Norwegian duo are targeting back-to-back Olympic Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reigning World and Olympic Champions Christian Sørum and Anders Mol are dominating beach volleyball. Their partnership, rooted in a Viking mentality, has kept them atop the sport for six years. They are now preparing for a historic back-to-back Olympic gold at Paris 2024 to honour Christian's mother's legacy.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dtt3kmg82b6kunoo91cr"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811004806+0000" stop="20240811014449+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Marathon</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best moments from the Olympic Games’ ultimate endurance events with stories from Emil Zatopek and Frank Shorter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dxjn2qu7uybyharsdyfe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811014449+0000" stop="20240811015910+0000">
    <title lang="en">A Family Affair | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">We head to Pullela Gopichand’s home as the family reflects on how far they have come. Pullela’s daughter Gayatri is put through her paces. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zfpoc7aqhh1lwuzjbr4b"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811015910+0000" stop="20240811021120+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Rise of the Doubles Players | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">India’s doubles players are thriving lately. We hang out with the charismatic men’s team of Satwick and Shetty, and follow Sikki Reddy through rehabilitation.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/izmk6egybas8dl4t5ede"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811021120+0000" stop="20240811022736+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Future of Indian Badminton | The Academy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pullela Gopichand looks towards the future with the latest batch of young students at the academy, some of whom rise at 3am to learn to play badminton.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/shrpedfvhf3y40sjm177"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811022736+0000" stop="20240811032014+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Invisible Bond | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">Discover the invisible bond that forges the relationship between an athlete with visual impairment and his guide. This bond transcends the field of play developed by trust, friendship, and the unwavering desire of achieving Paralympic glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkyxtc7pq7xnkemo5yiy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811032014+0000" stop="20240811041223+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can this Finnish Olympic ice hockey legend change a Chinese team’s fortune?</title>
    <desc lang="en">See how 1988 Olympic silver medalist Rexi Ruotsalainen imparts his knowledge and expertise on the Huijia Green Dragons of Beijing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/djwdzjukr6slwbdrcjpj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811041223+0000" stop="20240811050426+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Aquatics</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best diving, swimming and water polo stories from throughout Olympic history including Dawn Fraser, Greg Louganis and Michael Phelps.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vydzinqyv16sh5trwq8a"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811050426+0000" stop="20240811060234+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic and Arsenal legend save a football team from relegation?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cameroon &amp; Arsenal football legend Lauren coaches a struggling amateur league team from East London. Will he help them avoid relegation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rqfkn2zfzfgwog1hgosj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811060000+0000" stop="20240811065643+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women’s Tennis Singles Final, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could Monica Puig overcome Germany’s Angelique Kerber, world No. 1, to win Puerto Rico’s first-ever Olympic gold?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b63j1cjvyfbh6tzbfb8e"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811065643+0000" stop="20240811074817+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic and Arsenal legend save a football team from relegation?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cameroon &amp; Arsenal football legend Lauren coaches a struggling amateur league team from East London. Will he help them avoid relegation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rqfkn2zfzfgwog1hgosj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811074817+0000" stop="20240811084255+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Jackie Silva get this Brazilian volleyball team to defeat their rival?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian Olympic gold medalist Jackie Silva lends her expertise to a Rio indoor volleyball team as they try to win their first event ever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mwcu5tq4upkl1jm6icfc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811084255+0000" stop="20240811085811+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mariah: A Boxer’s Dream | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">16-year-old Navajo boxer Mariah Bahe is fighting against all odds to become the first female Native American Olympic boxer.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/adq0dixjiqcurvfd9flg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811085811+0000" stop="20240811093228+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811093228+0000" stop="20240811094044+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811094044+0000" stop="20240811094559+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811094559+0000" stop="20240811095249+0000">
    <title lang="en">World Cup winner from Argentinian football dynasty | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a father, uncle and two older brothers all professionals, Alexis Mac Allister was destined for a life in football. All three brothers even achieved their dream of playing on the same team for Argentinos Juniors, which saw young Maradona starts his legendary career and played with their father in the late 70’s. As a very fine member of this Argentinian football dynasty, Mac Allister is aiming to weave his midfield magic at the World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/scynz4fdr9pfdyi28oq1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811095249+0000" stop="20240811095843+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811095843+0000" stop="20240811100548+0000">
    <title lang="en">The New-Zealand striker who made his dreams come true | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">As one of only six kiwis to ever to play in Premier League, Chris Wood has achieved more than he could have ever imagined. Schooled by his football playing sister, Chris moved to England at the age of 15 and made his Premier League debut at 17. After a challenging period of loan moves, Wood met success with Millwall and a personal achievement at London 2012. Now a regular striker at Newcastle United, Wood’s New Zealand has just missed out on World Cup qualification. Arguably the nation’s greatest ever player, he has sights set on another great stage, Paris 2024 where he would be participating in the Olympics for the 3rd time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b60painhtemnajlhqfs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811100548+0000" stop="20240811101141+0000">
    <title lang="en">Talented midfielder Louza sets hope for Paris 2024 | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">The talented midfielder from Watford was desperately unlucky and suffered ligament damage ruling him out of the World Cup selection for Morocco. A product of Nantes F.C. football academy, he joined the UK Premier League as well as debuting and scoring at his first game with the national team. At just 23, he now sets his hopes on Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jpojslmkvpt1kli3bnhd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811101141+0000" stop="20240811102339+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs weightlifting with Shimizu Satoshi &amp; Takao Hiroaki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Olympic boxing bronze medallist snatch 40 kg on his first attempt? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxffrstaqlasgzgnrqtc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811102339+0000" stop="20240811103811+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs race walk with Kanie Miki &amp; Tanii Takayuki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a race walk champion tries to shoot an arrow?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qy9tevadjqoobtb1haoo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811103811+0000" stop="20240811104113+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Japan's 16-year-old sport climbing sensation | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mori Ai started climbing walls when she was eight.  After competing and winning the World Championships, she is focused on being one of the world's top climbers. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iyvfdf4j6tv9v6r0iyyb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811104113+0000" stop="20240811104414+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Japan's table tennis belongs to this 13-year-old prodigy | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Harimoto Miwa's older brother Tomokazu has been the face of Japanese table tennis. Still, he is not the only Harimoto shouldering the hopes of a nation as Miwa is making a name of her own. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlq8b9bzzojdlziqbks1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811104414+0000" stop="20240811104711+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811104711+0000" stop="20240811104959+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811104959+0000" stop="20240811105256+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811105256+0000" stop="20240811105516+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811105516+0000" stop="20240811105709+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811105709+0000" stop="20240811105857+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811105857+0000" stop="20240811112815+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811112815+0000" stop="20240811113234+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811113234+0000" stop="20240811122839+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811122839+0000" stop="20240811123925+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811123925+0000" stop="20240811124918+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811124918+0000" stop="20240811125721+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811125721+0000" stop="20240811130313+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811130313+0000" stop="20240811130816+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811130816+0000" stop="20240811131314+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811131314+0000" stop="20240811131814+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811131814+0000" stop="20240811132723+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811132723+0000" stop="20240811133855+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811133855+0000" stop="20240811135025+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811135025+0000" stop="20240811140151+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811140151+0000" stop="20240811141406+0000">
    <title lang="en">Lyla Nourtier: you can succeed - France / Weighlifting I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lyla is a 15 year old weightlifter  from a small village in France without much access to sports. We meet her at a turning point in her life as she plans to leave home to pursue her dream. She joins an elite sport and education program where she is the first ever female weightlifter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sjzbaetxwitdiurxb4av"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811141406+0000" stop="20240811142318+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can imagining success actually help you achieve it? | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Learn how these visualization techniques practiced by some of the world’s greatest Olympians could help you overcome the challenges in your day to day life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/u7lyx1vw3goxwe3xgnto"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811142318+0000" stop="20240811142942+0000">
    <title lang="en">How an Olympic champion swimmer almost drowned at London 1948</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Sinking Dream”, Greta Andersen shares how her quest for a second gold was cut short when she blacked. But it didn’t define her career.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/clebcrcrrpzrvirw3vsf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811142942+0000" stop="20240811143750+0000">
    <title lang="en">The inspiring story of the first woman to win an Olympic gold for Australia</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Lithgow Flash”, Marjorie Jackson recalls her early training leading up to two gold medals in 1952 and her life upon returning home.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o8wxabyggsnakkhbjl9m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811143750+0000" stop="20240811144410+0000">
    <title lang="en">The incredible story of the orphan who made it to the Olympic podium</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Game of Life”, Kriss Akabusi shares how he discovered running in the British Army and what it felt like to win silver in LA1984.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zhkr0twlijswtrgjx9ts"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811144410+0000" stop="20240811145401+0000">
    <title lang="en">The story of the basketball legend who never gave up on her Olympic dream</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Queen”, Brazilian legend Hortencia Marcari explains why she came out of retirement only months after giving birth. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fr0u01e6bgquep8bxo8k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811145401+0000" stop="20240811150036+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a pioneering Egyptian swimmer broke boundaries and inspired the world</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “The Golden Fish”, Rania Elwani tells how her determination as an Olympic swimmer was matched only by her commitment to peruse her career as a doctor.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uvbg6uso2jsmt7irbn32"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811150036+0000" stop="20240811155627+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can an Olympic and Arsenal legend save a football team from relegation?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cameroon &amp; Arsenal football legend Lauren coaches a struggling amateur league team from East London. Will he help them avoid relegation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rqfkn2zfzfgwog1hgosj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811155627+0000" stop="20240811165210+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Jackie Silva get this Brazilian volleyball team to defeat their rival?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian Olympic gold medalist Jackie Silva lends her expertise to a Rio indoor volleyball team as they try to win their first event ever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mwcu5tq4upkl1jm6icfc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811165210+0000" stop="20240811174840+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Triathlon, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brothers Alistair and Jonny Brownlee race against the world's best in the 2012 Olympic men's triathlon. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ix1a4g7jedfs5yoeic2m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811174840+0000" stop="20240811184033+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rise of Women Olympians</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 1 : The story of Women at the Games, Rise of Women Olympians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxcua384ycbgx9v2zjyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811184033+0000" stop="20240811185225+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811185225+0000" stop="20240811185739+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811185739+0000" stop="20240811190429+0000">
    <title lang="en">World Cup winner from Argentinian football dynasty | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a father, uncle and two older brothers all professionals, Alexis Mac Allister was destined for a life in football. All three brothers even achieved their dream of playing on the same team for Argentinos Juniors, which saw young Maradona starts his legendary career and played with their father in the late 70’s. As a very fine member of this Argentinian football dynasty, Mac Allister is aiming to weave his midfield magic at the World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/scynz4fdr9pfdyi28oq1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811190429+0000" stop="20240811191023+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811191023+0000" stop="20240811191728+0000">
    <title lang="en">The New-Zealand striker who made his dreams come true | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">As one of only six kiwis to ever to play in Premier League, Chris Wood has achieved more than he could have ever imagined. Schooled by his football playing sister, Chris moved to England at the age of 15 and made his Premier League debut at 17. After a challenging period of loan moves, Wood met success with Millwall and a personal achievement at London 2012. Now a regular striker at Newcastle United, Wood’s New Zealand has just missed out on World Cup qualification. Arguably the nation’s greatest ever player, he has sights set on another great stage, Paris 2024 where he would be participating in the Olympics for the 3rd time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b60painhtemnajlhqfs1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811191728+0000" stop="20240811192321+0000">
    <title lang="en">Talented midfielder Louza sets hope for Paris 2024 | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">The talented midfielder from Watford was desperately unlucky and suffered ligament damage ruling him out of the World Cup selection for Morocco. A product of Nantes F.C. football academy, he joined the UK Premier League as well as debuting and scoring at his first game with the national team. At just 23, he now sets his hopes on Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jpojslmkvpt1kli3bnhd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811192321+0000" stop="20240811193519+0000">
    <title lang="en">Boxing vs weightlifting with Shimizu Satoshi &amp; Takao Hiroaki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can Olympic boxing bronze medallist snatch 40 kg on his first attempt? </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bxffrstaqlasgzgnrqtc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811193519+0000" stop="20240811194542+0000">
    <title lang="en">Archery vs race walk with Kanie Miki &amp; Tanii Takayuki | Sports Swap Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens when a race walk champion tries to shoot an arrow?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qy9tevadjqoobtb1haoo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811194542+0000" stop="20240811194843+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Japan's 16-year-old sport climbing sensation | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mori Ai started climbing walls when she was eight.  After competing and winning the World Championships, she is focused on being one of the world's top climbers. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iyvfdf4j6tv9v6r0iyyb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811194843+0000" stop="20240811195734+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Japan's table tennis belongs to this 13-year-old prodigy | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Harimoto Miwa's older brother Tomokazu has been the face of Japanese table tennis. Still, he is not the only Harimoto shouldering the hopes of a nation as Miwa is making a name of her own. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hlq8b9bzzojdlziqbks1"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811195734+0000" stop="20240811204912+0000">
    <title lang="en">Speed and grace</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 2 : The story of Women at the Games, Speed and grace.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zzs8tfcep2xnog47vvcj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811204912+0000" stop="20240811205208+0000">
    <title lang="en">This Skater-girl is inspiring a new generation of skateboarders |  Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ogawa Kihana was born in Fujisawa and began skateboarding after imitating her brother when catching waves. She is working hard to be an inspiration for younger female skateboarders</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qcrmpch4jhda4wfgyjmc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811205208+0000" stop="20240811211023+0000">
    <title lang="en">Mariah: A Boxer’s Dream | Film</title>
    <desc lang="en">16-year-old Navajo boxer Mariah Bahe is fighting against all odds to become the first female Native American Olympic boxer.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/adq0dixjiqcurvfd9flg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811211023+0000" stop="20240811211311+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kyoto-born BMX rider is going for glory at Tokyo 2020 | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nakamura Rim has been on wheels since his childhood. With BMX freestyle set to debut at the Olympic Games in Tokyo, Rim is eyeing more than just a gold medal on home turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ixkymqnvoo7inzmjgmly"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811211311+0000" stop="20240811211608+0000">
    <title lang="en">This future star of Japanese Judo is following in his father's footsteps | Heroes Of the Future - Japan</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saito Tatsuru the 17-year-old judoka, son of the two-time Olympic gold medallist and world champion Saito Hitoshi. His dream is to become an Olympic champion, like his father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aqne4yaf3i3vzhbsqnia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811211608+0000" stop="20240811211828+0000">
    <title lang="en">Knowing what motivates you can help you stand out | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motivation is your brain's way of keeping you going when times get tough, is the key to success in so many walks of life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yw027lmcr1rowehiamdd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811211828+0000" stop="20240811212021+0000">
    <title lang="en">How you can turn negative emotions into positives | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mindfulness is about being aware of physical sensations and that’s why many Olympians use it to optimise their training and competition performance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/msbsieryznil8oldv9ae"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811212021+0000" stop="20240811212209+0000">
    <title lang="en">The secret weapon we all have but might not be using | Olympic State of Mind</title>
    <desc lang="en">Visualisation is a technique in which you use your imagination to picture challenges ahead of you to help you achieve them in real life.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hnelb8qmy266s4i1fgol"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811212209+0000" stop="20240811214808+0000">
    <title lang="en">Netherlands’ Pieter van den Hoogenband (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dutch swimming legend Pieter van den Hoogenband won seven Olympic medals. Now, he’s helping others swim their fastest. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxt20vauetnhtdxbhvn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811214808+0000" stop="20240811221713+0000">
    <title lang="en">Spain’s “Las Niñas de Oro” (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">“Las Niñas de Oro” were the youngest Spanish Olympic medallist when they won gold in Atlanta 1996. They continue to inspire younger generations, including the Rio 2016 silver medallist Spanish national team.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fovyivvmiyvewfvuubty"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811221713+0000" stop="20240811222132+0000">
    <title lang="en">How a secret source of inspiration helped Billy Mills win gold in Tokyo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In “Wings of an Eagle”, Native American Billy Mills’ tells the personal journey that helped him heal his pain over the loss of his mother.  </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/p8znkwv860bwthmqrzy2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811222132+0000" stop="20240811231757+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811231757+0000" stop="20240811232843+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Christine Girard was finally awarded the gold medal she deserved</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Girard finished in 4th place at Beijing 2008, the Canadian weightlifter fell into a depression. She worked back into shape for London 2012, where she finished in third. But now, after disqualifications due to doping and the reallocation of medals, she is finally awarded the Olympic medals she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xpeh2dcqkejuyfd6xrad"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811232843+0000" stop="20240811233836+0000">
    <title lang="en">After unspeakable sadness, Skujyte finds redemption in reallocated medal</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doubt, doping sanctions saw Lithuanian heptathlete Austra Skujyte upgraded from fifth place in the London 2012 heptathlon to the bronze medal. Watch how she found overdue redemption following her fourth and final Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dsbrvkgqdpozgl9dgin2"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811233836+0000" stop="20240811234639+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Betty Heidler received her silver medal after a seven-year wait</title>
    <desc lang="en">The German hammer thrower was upgraded to the silver medal after the re-analysis of control samples and the disqualification of multiple competitors. She describes feeling a mix of emotions upon the news that she would finally be awarded the Olympic medal that she deserved.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bb6cjfewed38opznlnne"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811234639+0000" stop="20240811235231+0000">
    <title lang="en">How sport climbing star Shauna Coxsey found her sport | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shauna Coxsey is a sport climbing sensation from the UK. With her motto “find something that makes you happy” she made it to the top and is now ready to step up to represent the sport at the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jmyinccm6xrasloqnj0l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811235231+0000" stop="20240811235734+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Bruce Lee first inspired this karate champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Saadi Abbas, a karateka from Pakistan, nearly gave up on his Olympic dream. After learning that the sport would join the Olympics in Tokyo, he jumped back into training despite injuries and a lack of funding. Now, he hopes to follow the example of Seoul 1988 bronze medallist Hussain Shah, who is from the same neighbourhood of Karachi, to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pax2cxcg5fba3hscw3ap"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240811235734+0000" stop="20240812000232+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Jordyn Barratt found herself through skateboarding | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in Hawaii, it’s not surprising that Jordyn was a surfer long before she stepped on a skateboard. But her life changed when she entered a skatepark for the first time. She finally felt at home and was able to express herself through her movements on the board. Now that skateboarding is an Olympic sport, she’s ready to represent her community on the biggest stage of all.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/flbc0bvsydyi6ukdyeak"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812000232+0000" stop="20240812000732+0000">
    <title lang="en">How Peruvian star Lucca Mesinas fell in love with surfing | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his parents’ footsteps, Lucca fell in love with surfing at a young age thanks to long sessions in the water with family and friends. With a surprising competitive streak, Lucca has now qualified for the Tokyo 2020 Games, where surfing will make its Olympic debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dooorqreeo5tta52whbg"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812000732+0000" stop="20240812001217+0000">
    <title lang="en">How fun fuels this Para-Taekwondo world champion | Unleash the New</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Juan-Diego Garcia entered a dojang for the first time at age five, he knew he found his place. As success came against abled bodied competitors, other kids used to ask, “But he doesn’t have an arm, how did he win?” He always proved to himself and others he can do anything. Now, Mexico’s first-ever world champion in Para-Taekwondo is training harder than ever to represent his country and hometown at the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Games where the sport will make its debut. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/s1jyymsc1j3mqhn3ydgm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812001217+0000" stop="20240812002651+0000">
    <title lang="en">Margie Didal: do what you love - Philippines / Skateboarding I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Margie first encountered skateboarding while helping her mother sell street food to make ends meet. Now she supports her family as one of the top skateboarders in Asia. Being a skater, she is a bit of a rebel in  Filipina culture, but she is the sport sensation of the country and a strong chance of a medal at Tokyo 2020. She is paving the way for the next generation of women in skateboarding. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/neojfuptv894phdk3qmd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812002651+0000" stop="20240812003821+0000">
    <title lang="en">Arijah Haseeb: start playing anywhere  - Pakistan / Cricket I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her whole life, Arijah has been the only girl playing cricket on the streets with the boys of her neighbourhood. She was scouted to join the local academy with other girls pursuing the sport and quickly became one of the best players on the team. She now has the women’s national team in  her sights. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/kiwgfnjswicai3ak48p3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812003821+0000" stop="20240812004948+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tracie Leost: you can have it all - Canada / Ice Hockey I By Her Rules</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tracie is the first generation urban indigenous person in her family and she’s an Ice hockey coach, a graduate student of social work, and an ice fisher, At 16 years old, she ran 140 kilometres to raise awareness for missing and murdered indigenous women and girls and now she is empowering  indigenous youth living in Winnipeg area.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/opyp5sgaszknxuwyk8e7"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812004948+0000" stop="20240812014708+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women’s Tennis Singles Final, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could Monica Puig overcome Germany’s Angelique Kerber, world No. 1, to win Puerto Rico’s first-ever Olympic gold?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b63j1cjvyfbh6tzbfb8e"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812014708+0000" stop="20240812021635+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812021635+0000" stop="20240812031143+0000">
    <title lang="en">Can Jackie Silva get this Brazilian volleyball team to defeat their rival?</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brazilian Olympic gold medalist Jackie Silva lends her expertise to a Rio indoor volleyball team as they try to win their first event ever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mwcu5tq4upkl1jm6icfc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812031143+0000" stop="20240812040346+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Triathlon, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brothers Alistair and Jonny Brownlee race against the world's best in the 2012 Olympic men's triathlon. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ix1a4g7jedfs5yoeic2m"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812040346+0000" stop="20240812041315+0000">
    <title lang="en">Japanese winger who qualified his team for the World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having risen through the ranks at Kawasaki Frontale, Kaoru Mitoma made the unorthodox decision to go to University and not enter professional football. Now at Premier League Brighton, Mitoma’s greatest success so far has been for the national team so far. Scoring two vital goals to secure his nation's place at the World Cup. He is now ready to tackle the competition to come.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/c9lvbsggy7neisuljjhq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812041315+0000" stop="20240812042132+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tokyo 2020 top scorer sets sights on World Cup | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Growing up in a rural town in Brazil, Richarlison took an unconventional path to success. He played for his hometown club until the age of 16. He embarked on a journey of many trials until he was signed by América Mineiro. His rise is nothing but remarkable with his move to Premier League club Tottenham. Tokyo 2020 was a dream tournament for him as he was given the fabled number 10 shirt and went on to win a Gold medal and the golden boot. Watch out for Richarlison who scored his country's first two goals at the 2022 World Cup.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ac5bz5mau81kavxiqdtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812042132+0000" stop="20240812042646+0000">
    <title lang="en">Iranian superstar ready to give all for national team | World at their Feet</title>
    <desc lang="en">Now one of Iran’s greatest ever footballers, Azmoun could have chosen volleyball but his father decided otherwise. He left Iran for Russia at the age of 18 to develop his talent and career. Unsuccessful striker at the 2018 World Cup, he made an impressive move to Bayer Leverkusen. Having now returned to the national team, he is ready to give it all for the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uwdhxqvc7qpajztsyjby"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812042646+0000" stop="20240812060241+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rulon | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">At the 2000 Olympic Games, American wrestler Rulon Gardner beat the unbeatable and became an overnight sensation. But what came after the ‘Miracle on the Mat’ was even more unpredictable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qwzxffsmpbcfufiy08dh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812060000+0000" stop="20240812102204+0000">
    <title lang="en">Opening Ceremony | Olympic Games Paris 2024 </title>
    <desc lang="en">Re-experience an Opening Ceremony for the ages, walking you through the history of the Host nation while celebrating Olympic Values in spectatcular fashion.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ckey7blrnquhbomn3jxx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812102204+0000" stop="20240812111719+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Olympic Series: The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 4 : The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nsou8dw7a1xyj4omjz1v"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812111719+0000" stop="20240812112541+0000">
    <title lang="en">India’s Top Pistol Shooter Manu Bakher | Jee Jan Se</title>
    <desc lang="en">Throughout her childhood and teenage years, Manu Bakher switched sports half a dozen times. When she started practicing air pistol shooting, she knew this was the one for her. This is her amazing story. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812112541+0000" stop="20240812113720+0000">
    <title lang="en">Shooting vs Cricket with Manu Bhaker and Smriti Mandhana | Sports Swap India</title>
    <desc lang="en">What happens in the battle of precision between cricket and shooting? The challenge is on, as Smriti Mandhana and Manu Bhaker swap the pistols and bats. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pxn7nrwwg05zmutrvbkf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812113720+0000" stop="20240812125222+0000">
    <title lang="en">10m Air Rifle Mixed Team Finals | Shooting | Olympic Games Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 27/07/2024 at the Chateauroux Shooting Range, Paris. CHN claimed the Gold, KOR the Silver and KAZ completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jflrllwg01vulgaxd48j"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812125222+0000" stop="20240812125641+0000">
    <title lang="en">Hero of the Future: 15-year-old German Diving Prodigy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lena Hentschel, 15, is a German High Diver and a big hope for her country in The Olympic Games 2020. Her motto is "no fun, no success."</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gsvrleenefjs47hcqj1f"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812125641+0000" stop="20240812130200+0000">
    <title lang="en">The future of Mexican diving belongs to this 15-year-old phenomenon</title>
    <desc lang="en">Randal Willars Valdez has a mission: first win gold at YOG 2018 in the 10m platform and then do the same Tokyo 2020.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pxxdhd6d8qgrim1yxujl"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812130200+0000" stop="20240812130550+0000">
    <title lang="en">Molly Carlson, Canada’s Brave High Diver | Splash In</title>
    <desc lang="en">She started as a gymnast, then switched to diving, before specializing in high diving (20m) because that is what bravery is to her. Along the journey, she learned how to deal with mental health struggles, an experience that she now shares with her fans as a  mental health advocate and founder of the #bravegang. 
Soundtrack: Bastille, Shut Off The Lights
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ma3ve9oaudrlicg4z4hq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812130550+0000" stop="20240812131336+0000">
    <title lang="en">Melissa Wu, the Australian Olympic Diver Who Does Not Give Up | Splash In</title>
    <desc lang="en">At the age of 10 she knew that diving was the sport for her. Throughout her 16 years career, diving helped her overcome depression, anxiety, and lack of self-belief, until she won bronze in Tokyo 2020. Watch her story. 
Soundtrack: Bree Runway, Pressure. 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/udxqki5gabazcidnrrrw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812131336+0000" stop="20240812132251+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ale: the Mexican diver trying to keep it all in synch | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Alejandra Orozco, two-time Olympic medallist in diving for Mexico, makes her fourth return to the Olympics at Paris 2024. More in sync than ever with her diving partner, Gabriela Agundez, and her family, she takes us back to where it all began: the family farm in the outskirt of Guadaljara. With the support of a loving family, hard work and dedication, she is hoping to reach the pinnacle of her career with Gold this Summer surrounded by her loved ones.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zmfuvbeujwgei666ihwi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240812132251+0000" stop="20240812133027+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: the long and bumpy road to Olympic gold | Wait For It Tokyo 2020</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thirteen years after his Olympic debut, the British diver finally landed the gold medal that was missing from his collection.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/uiluzuv9rhtucenqzoyr"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
