<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2024-07-01 00:00:03">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240630201309+0000" stop="20240701000659+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Park  - Skateboarding | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 04/08/2021 at the Ariake Urban Sports Park, Tokio. It includes the Women's Park Prelims Heats and Finals as well as the Victory Ceremony. Yosozumi (JPN) claimed the Gold, Hiraki (JPN) Silver and Brown (GBR) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/y8shjsvrgeyzdq0s5cai"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701000659+0000" stop="20240701003601+0000">
    <title lang="en">Anatomy of: Cycling BMX, Basketball 3x3, and Surfing</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a sports science lab, we studied the physiques of BMX racer Connor Fields, basketball player Laetitia Guapo, and Surfer Brisa Hennessy to find out what makes them special at their sports.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/r7uogf54bnnu9hwea3kh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701003601+0000" stop="20240701010523+0000">
    <title lang="en">Skier Crey &amp; BMX rider Foronda chase Games glory</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tom Crey, a 15-year-old French skier, and Nicole Foronda, a nine-year-old Colombian BMX rider, fight for their Paralympic and Olympic dream.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/avgnbtwekz9cwitp4kzn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701010523+0000" stop="20240701050435+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Combined Finals  - Climbing | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 05/08/2021 at the Aomi Urban Sports Park, Tokyo. It includes the Men's Combined - Speed, Bouldering and Lead Finals and the Victory Ceremony. Gines Lopez (ESP) claimed Gold. Coleman (USA) Silver and Schubert (AUT) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zqzwyvcry7sji2nmnyfw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701050435+0000" stop="20240701051647+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Adrien Raza, the godfather of urban skimboarding | Urbanity</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adrien Raza is a unique and talented skimboarder, who has taken the urban skimboarding scene by storm. From fountains to ramps to stairs, he skims it all!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wzcxc4qrh1xcuo46jcde"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701051647+0000" stop="20240701052550+0000">
    <title lang="en">Johan Tonnoir: parkour’s force of nature | Urbanity</title>
    <desc lang="en">Johan Tonnoir, an athlete and artist who uses Paris’ architecture to defy gravity and who is taking free running to a whole new level.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/rkemnahsx2vgafhgvlnn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701052550+0000" stop="20240701054003+0000">
    <title lang="en">From NYC to Alaska, meet the pioneers and US champion | Breaking Life </title>
    <desc lang="en">As the birthplace of a global hip-hop movement, we meet some of the pioneers of Breaking in New-York City. While Kid Glyde shares his passion for breaking with the next generation at his Harlem studio, three thousand miles away in Anchorage Alaska, B-Boy Icey Ives, two-time US national champion, melts the ice with his local crew Frozen Flow while being a community leader, a teacher and a role model for the youth living in extremely challenging conditions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dovd8hi3ceymcdhls5v8"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701054003+0000" stop="20240701060238+0000">
    <title lang="en">Young breakers take over the streets of Medellin | Breaking Life</title>
    <desc lang="en">Colombia used to be one of the most dangerous countries in the world but has found new life through a revival in urban arts, becoming a global creative mecca. 
B-Girl Luma and 4Eskuela hip hop school, where she learnt Breaking and is now a teacher, have been instrumental to this change in Medellin (Colombia). But it’s not been an easy journey for Luma who also had her doubts about what she can really achieve through dancing. By winning international dance events around the world, she is now confident it gave her a career and a drive, also when teaching young kids in her neighbourhood. She is keen to participate to Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iddfhrgah2b2pkoabbbd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701060000+0000" stop="20240701085641+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Qualification &amp; Final - Trampoline Gymnastics | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 31/07/2021 at the Ariake Gymnastics Centre, Tokyo. Ivan Litvinovich (BLR) claimed the Gold, Dong Dong (CHN) took the Silver and Dylan Schmidt (NZL) completed the podium.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vww41bsentpyuzwhfau6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701085641+0000" stop="20240701120001+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Team Final - Artistic Gymnastics | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 27/07/2021 at the Ariake Gymnastics Centre, Tokyo. ROC claimed the Gold, USA the Silver and GBR completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/j0yuzoas8xctdbp0bmbe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701120001+0000" stop="20240701154628+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Individual All-Around Final  - Artistic Gymnastics | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 28/07/2021 at the Ariake Gymnastics Centre, Tokyo. Hashimoto (JPN)  claimed the Gold, Xiao (CHN) Silver and Nagornyy (ROC) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fkhjrz2tqoch1avzrjs4"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701154628+0000" stop="20240701185724+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Rings,Vault &amp; Women's Floor - Artistic Gymnastics | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 02/08/2021 at the Ariake Gymnastics Centre, Tokyo. Liu (CHN) claimed the Gold in the Men's Rings, Carey (USA) in the Women's Floor and Shin (KOR) in the Men's Vault.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkp7vamytitw7r7hcmdx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701185724+0000" stop="20240701225053+0000">
    <title lang="en">Individual All-Around Final - Rhythmic Gymnastics | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 07/08/2021 at the Ariake Gymnastics Centre, Tokyo. Ashram (ISR) claimed Gold, Avernina (ROC) Silver and Harnaso (BLR) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pveelqtha3fedfvtmgow"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701225053+0000" stop="20240701230546+0000">
    <title lang="en">All Around | Upgrade Season</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the sixth episode of the gymnastics show All Around: 2020 is here and it’s time to upgrade the routines for the Olympic year. Yile is gradually recovering from her injury; Morgan is happy with developing new skills; and Angelina enjoys Christmas in Moscow.
All Around is the Olympic Channel's first original gymnastics documentary series, with new episodes released monthly until Tokyo 2020. Watch now!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vq561n05jkr0zjombvxd"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701230546+0000" stop="20240701232140+0000">
    <title lang="en">All Around | It’s Not All Work</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the seventh episode of the gymnastics show All Around: Angelina is back to training after her first ever snowboarding trip; Morgan and her mother open up about the adoption story; Yile, who has made big progress on recovery, enjoys some fun training games with her teammates and coaches.  
All Around is the Olympic Channel's first original gymnastics documentary series, with new episodes released monthly until Tokyo 2020. Watch now!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/i0gxslgpmtoztds3djzy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701232140+0000" stop="20240701233252+0000">
    <title lang="en">All Around | All Systems Pause</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the ninth episode of the gymnastics show All Around: the world of sports is interrupted by the Covid-19 pandemic; Morgan comes back from winning American Cup 2020 to see Delaware under lockdown and her gym closed; Yile and the Chinese gymnastics team continue training in isolation under the lockdown; And Angelina is having trouble focusing on her training in the light of competitions being cancelled.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/o8mefyebajjihinvpi1h"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701233252+0000" stop="20240701234626+0000">
    <title lang="en">All Around | The Clock Resets</title>
    <desc lang="en">The tenth episode of the gymnastics show All Around: The Olympics are postponed and sport competitions are put on pause. Angelina, Morgan and Yile reflect on a new reality in the world of sport and remain determined to chase that Olympic dream.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dve0fskoltjspqzz5hyv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240701234626+0000" stop="20240702020455+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Artistic Gymnastics All Around | Rio 2016 | Great Olympic Moments</title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch the artistic gymnastics individual all around from the Rio Summer Olympic Games in 2016 and follow Simone Biles and Alexandra Raisman as they win gold and silver for the USA and Aliya Mustafina as she claims bronze for Russia</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q00hnptow4cpcjpa8bcp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702020455+0000" stop="20240702030037+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702030037+0000" stop="20240702051157+0000">
    <title lang="en">Finals - Women's Trampoline | London 2012 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 04/08/2012 at North Greenwich Arena, London. Rosannagh MacLennan (CAN) claimed the Gold. Huang Shanshan (CHN) and He Wenna (CHN) completed the podium</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mzhhxclfqou1ozaxrume"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702051157+0000" stop="20240702060217+0000">
    <title lang="en">Viktoriia: Ukraine’s Gymnastics Hope</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the bombs dropped in her hometown of Kyiv and her father left home to fight in the war, Ukrainian rhythmic gymnast Viktoriia Onopriienko battled daily to make her dream – competing in Paris 2024 – come true. This documentary showcases her grit, resilience and determination in her inspiring journey to compete at the Olympic Games. Discover the indomitable spirit of this young athlete as she prepares to represent Ukraine on the world stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yulo58mhebnhzqdn48mp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702060000+0000" stop="20240702061859+0000">
    <title lang="en">Enzo Lefort's quest for individual gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore Enzo Lefort's journey from his Guadeloupean roots to the Paris 2024 Olympics, driven by his ambition for individual gold. Witness his rigorous training regimen and unwavering determination, fueled by past victories at World Championships and Olympic Games in the team events. As the Games draw near, Lefort's focus intensifies as he prepares to compete on home turf, aiming to etch his name in Olympic history with a triumphant performance in a memorable venue: le Grand Palais at the heart of Paris. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dttzimmubmjhc96oh6kn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702061859+0000" stop="20240702063630+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Girl India aims for historic gold at Paris 2024 | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow India's remarkable journey from hometown studio of La Hague to the Olympic stage. While she qualified for the Games at the European Championships, with her unique style blending raw energy and finesse, she faces formidable rivals on her quest for breaking glory. Will her unmatched determination and skill make history at the Olympics where the sport is making its debut at Paris 2024?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fgps2zdjfhlhkjt0cnid"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702063630+0000" stop="20240702065230+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kauli Vaast’s Tahitian roots make him a favourite for Gold | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Witness Kauli Vaast's journey from his childhood Tahitian shores to the world stage. Surrounded by his family and long time friend and mentor Jeremy Flores, he refines his craft at Teahupo'o impressive pipe where he will compete on hometurf for an Olympic Gold medal in surfing. Driven by passion and cheered on by those who believe in his dream, he balances the thrill of competition with the warmth of a unique community.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/atn7hr8mywzvlqx35qmf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702065230+0000" stop="20240702071030+0000">
    <title lang="en">Kieran Reilly’s ride to the world stage | Athletes to Watch</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Kieran Reilly on his quest for Olympic glory as he reflects on his journey from Gateshead to becoming BMX world champion. He navigates the challenges of training, family support, and personal growth, while striving to make his hometown proud. Follow his inspirational story as he prepares to represent his community at the next Olympic Games in Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/iugk9xuu6whsufdols9z"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702071030+0000" stop="20240702094750+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's Artistic Gymnastics All Around | Rio 2016 | Great Olympic Moments</title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch the artistic gymnastics individual all around from the Rio Summer Olympic Games in 2016 and follow Simone Biles and Alexandra Raisman as they win gold and silver for the USA and Aliya Mustafina as she claims bronze for Russia</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q00hnptow4cpcjpa8bcp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702094750+0000" stop="20240702114122+0000">
    <title lang="en">SWE v ESP - Men's Quarter-Final - Handball | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This Men's Quarterfinal Match took place on 03/08/2021 at the Yoyogi National Stadium, Tokyo. Final Score ESP 34:33 SWE</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pndsrr1owdjlc54ukmtj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702114122+0000" stop="20240702193340+0000">
    <title lang="en">Women's -49kg &amp; Men's -58kg R16/Quarter-Finals/Semi-Finals - Taekwondo | Tokyo 2020 Replays</title>
    <desc lang="en">This event took place on 24/07/2021 at the Makuhari Messe Hall A, Tokyo. It includes the Women's -49 kg and the Men's -58 kg Round of 16, Quarterfinals and Semifinals.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dy9aex4dupmvvpaxwsyv"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702193340+0000" stop="20240702195033+0000">
    <title lang="en">Meet Flo Meiler the 85-year-old grandma breaking world records</title>
    <desc lang="en">Flo started to pole vault at 65. Every day she proves that age is no barrier. She is one of the most decorated senior athletes ever. We follow her as she is getting ready to shatter and set more world records at the National Senior Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bm6nwjfcnpflcgwtjyhc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20240702195033+0000" stop="20240703025725+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men's Road Race | Rio 2016 | Great Olympic Moments</title>
    <desc lang="en">Greg van Avermaet wins the Gold for Belgium, Jakob Fuglsang the Silver for Denmark and Rafal Majka the Bronze for Poland in the men's cycling road race at the Rio Summer Olympic Games in 2016</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mb14xd0ilbi669mbcigd"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
