<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="TVCTC" source-info-url="https://olympics.com" time-created="2025-06-22 00:00:04">
  <channel id="olympic-channel.olympics.com">
    <display-name>Olympic Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thumbs2.imgbox.com/45/27/1M1IrWhV_t.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250621235403+0000" stop="20250622001132+0000">
    <title lang="en">Khalifa: An Olympic dream in the heart of Africa’s football powerhouse | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young Ghanian football player takes us into his world. Through his community, family and team we learn why football is so important to him and what he hopes to accomplish one day.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vgqzngvj1o4cwr6mqjs6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622001132+0000" stop="20250622002723+0000">
    <title lang="en">Aya: the first female swimmer to represent Gabon at the Olympics | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">An Olympic swimmer overcomes her tragic past and is determined to keep swimming. We see the inspiring relationship she has with her father as they train for future competitions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ln7ihg4fero3yvf6n1ia"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622002723+0000" stop="20250622004423+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayomide: Born in a canoe, now a Nigerian rowing star | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Her mother gave birth to her inside a canoe some 20 years ago. Ayomide Bello grew up to become the first female canoeist from Nigeria to qualify for the Olympics.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/hvr9skjd78d5ohz9hody"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622004423+0000" stop="20250622005944+0000">
    <title lang="en">Miyanda: the lioness of Southafica’s BMX scene | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">Miyanda Masseti is the highest ranked female BMX rider in Africa, shows us what inspires her to keep pushing and opening new possibilities for future female BMX riders in Africa.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ce6pgaujuftmx9lth3we"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622005944+0000" stop="20250622011427+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ornella: knocking down social prejudices pursuing her Olympic dream | Playing Fields</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the first female boxer to represent her country, Ornella shows us why it’s important for the world to see more female African boxers on the global stage.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dob7vauikkp9fiqjge6t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622011427+0000" stop="20250622024516+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: 1.6 Seconds | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">This feature documentary dives into the life of the UK’s diving legend. From Beijing 2008 to his gold medal in Tokyo 2020 and final Olympics in Paris 2024, Daley shares his personal journey, the pressures, losses, and triumphs that defined his career. Exclusive footage and candid moments reveal a story of resilience and growth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xgpfd7xks6xvxhiuxs2n"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622024516+0000" stop="20250622030720+0000">
    <title lang="en">B-Boys and B-Girls Take The Spotlight | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">As breaking prepares to make its Olympics debut in Paris 2024, we go inside the lives and regimens of the top breakers in the world leading up to the games. We meet b-boy Victor and b-girl Nicka who have secured Olympic spots, along with Olympic hopeful b-girl Anti still battling her way to the top. They all meet up in Los Angeles for one of the top event of the scene.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fwxkuqavk3lizzafvwh9"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622030720+0000" stop="20250622032956+0000">
    <title lang="en">Nicka takes it to the next level | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">As b-girl Nicka continues her intense preparation for the Games, Anti is about to take on a new opponent at the WDSF Breaking for Gold Series in Hong Kong: Japanese b-girl Ayane, whose brother b-boy Shigekix has already confirmed his spot on Team Japan. The energy in Hong Kong is intense as Ayane tries to make a final push to reach the Olympic Qualifiying Series.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/pqvabpybcovdejw3xk2p"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622032956+0000" stop="20250622044533+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Golden Generation | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">How a once-in-a-generation Argentina men's basketball team, led by Manu Ginobili, brought down the USA “Dream Team” and won the gold at the Athens 2004 Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/htzqidm5i5a69jgxnnt3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622044533+0000" stop="20250622054143+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622054143+0000" stop="20250622060220+0000">
    <title lang="en">Pamela Rosa: The Champion | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pamela Rosa from São Paulo, Brazil, is a former women’s world champion in skateboarding. With two X-Games wins and four other podium finishes, she represented Brazil in skateboarding's Olympic debut. Despite an injury in Tokyo, she reclaimed the world champion title in 2021. As a key member of the Brazilian national team, Pamela continues to be one of the most recognizable and formidable skaters in the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/r0j731fwy4kw0rnwjrdq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622060000+0000" stop="20250622065351+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rise of Women Olympians</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 1 : The story of Women at the Games, Rise of Women Olympians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxcua384ycbgx9v2zjyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622065351+0000" stop="20250622070930+0000">
    <title lang="en">Funa Nakayama: The Groundbreaker | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hailing from Toyama City, Funa Nakayama has quickly risen through the skateboarding ranks. At just 18, she's competed in top contests worldwide, earning accolades, including a bronze medal in the 2020 Tokyo Olympics. Follow Funa's journey of hard work, skill, and dedication as she breaks new ground in skateboarding.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fmeqt3znvclebptpucuh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622070930+0000" stop="20250622072552+0000">
    <title lang="en">Pamela Rosa: The Champion | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pamela Rosa from São Paulo, Brazil, is a former women’s world champion in skateboarding. With two X-Games wins and four other podium finishes, she represented Brazil in skateboarding's Olympic debut. Despite an injury in Tokyo, she reclaimed the world champion title in 2021. As a key member of the Brazilian national team, Pamela continues to be one of the most recognizable and formidable skaters in the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/r0j731fwy4kw0rnwjrdq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622072552+0000" stop="20250622074012+0000">
    <title lang="en">Chloe Covell: The Rising Star | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Australian sensation whose meteoric rise in the skateboarding world has made her a formidable competitor and a beloved figure in the street scene. Follow Chloe as she challenges the best, forms lasting friendships, and takes one step closer to her Olympic dream. Chloe's journey is one of passion, dedication, and the relentless pursuit of greatness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/g8zkfmhjkndqnnxppw8p"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622074012+0000" stop="20250622075156+0000">
    <title lang="en">Paige Heyn: On the road to Paris | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">US street skateboarder Paige Heyn is known for her powerful and skilled skating. Originally from California, Paige has quickly risen through the ranks despite numerous struggles on her path to the top. As the US hope for gold, Paige has her sights firmly set on Paris 2024, making her a rising star to watch.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qposo6xmtc8yzkec8kka"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622075156+0000" stop="20250622084515+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Gymnastics Individual All-Around, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could the Olympic men’s individual all-around gymnastics champ strike gold again in 2016? A pair of Europeans aimed for their own glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ugiqndgrb6vvh55fscrp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622084515+0000" stop="20250622101831+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: 1.6 Seconds | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">This feature documentary dives into the life of the UK’s diving legend. From Beijing 2008 to his gold medal in Tokyo 2020 and final Olympics in Paris 2024, Daley shares his personal journey, the pressures, losses, and triumphs that defined his career. Exclusive footage and candid moments reveal a story of resilience and growth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xgpfd7xks6xvxhiuxs2n"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622101831+0000" stop="20250622102725+0000">
    <title lang="en">Michael: No rest on the road to Olympic gold | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Take a look inside Michael Norman’s rigid routine as he prepares to redeem himself with an Olympic gold in the 400m distance at Paris 2024 this summer. While he is visiting his first track and field community, with family and fiancee all behind him, the American sprinter is dedicated to excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/czmk0qtmxfpna25t2i4t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622102725+0000" stop="20250622103609+0000">
    <title lang="en">Phil: breaking barriers to represent his community | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Canadian Breaker Phil ‘Wizard’ Kim, who comes from a traditional Korean family, takes to the streets of Vancouver, where he remembers how he fell in love with breaking and recounts his relentless journey to do what he loves the most : to dance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/v5q27smoc56yyvktpcxx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622103609+0000" stop="20250622104523+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ale: the Mexican diver trying to keep it all in synch | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Alejandra Orozco, two-time Olympic medallist in diving for Mexico, makes her fourth return to the Olympics at Paris 2024. More in sync than ever with her diving partner, Gabriela Agundez, and her family, she takes us back to where it all began: the family farm in the outskirt of Guadaljara. With the support of a loving family, hard work and dedication, she is hoping to reach the pinnacle of her career with Gold this Summer surrounded by her loved ones.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zmfuvbeujwgei666ihwi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622104523+0000" stop="20250622105427+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ni Nengah: a role model and a hero for Indonesia | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">She is Indonesia’s premiere Paralympic powerlifter and the country’s pride. A two-time Paralympic medallist, she is a mentor for the team as she prepares for her next objective: taking gold at Paris 2024 this summer. Although a recent injury puts all her work at risk, she is confident she will rise to the challenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yqud48fm2bapbaqqzjjq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622105427+0000" stop="20250622114852+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Football Final, Atlanta 1996</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mighty football nation Argentina in an Olympic final against Nigeria hoping to become the first major football champion from Africa. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vnt0fpbnbzdd5ev5rkpm"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622114852+0000" stop="20250622124055+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Gymnastics Individual All-Around, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could the Olympic men’s individual all-around gymnastics champ strike gold again in 2016? A pair of Europeans aimed for their own glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ugiqndgrb6vvh55fscrp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622124055+0000" stop="20250622133527+0000">
    <title lang="en">Triumph and Tragedy | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an emotional journey with his son and grandson, Finland’s Lasse Virén revisits the spot where he rose to his feet after a dramatic fall to win gold. The next day, the spirit of Munich was shattered when a terror attack at the Olympic Village took the lives of 11 Israeli athletes and coaches – a day of tragedy as told by an Israeli survivor, Shaul Ladany, and the gold medallists from around the world who bore witness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ishr6vmaunsc38joibk6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622133527+0000" stop="20250622143112+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622143112+0000" stop="20250622150039+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622150039+0000" stop="20250622152039+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayane and Shigekix, a breaking family | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meet London-based b-girl Stefani who dances for Ukraine. Even though Ukraine’s breaking team is scattered across the globe, it doesn't dampen her spirit — she's all about having fun. Stefani faces b-girl Ayane at Hong Kong. Back in Japan, brother and sister breaking duo Shigekix and Ayane started breaking together. Along the last two years of competition, Shigekix is emerging as a favourite for a medal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aernq7xbxjm3lgtsqy3l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622152039+0000" stop="20250622153911+0000">
    <title lang="en">Who will join B-boy Victor for Team USA | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Victor has secured a spot on Team USA. Who else will make it to Paris 2024? Jeffro is training with b-girl Logistix in Colorado Springs for a pre-Olympic festival in Japan. Each of our world class breakers gears up for the Olympic Qualifier Series and then the ultimate challenge: Olympic Games Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gmepych2lmnulrgigzun"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622153911+0000" stop="20250622171211+0000">
    <title lang="en">La Grande Seine, Paris 2024 Opening Ceremony making-of | The full story</title>
    <desc lang="en">Discover the Paris 2024 Opening Ceremony full preparations, from first sketches until the very end of the show. We follow every aspect, including exclusive access to Celine Dion’s rehearsal, as a small team of dedicated individuals defy all odds to create one of the most incredible TV shows that has ever-been produced.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/l0dfz4hy4ea8imcaxdah"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622171211+0000" stop="20250622172910+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘We’re the Best Team in New York City’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">City soccer is very special in New-York City and MLK sits at the top, with 19 titles in 25 years. The team is off to a new season and gunning for its 20th title. Coach Jake and assistant Kamani welcome the team for their first practice and super-pro prospect Carlos Lainez is back from Spain. TThey will soon play the top Ohio State team. After a rough start, the team is taking shape but it’s a 16 match competition before the play-offs begin.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jkledz0yuuypaxfwd3xu"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622172910+0000" stop="20250622175047+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Guy in the Mirror is Usually the One Stopping You’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Carlos Junior, the team captain and best pro prospect has 13 brothers and sisters, 4 are living with him and his dad in the Bronx. A semi-pro club in Spain offered him a contract but he made the promise to Jake and his MLK family to get them that 20th win. Maynor, also from Honduras, is taking care of his disabled mother. After a shaky start to the season, he comes into his own against Upper West Side rival Beacon.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/bqaakxjnat3fcicgvfvj"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622175047+0000" stop="20250622180923+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘Bacon, Egg and Cheese’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">David Reyes Aka D. Dotty is a burly defender but he is juggling soccer and a burgeoning rap career with the need to help his family earn money in a tough Bronx neighbourhood. He often comes late or tired to the pitch. As the team moves up the rankings, Coach Jake is getting nervous and talks about his past troubles with addiction.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fmh1epkngm7ngg3unml5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622180923+0000" stop="20250622182756+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘You Not Really about it’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">MLK high school has been unstoppable this year. They are about to achieve an undefeated season. But Coach Jake is getting increasingly tense. While some players like Charles are doing great both at school and on the team, others like goalkeeper Raymond are struggling to keep their nerves, putting the whole team at risks. Raymond is trying to live up to the dreams and expectations of his father, a talented goalkeeper himself who never made it pro. Soon the team faces a decisive game which will determine the number one seed in the playoffs.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/if7vuj7ifiybsfkhwmuh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622182756+0000" stop="20250622184430+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘This is What We Live For’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">MLK finally enters the playoffs. Three more games separate the team from their goal but their starting goalkeeper is now suspended. Assistant coach Kimani, both the kids’ chief on-field instructor and off-field confidant, manages to keep the team in balance. His patience combined with Jake’s drive are a perfect match. Defender Vakaba, who has come to New York City to fulfil his dream, joins the team and becomes an essential part of its success.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dp63tlka8kzbj8dfsbhk"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622184430+0000" stop="20250622190915+0000">
    <title lang="en">‘The Only Game that Matter is the Last One’ | We Are King</title>
    <desc lang="en">Can we tell a King player from another player just by his look?. A storybook season must end in storybook fashion. But as MLK is leading in semi-final, top player Carlos get a yellow card against their long-time rivals Beacon. Jake's obsession is now turning into superstition as he makes a final call that will soon turn the team fortune. Maynor, who had seemed to struggle in front of the goal since the start of the season, is proving to be a decisive striker.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wcyl9ogeioantt1eg57k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622190915+0000" stop="20250622200708+0000">
    <title lang="en">Nuffin for Nuffin | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">Forty-five years after their first and only Olympic medal, Bermuda's hopes of glory now rest on the shoulders of a new generation of boxers. See how these young boxers overcome adversity and struggle beyond the ropes to keep this tiny island nation's Olympic dreams alive.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/t9vrzq7ddwpt7dyaegcs"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622200708+0000" stop="20250622210336+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rise of Women Olympians</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 1 : The story of Women at the Games, Rise of Women Olympians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxcua384ycbgx9v2zjyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622210336+0000" stop="20250622211915+0000">
    <title lang="en">Funa Nakayama: The Groundbreaker | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hailing from Toyama City, Funa Nakayama has quickly risen through the skateboarding ranks. At just 18, she's competed in top contests worldwide, earning accolades, including a bronze medal in the 2020 Tokyo Olympics. Follow Funa's journey of hard work, skill, and dedication as she breaks new ground in skateboarding.

</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fmeqt3znvclebptpucuh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622211915+0000" stop="20250622213536+0000">
    <title lang="en">Pamela Rosa: The Champion | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">Pamela Rosa from São Paulo, Brazil, is a former women’s world champion in skateboarding. With two X-Games wins and four other podium finishes, she represented Brazil in skateboarding's Olympic debut. Despite an injury in Tokyo, she reclaimed the world champion title in 2021. As a key member of the Brazilian national team, Pamela continues to be one of the most recognizable and formidable skaters in the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/r0j731fwy4kw0rnwjrdq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622213536+0000" stop="20250622214956+0000">
    <title lang="en">Chloe Covell: The Rising Star | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Australian sensation whose meteoric rise in the skateboarding world has made her a formidable competitor and a beloved figure in the street scene. Follow Chloe as she challenges the best, forms lasting friendships, and takes one step closer to her Olympic dream. Chloe's journey is one of passion, dedication, and the relentless pursuit of greatness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/g8zkfmhjkndqnnxppw8p"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622214956+0000" stop="20250622220141+0000">
    <title lang="en">Paige Heyn: On the road to Paris | skate-hers</title>
    <desc lang="en">US street skateboarder Paige Heyn is known for her powerful and skilled skating. Originally from California, Paige has quickly risen through the ranks despite numerous struggles on her path to the top. As the US hope for gold, Paige has her sights firmly set on Paris 2024, making her a rising star to watch.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/qposo6xmtc8yzkec8kka"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622220141+0000" stop="20250622225553+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Gymnastics Individual All-Around, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could the Olympic men’s individual all-around gymnastics champ strike gold again in 2016? A pair of Europeans aimed for their own glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ugiqndgrb6vvh55fscrp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250622225553+0000" stop="20250623002453+0000">
    <title lang="en">Tom Daley: 1.6 Seconds | Documentary</title>
    <desc lang="en">This feature documentary dives into the life of the UK’s diving legend. From Beijing 2008 to his gold medal in Tokyo 2020 and final Olympics in Paris 2024, Daley shares his personal journey, the pressures, losses, and triumphs that defined his career. Exclusive footage and candid moments reveal a story of resilience and growth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/xgpfd7xks6xvxhiuxs2n"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623002453+0000" stop="20250623003347+0000">
    <title lang="en">Michael: No rest on the road to Olympic gold | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Take a look inside Michael Norman’s rigid routine as he prepares to redeem himself with an Olympic gold in the 400m distance at Paris 2024 this summer. While he is visiting his first track and field community, with family and fiancee all behind him, the American sprinter is dedicated to excellence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/czmk0qtmxfpna25t2i4t"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623003347+0000" stop="20250623004230+0000">
    <title lang="en">Phil: breaking barriers to represent his community | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Canadian Breaker Phil ‘Wizard’ Kim, who comes from a traditional Korean family, takes to the streets of Vancouver, where he remembers how he fell in love with breaking and recounts his relentless journey to do what he loves the most : to dance.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/v5q27smoc56yyvktpcxx"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623004230+0000" stop="20250623005145+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ale: the Mexican diver trying to keep it all in synch | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">Alejandra Orozco, two-time Olympic medallist in diving for Mexico, makes her fourth return to the Olympics at Paris 2024. More in sync than ever with her diving partner, Gabriela Agundez, and her family, she takes us back to where it all began: the family farm in the outskirt of Guadaljara. With the support of a loving family, hard work and dedication, she is hoping to reach the pinnacle of her career with Gold this Summer surrounded by her loved ones.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zmfuvbeujwgei666ihwi"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623005145+0000" stop="20250623010049+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ni Nengah: a role model and a hero for Indonesia | The Starting Line</title>
    <desc lang="en">She is Indonesia’s premiere Paralympic powerlifter and the country’s pride. A two-time Paralympic medallist, she is a mentor for the team as she prepares for her next objective: taking gold at Paris 2024 this summer. Although a recent injury puts all her work at risk, she is confident she will rise to the challenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/yqud48fm2bapbaqqzjjq"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623010049+0000" stop="20250623015252+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Gymnastics Individual All-Around, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could the Olympic men’s individual all-around gymnastics champ strike gold again in 2016? A pair of Europeans aimed for their own glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ugiqndgrb6vvh55fscrp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623015252+0000" stop="20250623024734+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623024734+0000" stop="20250623031701+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623031701+0000" stop="20250623033702+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ayane and Shigekix, a breaking family | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meet London-based b-girl Stefani who dances for Ukraine. Even though Ukraine’s breaking team is scattered across the globe, it doesn't dampen her spirit — she's all about having fun. Stefani faces b-girl Ayane at Hong Kong. Back in Japan, brother and sister breaking duo Shigekix and Ayane started breaking together. Along the last two years of competition, Shigekix is emerging as a favourite for a medal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/aernq7xbxjm3lgtsqy3l"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623033702+0000" stop="20250623035533+0000">
    <title lang="en">Who will join B-boy Victor for Team USA | Breaking Life, Road to Paris 2024</title>
    <desc lang="en">Victor has secured a spot on Team USA. Who else will make it to Paris 2024? Jeffro is training with b-girl Logistix in Colorado Springs for a pre-Olympic festival in Japan. Each of our world class breakers gears up for the Olympic Qualifier Series and then the ultimate challenge: Olympic Games Paris 2024.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/gmepych2lmnulrgigzun"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623035533+0000" stop="20250623052833+0000">
    <title lang="en">La Grande Seine, Paris 2024 Opening Ceremony making-of | The full story</title>
    <desc lang="en">Discover the Paris 2024 Opening Ceremony full preparations, from first sketches until the very end of the show. We follow every aspect, including exclusive access to Celine Dion’s rehearsal, as a small team of dedicated individuals defy all odds to create one of the most incredible TV shows that has ever-been produced.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/l0dfz4hy4ea8imcaxdah"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623052833+0000" stop="20250623060219+0000">
    <title lang="en">Doubles Trouble: Rohan Bopanna’s Olympic Journey</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join India’s top men’s doubles tennis player, Rohan Bopanna, as he seeks the perfect partner for Paris 2024. Relive his historic victories, heartbreaking defeats, and past Olympic adventures and witness his relentless pursuit of excellence at age 44. Will he bring India a long-awaited tennis medal?
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lkddil6h07ayv2w3yss5"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623060000+0000" stop="20250623065336+0000">
    <title lang="en">Olympic spirit : The story of the torch</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 3 : The Olympic spirit : The story of the torch.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/d9hqaosoc2lciqdjhidc"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623065336+0000" stop="20250623072057+0000">
    <title lang="en">Brazil’s Jackie Silva (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Olympic gold medallist Jackie Silva won a historic title in Atlanta. Now, the Brazilian legend helps troubled youth shape up through sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/sowqmooymlc1xjs03g4k"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623072057+0000" stop="20250623074746+0000">
    <title lang="en">United States’ Michael Johnson (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">History-making Olympic champion Michael Johnson continues to connect with the next generation and loves making a difference</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zz9vah3rdbl2umai4eek"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623074746+0000" stop="20250623081429+0000">
    <title lang="en">Canada’s Clara Hughes (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Clara Hughes was a troubled teen but the multiple Olympic medallist was saved by sport and is determined to help others find the right path</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/mawo8pwy6snt9da2mmuw"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623081429+0000" stop="20250623084149+0000">
    <title lang="en">Romania’s Nadia Comaneci (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romania’s Nadia Comaneci scored the first perfect 10 in gymnastics but is finding a new thrill coaching and helping people in her homeland</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/lfxs9rqbceh0ekxkdaeb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623084149+0000" stop="20250623093401+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Olympic Series: The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.3, Program 4 : The Olympic spirit : Redefining sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/nsou8dw7a1xyj4omjz1v"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623093401+0000" stop="20250623104837+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Golden Generation | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">How a once-in-a-generation Argentina men's basketball team, led by Manu Ginobili, brought down the USA “Dream Team” and won the gold at the Athens 2004 Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/htzqidm5i5a69jgxnnt3"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623104837+0000" stop="20250623114126+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Basketball Final, London 2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the closest finish in 40 years, the USA played Spain for the men's basketball gold medal, in a thrilling rematch. </desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxghggiuz8etqdt6y6lb"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623114126+0000" stop="20250623120914+0000">
    <title lang="en">Ethiopia’s Haile Gebrselassie</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two-time Olympic champion Haile Gebrselassie is combining life as a businessman with paving the way for the next generation of athletes</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/twep3ocjvzvvaourtc6x"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623120914+0000" stop="20250623123702+0000">
    <title lang="en">Australia’s Ian Thorpe (extended)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ian Thorpe is one of the greatest swimmers ever, but after leaving the sport he had to overcome a dark personal time before inspiring others</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/jp21nc0mw3ls4cywjn8d"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623123702+0000" stop="20250623133038+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Aquatics</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best diving, swimming and water polo stories from throughout Olympic history including Dawn Fraser, Greg Louganis and Michael Phelps.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/vydzinqyv16sh5trwq8a"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623133038+0000" stop="20250623142327+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Marathon</title>
    <desc lang="en">The best moments from the Olympic Games’ ultimate endurance events with stories from Emil Zatopek and Frank Shorter.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/dxjn2qu7uybyharsdyfe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623142327+0000" stop="20250623153036+0000">
    <title lang="en">The Distance | Five Rings Films</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of an enduring Japanese marathon tradition and a humble champion named Naoko Takahashi who captured her nation’s imagination with a run for the ages at the 2000 Olympic Games.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/t0bphzone9fzs3b5voxe"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623153036+0000" stop="20250623162357+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Middle Distance</title>
    <desc lang="en">The stories behind the key moments in middle distance running at the Olympic Games, including stars like Paavo Nurmi and Maria Mutola.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/weswph1l0navqhgryspy"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623162357+0000" stop="20250623171649+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Athletics - The Sprinters</title>
    <desc lang="en">A journey through the essential stories of the Olympic Games, focusing on the sprints in athletics, including Jesse Owens and Carl Lewis.
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/a10ssakopgyui2lshtxf"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623171649+0000" stop="20250623181157+0000">
    <title lang="en">Becoming an Olympic Legend | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after his famous tally of seven Olympic gold medals and seven world records, legendary swimmer Mark Spitz makes an emotional return to Munich Olympic Park and the swimming pool, where his life was changed forever.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/fu8b8krwuc98ozzpiroo"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623181157+0000" stop="20250623190658+0000">
    <title lang="en">Gold Medals Relived | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">US athletic comeback star Dave Wottle, Germany’s celebrated gymnast Karin Janz, acclaimed sprinter Valerii Borzov, and nine-time Olympic medallist Ludmilla Tourischeva revisit their gold medal journeys during Munich 1972.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/q2qupehpqfcq4l36umky"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623190658+0000" stop="20250623200019+0000">
    <title lang="en">Road to Glory - Gymnastics</title>
    <desc lang="en">Glorious gymnastics moments spanning the history of the Olympic Games, including Olga Korbut, Nadia Comaneci and Yukio Endo.
 
</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/zhv3fy9vle8wby95tagn"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623200019+0000" stop="20250623205413+0000">
    <title lang="en">Men’s Gymnastics Individual All-Around, Rio 2016</title>
    <desc lang="en">Could the Olympic men’s individual all-around gymnastics champ strike gold again in 2016? A pair of Europeans aimed for their own glory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ugiqndgrb6vvh55fscrp"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623205413+0000" stop="20250623214848+0000">
    <title lang="en">Triumph and Tragedy | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an emotional journey with his son and grandson, Finland’s Lasse Virén revisits the spot where he rose to his feet after a dramatic fall to win gold. The next day, the spirit of Munich was shattered when a terror attack at the Olympic Village took the lives of 11 Israeli athletes and coaches – a day of tragedy as told by an Israeli survivor, Shaul Ladany, and the gold medallists from around the world who bore witness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/ishr6vmaunsc38joibk6"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623214848+0000" stop="20250623224331+0000">
    <title lang="en">Memory Lane | 72 - A Gathering of Champions</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fifty years after their Olympic victories in Munich, famed gymnast Olga Korbut, Germany’s long jump star Heide Rosendahl, Kenya’s long-distance running hero Kip Keino and Great Britain’s celebrated pentathlete Mary Peters make an emotional return to the scene of their gold medal wins.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/znepfamdwqwctyz7izbz"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623224331+0000" stop="20250623233642+0000">
    <title lang="en">Rise of Women Olympians</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 1 : The story of Women at the Games, Rise of Women Olympians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/wxcua384ycbgx9v2zjyh"/>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="olympic-channel.olympics.com" start="20250623233642+0000" stop="20250624002904+0000">
    <title lang="en">Changing Times</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Olympic Series Vol.5, Program 3 : The story of Women at the Games, Changing Times.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sport</category>
    <icon src="https://img.olympics.com/images/image/private/t_16-9_1280/primary/b8xuec9fx6q15w22jd72"/>
  </programme>
</tv>
